Chapter 668: Annihilation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Eh?" Garen did not expect that this armor could have such a high defense. This defensive strength already belonged to the highest level. He had not held back when he'd thrown the fragments just now. Although he hadn't used acceleration to increase their impact, the strength of the fragments alone was enough to create a tremendous impact. The weight of several tons crashed into them, which was equivalent to a heavy truck crashing into them at full speed. They could even get out of that alive with nothing but concussions.

He walked towards them and grabbed one of the armored members.

"Let me try again."

He grabbed the person's neck with one of his hands and grabbed onto his waist with his other hand and pulled.

Peng!

It sounded like steel tendons were being torn apart.

Garen was even more amazed now.

Suddenly, he felt some slight movement from the armored person in front of him. This person had not fainted and had just been pretending. A fine blue needle popped out from his wrist guard and shot towards Garen's abdomen.

The needle had been smeared with black poison and it stabbed into Garen's skin. It only penetrated Garen's skin slightly and left a white spot before it fell to the ground.

The pair of eyes inside the armor now held a trace of despair.

"Hey," Garen gave a low snarl and put strength into his hands.

Hiss!

The whole armor was torn into two pieces and thrown aside.

Blood splattered on to the ground. The others seemed to have truly fainted. They did not have the slightest reaction.

His strategy was raiding the base at breakneck speed so that they would have no time to react. True enough, they could only hastily assemble their elite unit which was defeated.

Garen stamped on each of their heads and crushed them like he was stepping on watermelons. The strongest elite squad in White Phoenix's entire organization was wiped out just like that.

He looked around and saw that with the flashing of the alarm, the doors of the elevator leading upstairs were closing. It was already half-closed. His toes moved and a piece of debris flew out. It was accurately stuck between the elevator's doors so that it could not close completely.

Only then, Garen slowly walked over, pried the elevator's doors open and entered it.

When he'd just walked in, the top corner of the elevator sprayed out a white mist with a hissing sound.

"Poison gas?" Garen took a sniff and no longer cared about it. He had seven points of vitality after all. In the face of poison like this, he would only treat it as though it was a diluted pepper spray. Other than the fact that it was slightly suffocating, it has no other effects.

Pressing the buttons on the elevator, there was no reaction. It seemed the elevator had been locked down.

"Interesting," Garen smirked and looked upwards.

******************

"Hurry up!! Lock down all the elevators below the third basement immediately! Activate all of the automatic weapons!" in the main control room, a woman issued one order after another nervously.

Behind her were more than ten personnel sitting in rows. Some were monitoring the computers, some were adjusting equipment and some were very tense, with their hands and legs shaking and despaired expressions on their faces.

The woman calmed herself down and quickly issued a few more orders.

"Mr. Rod, soon there will be people escorting you safely out of the base. Please rest assured, we are absolutely confident that we are able to guarantee your safety."

The woman turned back and spoke towards a man wearing a white armor.

"I believe in the captain's arrangement but what is his current status?" Rod frowned and asked. His current organization was on the same level as the Primary Colors' White Phoenix. He was naturally clear on the strength of the White Phoenix. Their power was something that could not be easily overturned.

"Rest assured, Captain's condition is still well except that he's in a stalemate." the woman replied while hiding the truth from Rod. Although she tried her best to appear calm, this time, she really had no idea what kind of enemy the White Phoenix had encountered. The enemy was just a single person and he'd charged in here crashing everywhere, claiming to be the Nighthawk King. He completely disregarded any kind of attack whether it was guns, bombs, lasers and high-speed cutting knives. Everything was useless against him!

That horrifying figure was now moving upwards using the stairs. As for the captain… White Phoenix Captain's current status was unknown and they could not contact him. The rest of the people were seen clearly using the surveillance camera, and they'd been killed easily.

"Damn it! It just had to be at this time when all the higher-ups are absent!" the woman thought viciously. If only the Lotus Pearl and Gremlin were here! This guy would not be so arrogant!

Rod did not ask anymore. It was just that he was feeling uneasy. Even the White Phoenix was acting as though they were facing a formidable enemy. He did not know what sort of enemy they had provoked, but it seemed that not even the White Phoenix captain could suppress him. He'd personally met that small elite team. It was a team composed of the most elite mercenaries wearing special armor. Neither bullets nor lasers were effective on it and it was equipped with hidden killing machinery. It was definitely the most potent killing machine.

Crash!!

Suddenly, there was a sound of broken glass. Rod had only half worn the armor before he saw that amidst countless screams, a large hole had opened up within the floor of the main control room. A hand had directly smashed the tempered glass on the floor and was grasping at the edge of the hole.

"Open fire! Open fire!!" The woman screamed in a distorted voice but she herself had retreated backward. With the escort of several guards, they retreated to the emergency elevator. Without even seeing the results, they had planned to escape.

Rod's heart thumped. He immediately ran in the opposite direction of where the woman had fled, which was the ordinary staircase.

More than ten subordinates followed behind him.

"Do not stand with the people from White Phoenix! We use the stairs!" Rod immediate made a decision and shouted. He quickly sprinted to the stairs and ran upwards. He felt his heart beating profusely while cold sweat oozed from his skin and was blown dry by the cool wind.

Each of his men showed a terrified expression but they were still able to keep themselves in check.

"He did not come for us. As long as we do not provoke him, nothing will happen to us!" One of his subordinates quickly said.

"We need to show our identity and let that person know that we're not with the White Phoenix!" someone quickly said.

"How do we show?"

"Let's get out of here first!"

His subordinates quickly gave out their opinions.

Rod tried to calm himself down. He'd experienced such situations multiple times and he knew that he could only bet on his luck now, as the identity and allegiance of the other party were unknown. Now he could only hope that the woman from White Phoenix could hold on. It would perfect if she died only after they'd escaped from the base.

How could he not know that the White Phoenix elite team were mostly dead now? He no longer held any hope for them.

As time went on, their running speed and the rhythms of their breathing were getting faster, but everyone here had been specially trained so this sort of run was nothing to them.

At this moment, the wall on the left side in front of them was smashed open and a figure lightly jumped out.

Rod stopped and looked up the stairs, aghast. He saw a man with sun-tanned muscles shaking his head and moving his shoulders.

"Wait! We're not White Phoenix's people!!" He quickly shouted, using the international lingua franca from America.

Hu…

A gust of wind stopped in front of Rod's forehead. There was a piece of black metal that seemed to be part of a machine. One side of it was sharp and the other side blunt.

The fragments stopped firmly in front of the middle of his forehead, almost touching his skin.

Only then, Rod saw that with a flash, the man that was standing up there had appeared in front of him. He was holding firmly onto the fragments so that it did not pierce him.

Rod was covered in cold sweat. A moment could decide whether he would live or die. Just a little more and he would've been sacrificed, he knew that he wouldn't be able to forget this experience for his whole life.

"We're not White Phoenix's people!" He stared at this man's mask and repeated firmly while barely suppressing the fear in his heart. "We just came here to deliver something. Our group is Rexott Group, specializing in firearms and all kinds of precious metals. Maybe we can cooperate with each other!"

He quickly put out the advantages of his group. Rexott Group was one of the top groups in the world. Naturally, a lot of people have heard of them. Maybe the other party might give them some face.

All the subordinates behind looked as though they'd met a formidable enemy. Their faces were pale and none of them dared to move. The hole that had been smashed open in the hall just now had left them with the horrifying impression of a non-human.

"Rexott Group?" The other party's voice sounded pleasant, charming and tempting. Just based on the voice, the other party was at least a man of good looks and temperament.

There were fifty organizations that were considered the world's top organizations, known as The World's Top Fifty. Primary Colors was one of the top-ranking organizations, and Rexott was around the same ranking. Both had their ups and downs but always ranked within the top ten. They were extremely powerful and their connections were everywhere. It was said that they had close relationships with many big countries.

Garen immediately understood these people's backings. Although both his disciples, Hochman and Dahm could sweep through half of America and they had strong financial power and large forces, even when adding in the combat clubs, they were far from competing with giants like Primary Colors and Rexott. These organizations could directly face the top levels of countries. Their policies and actions could even affect a country's decisions and were not simply economic empires.

This was a circle of organizations that had come to a compromise after countless struggles. Perhaps, Hochman and Dahm's families would need a very long time to get into this circle. This was the gap in their history.

Besides, as long as there was no vacancy, they had to develop their potential and then drag down one of the groups to have a chance at joining.

However, this was not easy. A top circle like this was actually closely related to the supernatural powers of this world and was not merely a circle for humans.

A thought flashed through his mind and Garen put down the fragment in his hand.

"Rexott Group, my aim is only the Primary Colors' White Phoenix. Since you guys are not Primary Colors' people, I'll let you guys go."

Hu… once these words came out, this group of people could not help but let out a sigh of relief. Seeing that Garen had caught up with them, they clearly understood that the leaders of the Primary Colors' White Phoenix had mostly been annihilated. Otherwise, this man would not have the time to catch them.

From the moment Garen had appeared, Rod had been observing him carefully as though trying to figure out something.

However, the more he looked at him, the more horrified he was.

'He… he was actually an ordinary human!!!!' his heart was like a stormy sea.

No features belonging to the Blood Breeds! No features belonging to the Witches!

The parameters that were scanned from his wrists and sent back to his earphones indicated that he was just a human with excessive parameters!

Chapter 669: Annihilation 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Gulp…

Rod barely managed to squeeze out a smile while trying to suppress the horror in his heart.

"Thank you for your kindness, I'm called Rod Okland. May I know your name? The Rexott Group would not forget your favor."

He was full of sincerity, thinking of the direction and hope that the higher-ups had been searching for all this time. He knew that this man in front of him might be the hope they were looking for!

If he could really make a connection with him…

His heart began pounding again and he could not calm it no matter how had he tried. He even thought that his subordinates and this man in front of him could hear his heartbeat.

Their group had been searching for too long. The higher-ups had begun searching hundreds of years ago for that glimmer of light. However, one disappointment after another, one failure after another, had made everyone disheartened and turned their direction to the external armor and other sorts of research on equipment.

Yet now, this man in front of him…

"My name? I'm called Garen." Garen did not have any intention to hide his identity. Such a large organization could find out information about him easily as long as they wanted and he was lazy to hide it.

"Garen…" Rod could no longer resist. A startling thought flashed across his mind, and although his heart was tangled and hesitant, he finally decided and gulped, "May I have the pleasure to invite you to a dinner? We've only had a simple relationship with the Primary Colors where we exchange materials with each other, so you don't have to worry about us cooperating with Primary Colors. You can confirm this anytime. Not long ago, our core mercenary group clashed with the Primary Colors' Ohio Silk mercenary group and both sides received damages and were injured."

Garen was slightly stunned and for the first time, he took a closer look at his person in front of him.

This man knew that he'd slaughtered the Primary Colors' White Phoenix and yet he had the guts to invite him to dinner. Such nerves and such courage, as an ordinary person, he was excellent.

"Rod. I will remember your name."

He pondered for a bit and said, "Coincidentally, I need you to do me a little favor."

"What is it? Please say it, as long as it's within my means, I will not reject it!" Rod hurriedly answered. From the result that he'd received when he'd scanned the other party with the bracelet and analyzed with their base's database, he was even more confident in his judgment and the words he'd said. Although making contact with this person would provoke the Primary Colors' discontentment and fury, this person might be the hope that their higher-ups had been looking for. If there were further results, they might even be willing to help him fight the Primary Colors!

"I still have a captive. One killer's squad captain from the Primary Colors, but I feel that she still has some value and I need you to help me find a place to hide her."

It was obvious from Garen's words that letting Rod help him find a place was to pull him into this mess. Once the Primary Colors discovered this, naturally he would also bear some responsibility.

Rod suddenly hesitated but once his sight swept over the man's eye which held a trace of bloodlust, his heart trembled.

"No… no problem! Just a trifling matter," he replied while trying to calm himself.

"There's no problem then," Garen nodded in satisfaction. He turned around and walked up the stairs while beckoning, "Come with me."

He walked for a short distance and arrived in front of a map. Previously, he'd memorized nearly the entire structure of the base.

Now, he was familiar with it.

Rod and his subordinates behind sighed in relief.

"Sir, what now?"

His subordinate stepped forward and whispered in Indigenous people's language.

"What else can we do? Follow him," Rod replied in an annoyed tone, using an abstruse Indigenous people's language. There were at least dozens of indigenous languages in Mexico and the language they chose was a type that was almost lost. In order to deal with special situations like this, this served as an appropriate internal communication tool.

"But, agreeing with that man's request, what do we do about the Primary Colors' side?" his subordinate asked. He understood the risk that came with this request. Although he did not understand the reason his leader actively sought the man in front of them, this did not prevent him from analyzing this situation.

This would drag them into the fight between this man and the Primary Colors.

Rod was advancing while staring at that man's back.

"Daring to charge into the Primary Colors' base alone, if it's not absolute certainty, then it's absolute confidence in himself. No matter which is it, this person is not someone that is easier to deal with even when compared to Primary Colors. Before we understand the full picture, it is better that we do not make any move or promise."

After he'd calmed down, Rod felt that the invitation just now was a bit reckless, but he was unwilling to lose this opportunity. If this man was truly the hope they'd been looking for, his position within the organization and his right to speak would improve greatly.

They did not speak anymore. The subordinate was a clever man. He could see that Rod was taking a gamble.

After Garen left the base and took a few steps out of the tattered metallic door, he heard the sound of an explosion behind him.

The ground shook violently.

Garen turned towards the group of people and smiled.

"Using their bombs to make some fireworks seemed to have a good effect"

"This guy… blew up the entire White Phoenix base…" Rod muttered. Although he had some speculations, he could not help but feel a chill in his heart. These methods of his were too vicious.

The Primary Colors would definitely go to war! No matter what sort of reason and excuse was given, the higher-ups of the Primary Colors wouldn't meekly accept this.

Some people gulped. They knew that the White Phoenix base was done for. This base that the Primary Colors had invested hundreds of billions had been destroyed in a huge explosion and had become an underground mass of scrap metal. A loss of hundreds of billions was in no way a small amount, even for their Roxett Group. Although this base was just an ordinary storage base, the materials inside also cost a lot of money.

They stood in front of the doorway. Vaguely, they could hear the sound of explosions in the base that might've been due to some device that had blown up. They could also hear the cries of some people that did not make it out in time.

"Help!" "No! No!!..."

"Run! It's going to explode again!"

The sounds came from the ground. With Garen's keen hearing, he could clearly hear the sounds of the movement under the ground, along with shouting, cries for help, screaming and running footsteps together with the sound of the collapsing building.

The number of people that were too late to escape was estimated to be in the hundreds. From the beginning of his raid to the end when he came out, the time he took was less than ten minutes. In such a short time, many people had been inside the base without knowing what was happening.

"Pity…" Rod's complexion changed and drew a cross over his chest and prayed for the people trapped underground.

He glanced at Garen. Hundreds of people had died and a lot of them were innocent, but these seemed to have no effect on Garen. He did not mind the horror that was occurring underground.

"Let's go. We're going to see our cute little kitty," Garen called. After settling the base, his mood seemed to be good as he strode towards the forest.

He was now very interested in the little kitty who had attacked him. The girl called Semone led him all the way to this base under the influence of Fantasy Fist. She would definitely be on the White Phoenix' kill list.

Before he'd left, Garen did not left any bindings or prohibitions on her and only told her of this fact. She was a clever person and must have realized that going back would mean forfeiting her life. Between life and death, the choice a clever person would make was evident.

However, what Garen was interested in was not her cleverness but the trait that she had shown in the villa. The Invisible Creature seemed to be attracted to her.

‘Her mind must have been damaged by Fantasy Fist and triggered her hidden talent to attract the Invisible Creature,' Black Sethe explained. ‘What are you going to do with that Semone?'

"Isn't it just right to use her to understand more about the Invisible Creatures?" Garen said while leading Rod and his men.

He split the bushes in front of him with a machete to reveal a path that was wide enough for one man to travel. Those spiders, lizards, and snakes were scared off by the aura that came from his body and did not dare to approach. Some of the slower flying insects were swept over by his aura and fell down like rain.

‘What happened at the villa should be a coincidence. The invisible creatures are not something that will come out when you want them to. Their cycle of time is very long, so if you want to use this trait of hers, I'm afraid you will be disappointed,' Black Sethe laughed. ‘If you have so much time, why not search for more Void Creatures and kill them to collect Void Core to treat your eye? Your eye might be able to recover slowly.'

"This eye is still able to recover?" Garen was stunned and asked.

‘Of course! Why do you think I would bother collecting Void Cores? That thing is effective in treating injuries from Void Creatures and Rebels. It just takes a long time. Though if it was converted into Medicine Stone, it will shorten the time,' Black Sethe explained. ‘But this is only when the distance between you and Nadia is still far. If you are closer and within the effective range for all kinds of curses, you'll be in big trouble. Without the Void Core or Medicine Stone, you can't make a dent in the curse. This is the case if you are a Pursuer. If it's any other common creature, they can only face the curses head on and tried their best to resist them. Without the special trait of Pursuer, Void Core is useless for them,' Black Sethe laughed twice and continued. ‘Now you understand the importance of Void Core?'

Garen nodded his head and took note of it mentally. Truthfully, from his first encounter with Nadia, perhaps the one that had occurred in a dream, he had not felt much danger. He was not anxious at all; although Nadia said she would arrive soon, she was so far away. As long as he prevented her from knowing his coordinates, he would be able to delay her arrival indefinitely.

Hence, there had been no sense of urgency in his heart, but Black Sethe's words had woken him. As the Nine-Headed Dragon King, Nadia did not need to arrive in this world herself. Her long-distance projection was powerful, and together with curses and combat techniques, she would be terrifying to deal with.

Garen could not forget the time when he was cursed and had his attributes decayed. He would have to dedicate some effort to searching for more potential points to improve his body. If he received a more powerful curse at a time when he'd run out of Void Cores and was consequently unable to lift the curse, he would end up miserable.

His extremely strong body was his biggest shield. Now that Black Sethe mentioned the curse, he decided to be warier.

A curse from an ordinary Void Worm could already diminish his attributes, and if it was replaced by Nadia's curse…

Chapter 670: Annihilation 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"That mask has to be found as fast as possible. The accumulation of the void creature’s hollow core is also another urgent matter."

"It is good that you understand." Black Sethe was relieved, "You and I are now in one body. If you die, I will die too, and I do not wish for you innocently fall into your own carelessness."

Garen nodded his head.

"Perhaps I have been relaxed in this world for too long now…" He came to some realization, "Then, the search for the Twelve Masks will have to speed up."

"As long as you understand that the amount of time we have left is not much," Black Sethe pleasingly went back into hiding.

Walking in the thick and dark forest, Garen had very quickly returned to the previous trees with the round arch root.

Under the roots, the black bonfire ash was still there. Instead, the girl’s shadow was missing.

Garen took a look around, and his gaze stopped upon a dense cluster of black flowers.

"You can come out."

He said in a low voice.

Rod and the rest quietly stopped behind him, as they waited and see if changes would occur.

Soon, among the flowers, a blackish figure that was covered in black mud slowly stood up.

"How did you find me?" The figure gave out a girl’s voice.

"You are too weak."

Garen walked over and pressed his huge hands on her shoulder. She was slightly startled.

Buzz...

A severe yet frequent tremor suddenly rang out. It was as if the girl, Simone’s whole body was shivering but instead, she was shaking much rapidly.

The black mud and dirt that was smeared all over her body kept falling off because of the violent tremors, revealing her pale white skin underneath.

Under the stares of Rod and the rest, as well as Simon’s own attention, something miraculous happened.

It was as if the black mud on Simon’s body melted into a black water-like matter, following the curves of her body and slowly dripped down her body. It stained the of the inner part of her legs and down her heels, slowly flowing down onto the forest grass. Not only was it on her skin, but the dirt on Simone’s clothes all flowed quietly down to the ground, not making a sound.

Just within ten seconds, Simone’s whole body once again turned clean, returning to her usual delicate and pretty frame.

Her small lips were slightly opened, with wide round eyes. It was as if she was afraid to believe what she saw, she did not even dare to blink. She was afraid that if she blinked, everything in front of her would turn into an illusion and disappear.

But the feeling of her dry and cool body kept reminding her that this was not an illusion - This was reality.

"My Lord…" The few Catholics in Rod’s team started praying devotedly. This was absolutely a miracle!

Even Rod himself was stunned, his face wore the expression as if he saw a ghost.

"Damn it! That was not recorded!" He suddenly reacted. The rest also reacted, one after the other. Such a miraculous sight and yet no one recorded it, this was absolutely a huge lost!

Garen looked at reactions of these group of people in a funny way. That move just now would only be used by just upper martial artists who had terrific skills. However, top martial artists could also achieve the same level. Such as the saying "emerge unstained even from the filth", this referred to the realm of top martial artists.

Releasing his hands, Garen walked back to the bonfire heap and started to check through his things. He put on his backpack and checked the remaining amount of his drink.

He was not afraid of being poisoned unless it was a highly concentrated toxic. If not, any others toxins would also help him build up his liver function; it was the same as those who do not consume much alcohol.

Such powerful vitality would show in all ways, not just to the degree of skin defense.

"You failed, I suppose? White Phoenix Base is not a fun place to venture into!" After Simone was shocked, she quickly replied with a cold smile, "There is a twenty-four hours cycle surface surveillance system in the base, and we are not far from there. It will not take them long for them to find out where we are residing at. Then, they would send their elite team, and by that time, you will only be able to flee in panic!"

Simone’s words were distinct with an unforgiving tone, not paying the slightest attention the Rod and his men’s weird expression.

"What kind of people are they?"

She frankly questioned Garen.

"Them? These are some of my friends," Garen answered in a good temper, smiling.

Simone took a few steps to the side of the bonfire, and sat down on his butt, not minding the dirt, "I’m hungry, and I want the eat something. Quickly make me something to eat.

These few days, she had completely lost herself. Since Garen got a hold of her, if you wanted to do anything, he could have already done it. He would not have waited until this moment. So instead of feeling afraid, why not drink and eat well, regulating her own mood.

Garen gave a smile. From his bag, he took out some dried meat, a bottle of pure water and different types of seasoning. First, he lit up the bonfire again, then used a metal can, of which he brought to boil the meat soup. He stood up and took a walk around the surrounding of the forest. After his quick return, there were some extra plant rhizomes and mushroom in his hands; it was frightening looking at the red and green colors on them.

With the same skill, the mud and dirt were immediately shaken off. After rinsing it with water, it was put into the can for boiling.

Rod and his company were looking for some rocks to sit down by the side. After a couple of frightening experiences, they looked very panic-stricken too.

Seeing that Benjamin was busy with preparing his meal, Rod hesitated for a bit.

"Our planes and cars are not far from here. Mr. Garen, why not let’s eat when we return. How does that sound? I have already reserved a room with a feast in the Leonardo Hotel."

They had always taken the main road. With the planes and cars leading the way, they did not even have to walk through this wilderness; they could immediately enter the base. Now, there were a bunch of people, dressed in garments and wore leather shoes, walking on the forest grass. Having huge chunks of mud stuck on the sole of their shoe - Lifting their foot too felt heavy.

"No rush, it will be done soon," Garen smiled as he answered, while he stirred the soup in the can continuously.

As time passed in seconds and minutes, the essence of the soup slowly let out a rich scent. Even Rod, who had a habit of eating good food, could not resist salivating. One by one, his men also felt their saliva stir in their throats. All their attention was quickly captured by that pot of boiling soup in the can.

"In this forest, there are still a lot of things that can replenish your vitality. If we just leave, then it would have been wasted," Garen simply explained.

He then split the soup into a few bowls. The moment the soup was scooped up, she drank without hesitation as she had tried his cooking earlier on. She drank it all in one mouthful. Then very quickly, her eyes looked confused and started drooling from the edge of her mouth, her face revealed a silly smile.

"Hehe… Hehe… Too delicious… It’s too delicious…"

Once she put down her bowl, this girl started dancing and jumping. For a moment, she had seeped into her unconsciousness.

"La~ La la! La! It smells so good… Your body smells so good…" Simone threw herself on him, hugged him and bit him. Her snot and saliva were both dripping, both her eyes in a daze - They completely lost that spirit she had just now.

"Be good… If you listen, I will give you another bowl of soup in a bit."

"Really?"

"Really."

"Alright, I’ll listen. I’ll be good…" Simone acted as if she had completely turned into a child with a few years of IQ. She leaned over on Garen and stopped moving.

Rod, who stood at the side breathed in the delicious scent. At first, he had wanted to drink the bowl of soup. But once he saw this scene, he got the chills for a moment. The look in his eyes changed again and again towards Garen.

After Garen calmed Simone down, he started asking some questions that they still were not clear about.

"Other than this base, does White Phoenix have other bases?"

"They don’t."

"Then do you know where the person in charge of the base, Gremlin went?"

"I don’t know, I just want some soup!" Simone shook her head.

"You just had some. If you do not answer my question seriously, then I will not give it to you," Garen said with a beaming smile.

"Gremlin took Lotus Pearl with her - I don’t know." When Simone mentioned Lotus Pearl’s name, her face revealed an unhappy expression, "Lotus Pearl, that cow! Her smiles are all fake, she thinks I can’t see through it? That slut likes to pee standing up, and she used to be a witch. I saw her in bed with a man, with my own eyes. Then she went and found herself a not-so-secret-boytoy! Haha… Boytoy… She thinks nobody knows, that b*tch!"

Even though Simon was in a situation she was unconscious of, that mean tongue of hers would never go away. Just hearing it gave the group of men cold sweat.

Garen rubbed her brain. Suddenly, Simone gave out a dog-like sound of comfortable hum.

"I apologize. This one here is still of use to me, so I used a slightly special method," Garen quickly smiled at Rob and his men who were frightened by it.

The immense knowledge of subjects he had absorbed from the previous world impacted his high research attainments in hallucinogenic drugs and neuroscience. This soup was made specifically to tackle Simone’s mutation that was stimulated by the Fantasy Fist, and special execution would be directed towards modulating it.

Garen attentively examined Simone’s nerves in her head and found the area that stimulated the Fantasy Fist. Hence, the targeted mixed medicinal soup should continue to stimulate that part of the brain. After some experimentation, he wanted to see if he could once again extract the Invisible Creatures.

He was very curious towards the field of Invisible Creatures. This was an extremely broad spectrum, and it included every creature that the human cannot see; comparing the realms and worlds among them that were far away to a world with light, it would be much, much bigger.

After packing the leftover soup, Garen single-handedly picked Simone up while carrying his backpack.

"Let’s go. Let’s get on your ride for a bit."

"The pleasure is mine!" Rob quickly replied.

Temporarily, he refrained the thought of notifying the higher level authorities. He had to find out the opponent’s ins and outs clearly. Once it had been confirmed...

He also had his own idea; if it was really that hope that the higher authorities had been always looking for, then leaving some free time would also be a golden timing for his prior business relations! If he could hold on to it, then he would be able to keep this friendship for the first time - how precious is that!

A row of people marked the location according to the body device, and very quickly, they found a green helicopter that was parked on an emergency heliport.

The pilot was still smoking beside the plane, but White Phoenix’s airport guards were nowhere to be found. It was obvious that they did not escape. Instead, they must have gone to examine the base of the headquarters.

Seeing that Rod and his men had safely returned, along with them, they brought back two other weird-looking people. One gave out a whine like a dog, and the other was wearing a mask. Looking closely, they only one straight eye. The pilot wanted to immediately say something but was cut off by Rod.

"Leave this place immediately! Go to St. Jeddah City, I want to entertain very important guests!"

"Yes, sir!" The fine training quality the pilot had did not allow him to speak more. They could only obey and hence, he began the procedure of starting the helicopter.

A bunch of people entered the plane, one after the other. As the sound of the huge propeller came on, the green helicopter slowly rose to the sky and sped towards the far distance. It swept through the trees and over the sea, disappearing between the border of forest and sea.

Chapter 671: Corporate 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The space in the plane was huge and it was split into three rows. Rob and his assistant were sat at the front, in the middle were Garen and Simone, and at the back were his subordinates. There were a group of men left that could not fit into the plane. Instead, the rides on the were switched to cars, and they departed from the ground instead.

The pilot was from Lesothy. Once he found out about its particular conditions, he quickly had an expression as if he wanted to stay out of trouble.

Garen sat by the window, overlooking down at the moving trees and sea through the transparent glass window.

Between the trees and sea, of dark green colors mixed with yellow and red, he could see apes and eagles appearing from time to time.

As the plane rose up to a higher level and passed by a white waterfall entrance, Garen’s supervision swept across the border of the waterfall for an instant - Standing there was a young woman supporting herself with crutches.

This woman stood on a piece of empty land, and behind her was a small wooden house. However, the small house and the forest was merged as one. Those without supervision would not be able to tell the difference.

As if she could sense Garen’s stare, the woman raised her head towards the plane and looked at it. Her eyes were unexpectedly light golden in color, making her look very beautiful as it reflected the faint light of the golden sun.

Garen was slightly surprised, but when he wanted to take another look, the plane had already flown past the waterfall. The height of the plane was lowered as they sped towards the huge piece of flatland, river, and forest.

"There were once some nature-loving hermits who lived in this area. The Primary Colors Group had no problems with them. But after that, those who lived here suddenly disappeared, and some abandoned small houses were left behind. Those were the houses you saw just now," Rod turned his head to explain. He could see Garen’s line of sight from the reflective mirror.

"I saw a woman standing in front of a small house by the waterfall just now. Where is she from?" Garen asked.

"Woman? That’s not possible." Rod laughed, "The wooden houses here have been abandoned for many years now. You are talking about the woodland houses I suppose. I have been here a few times and that was what the people of Primary Colors call it. A woman used to live there but she disappeared after. According to rumors, she has been missing for many years now."

Garen frowned.

"I saw it. The woman’s eyes were golden."

Rob looked startled.

"That can’t be, whose eyes are golden? You must have seen wrongly. The reflection of the sunlight would have also caused an illusion."

"Maybe it’s that..." Garen temporarily tossed this small matter to the back of his mind.

He leaned slightly into the leather chair of the back seat and started to pay attention to the Attribute Pane below his field of vision.

‘Garen Thomas.

Strength 7. Agility 7. Vitality 7. Potential 10248%. Soul limit 30.

Seed of soul: The Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique.’

‘Void Hunter: Many ancient civilization inheritors, who were enemies with the Void race for generations, had the ability to capture the core of the void creature and its own powerful talent. That was the power of eternal talent given by ancient mystical strength.’

‘Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Level one entry (Total of 5 Foundation Level, derivative level of 3, full power of 8 levels) Every level’s exercise achievement would clean one’s own blood, gradually growing closer towards Hellfrost Peacock’s physique. The ultimate achievement would be the highest form of Hellfrost Peacock King, the limit being army level.’

‘Seven Star Life’s Secret Point: 4th Level (Total of 7 levels)’

‘Violin Skills: 2nd Grade, proficient level. (Total of 3 grades)’

He realized that his potential points had already increased to the extent of over a hundred points. Evidently, it had come to a point where wearing this mask on his face played an extremely crucial role. However, it was also obvious that it had started to increase slowly now.

This mask almost added him another one hundred potential points or so, which was an optimistic amount of revenue. Although it could not be compared to the total amount of antique he previously owned, this was the second of the Twelve Masks after all. If he could succeed in getting all the remaining masks to be in his possession, then the potential points he would receive could be an extremely impressive amount.

His sight fell into his own Specialization Technique. The Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s real effect was still not exemplified yet. What he was using now was just the original toughness of his physical fitness.

He hesitated for a bit, then his sight fell directly onto the Hellfrost Peacock Technique continuously for three minutes. The icon of the Hellfrost Peacock technique wavered for a while, and immediately after, there was no reaction. The potential point also had no sign of any changes. It was clear that the potential points could not be used to directly strengthen himself.

Regarding the information of this Secret Technique form suddenly appeared. Building the base was one of the effects of level one - spread the seeds all over the body. Whereas level two was where the real practice would start.

Once level two had been achieved, according to his memory of the information on Secret Technique, his Palm Power should contain a type of strange cold toxin. If it was in Totem World, maybe it would have become a more powerful cold toxin that could overcast the surroundings. But in this world, it could only be displayed on the cold toxins of Palm Power.

This was all the Basic Secret Technique every world had, to purely enhance physical quality. Once the Seven Star Life’s Secret Point had been added, it would be enough to achieve the limit - three hundred points of strength degree, but it would still be a huge loss. This was not a simple strength and speed issue. Instead, it was a problem of the control of the Secret Technique. With that kind of knife method, the moment the knife left his hand, the opponent would immediately get hit. Not understanding either the profoundness or using the same level of Secret Technique’s counterbalance would only result in getting beaten up; it would be very hard to reach a point where he could defeat Nadia, the Nine Head Dragon Queen. Yet, this Secret Technique was different. The root of the Secret Technique would come to a certain difficulty that would create various very strong effects towards the body. Who knew, but maybe it could produce a specific type of unique effect.

Garen started focusing his attention on his thoughts about the information of level two.

This was two conditions necessary for achieving level two.

With current technology, arctic lands could be imitated, but white Peacock Stone?

He only knew about the green Peacock Stone. He was unsure of the white one. Maybe this was not the type of Peacock Stone in which he knew?

He passed the question over to Black Sethe.

"Peacock Stone? In white? Why would you want that for?" Black Sethe seemed a bit shocked.

"Of course I need it for practicing the Secret Technique," Garen did not cover it up.

‘Then that would be a bit tricky. If I remember correctly, the Peacock Stone you ask for in the Secret Technique is not like the green stones you understand about. Instead, it is another type where the stones are inside the slime of the peacock’s body,’ Black Sethe explained, ‘Peacock slime is a type of Invisible Creature. A lot of worlds have it, even this world has it. But this, you would have to search for it yourself. I’m helpless in this situation.’

"Alright…" For a moment, Garen put down the Secret Technique’s progress rate. Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s name sounded very intense, but he was not specifically sure how much of an increase it would give, or whether it would help him deal with the Nine Head Dragon, Nadia who was getting more and more pressing.

As he returned to consciousness, the helicopter was slowly landing. Simone, sat on his left, was asleep with saliva dripping onto the black shirt in front of her chest. When dried up, it gave out a horrible smell.

"We’re here, we’re here." Rob hurriedly called out, "Down below, the people from our organization will act as reinforcement. Mr. Garen, you temporarily do not have to worry about Primary Color. Over here, nobody would leak this information."

"Thank you very much," Garen nodded his head. Looking down from the plane, on top of the grey and white round airport below was engraved with a red cross. In the middle of it stood a crowd of people, waiting. They were wearing grey and green military uniform, and a beret. Their postures were upright, in their arms held a black assault machine gun.

Garen took a look at his surroundings. Around the airport was enclosed with high walls, and there were a lot of soldiers with berets patrolling the area. It was as if this was a military base.

The helicopter slowly descended. Rob was the first to get down the plane. He then faced the officer below and gave a salute and they saluted back at him with speed and power. After that, the leader, a soft-spoken black officer muttered a few sentences in his ear. The both of them nodded their heads, indicating that they understood each other.

Only then, Rob quickly turned around to greet Garen.

"Everything has been arranged, Mr. Garen." His had a smile on his face and did not have the slightest fluster or panic of talking to a terrorist, " I understand that you wanted to ask us why we value you. Since we took the initiative wanted to be friends with you, yet we did not discuss White Phoenix or Primary Color. This answer is quite a long story, why not we have a meal and talk at the same time. Is that fine with you?"

"Many thanks for your hospitality," Garen smiled. Such top-level organization like a Rexott Group was also what he needed as a figure for an alliance.

Such large organization would often be so exaggerated that it had the power and strength to make people feel dumbfounded. He too wasn’t crazy. If it wasn’t necessary, who would want to look for trouble and make enemies with these world-class organizations?

If one got to the point where he had enemies all around the world, then that would really be a failure.

But indeed, as Rob said, he was very curious about his counterpart’s intention.

A group of people surrounded Garen and Rob while he introduced the situation here and was headed towards the airport’s dining hall.

The airport was situated outside the city; it was built on a flatland that was opened up from a forest, beside St. Jeddah City. This time, they luxuriously invited some well known international chef from a hotel and had already prepared Garen some scrumptious dishes.

After they sat down facing the steaming table of food in a white dining hall, Garen and Rob just randomly ate a bit, then put down their fork and knife. The taste palate here was very sweet, extremely sweet - mixing the chili and sweet drinks in a dish tasted weird.

Rob noticed this bit, and he revealed a trace of apology.

"My apologies, I have not welcomed you well."

"No worries, let’s talk about proper business. You guys, Rexott Group should have a deep understanding towards the Primary Colors Group right? With this amount of time, you should have found out about my identity and background, right?" Garen spoke frankly and bluntly.

Rob mocked him.

"Of course as you’ve expected, I just received all the information," With a waved of his hand, the servants in the dining room dispersed out the door and left. However, the guards were outside the door.

"You as Nighthawk King, and the conflict between Primary Colors and White Phoenix. Originally, we should not have mingled into this, but…" Rob paused, then carefully gave Garen a side eye.

"Over here, I would like to once again confirm your identity."

"Identity?" Garen raised his eyebrows, feeling that Rob was hinting something.

"You, are you really a pure human being?" Rob asked each word and each sentence seriously.

Garen was surprised. He never thought his counterpart would suddenly ask this sort of question.

"Of course, I am pure human," He answered, without a trace of hesitation.

Rob’s eyes were staring at him, as if debating how reliable that answer was.

"Why would I need to lie to you?" Garen laughed, and stroked Simone’s small brain, "Why don’t you just tell me what is wrong. I still have some other matters to sort out. I can’t stay here for long."

Rob nodded his head, lowered his head to look at his watch on his wrist, as if he finally confirmed something. His expression suddenly turned complicated, yet weird, like he was holding back some excitement to a joyful situation.

"Then I’ll just say it." He appropriately said the words, "To tell the truth, us, the Rexott group have always been researching the topic of human strength limitation. We have always attempted to search for the path of hope of becoming a normal human being. Phrasing it this way, are you able to understand?"

Chapter 672: Corporate 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen put down the bowl in his hand and nodded his head.

"Very clearly; I think I understood your idea."

Rob nodded his head the same way.

"Us, the Rexott Organization have always been at the forefront of the world in this area of research. Regarding the discovery and creation of human potential, we had always looked into it from a combat fight aspect. It had been a long time ago since we started experimenting with practitioners, who set out to find the limits of a human. Unfortunately, we found the human body do have a limit data."

"Oh?" Garen was suddenly interested, "Limit data?"

"Indeed." Rob nodded his head seriously, "The limit data refers to data that we have obtained and gathered of the maximum limit of human quality one can achieve. Power, resilience, and responsiveness - we have split the human quality into three types. Of course, there is a much more delicate division of it, but I won’t say much here. With these three types of data, we got an unbelievable result - human strength does indeed have a limit. That limit is about 460 kilograms, and this refers to a pure power without any impact."

"460 kilograms," Garen understood clearly. The statistics obtained from this data and their own research were exactly the same. He could see that their knowledge and study of this topic was not something that could have been done within a short amount of time.

"Precisely, the data you mentioned is correct. But what does this have to do with you looking for me?"

Rob took in a deep breath, with his eyes staring at Garen.

"I realize that your powers have far exceeded 460 kilograms, where it has reached a horrifyingly unknown level. That is why I had to repeatedly emphasize whether you really are a true human being. Because according to our research, it is impossible for a pure human being to have such great power."

He carefully observed Garen’s expression underneath the mask.

"And based on what I know, Mr. Garen’s numerous had disciples grown rapidly under your supervision. Now, their own strengths have also reached a very high standard."

"That I do not deny." Garen nodded his head, "I created the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist and Shooting Shadow Secret Skill, as you must have heard." When he saw Rob nodding his head as confirmation, he continued, "Since we all know each other’s intentions clearly, then how do you plan to tackle my breakthrough limit?"

Rob lifted up his hand and looked at his watch. After some hesitation, he replied.

"What the authorities mean is that we hope you can hand over the full set of martial arts’ fist materials. In exchange, we will assist you by taking over your revenge on Primary Colors Group. By looking further into your martial arts system, it would be very helpful for us to carry out evolutionary experiments on the improvements of human limitation. This is a huge matter that would help all mankind. I hope you can consider it well."

Once he finished his sentence, his expression did not look good. As he looked at Garen’s facial expression, his heart jumped - he knew it was going to end horribly.

However, he knew that Garen used Two-Faced Waterbird Fist and Shooting Shadow Secret Skill to control the two big organizations, combat club, and Nighthawk. For them to ask him to hand over all of his martial arts' secrets, they would be taking advantage of the situation by stealing his work.

"Two sets of materials on martial arts’ secrets?" Garen never thought the other party would bring this idea up. The Secret Technique was indeed profound, but technology was very powerful too. If he gave them all the information, maybe they might just come up with something new after a while.

"Please don’t be angry!" Rob looked terrible, and he quickly said, "We still want to add some gifts. We heard that you were looking for the Sleepless Faces. Our organization has been preserving the two masks we have used in the experiments. If you agree on the secrets, we can immediately gift the two masks to you with honor. And, we will send over the information on the other masks."

"Sleepless Faces?" It was the first time Garen heard that term.

"You don’t know? That is the ancient name of the mask you’re wearing," Rob explained. Seeing that Garen did not explode, he relaxed.

Garen sighed heavily.

"About the materials on Two-Faced Waterbird Fist and Shooting Shadow Secret Skill, I can give it to you, but these two Secret Techniques contain a distinct property. Without that distinct inheritance, there is no way you can train them yourself. I had to say that first, in case you have regrets in the future."

To be honest, he picked these two Secret Techniques randomly. In his memories, there were numerous Secret Techniques - not ten, but more than hundreds of them. These were just third-rate Secret Techniques. If it wasn’t for him, or his talent skills, even if he wanted to practice independently, he would at least need ten or twenty years of hard training. Still, that was the case for extraordinary appraisals.

Rob’s watch seemed to have the function of sending out whatever Garen had said. After looking at the reply on the screen of his watch, Rob nodded to show he understood.

"The authorities hope to invite you to collaborate in the organization’s higher level experiments to collect some related data. I don’t know…"

"That is not a problem. I also hope that there is a detailed test environment to define my true abilities," Garen said proudly. He had always wanted to test his own qualities, but there weren't enough high-tech experiments. A general test equipment wasn’t even enough for his lighter punches.

"It will be a pleasure working with you!" For a moment, Rob was relieved, "About Primary Colors, we will take over fully on your behalf - Don’t worry. Regarding the circle of nature, we will also sort that out. Your life will not be affected. And, we will also give you a satisfied reply from the White Phoenix."

Garen nodded his head. At least he could now relax slightly since White Phoenix Base had been destroyed.

"I still need to kill the group who murdered my assistant. That should not be a problem I suppose."

Rob sighed.

"That is little difficult, but that shouldn’t be a big problem," The authorities’ plan was obvious. The hatred between Nighthawk King and Primary Colors was deep. Since he chose to side with Nighthawk, then naturally, there would be nothing to talk about with Primary Colors. Moreover, there had always been old grudges between the top levels and Primary Colors, and they took the opportunity this time to erupt. The background characters from each circle would show up to discuss the particular matter.

In fact, White Phoenix was not the only violent party from the Primary Colors’ subordinates; there were more than ten parties, and White Phoenix was the person in charge of this area. Equivalent to a subsidiary, in the face of another world-class monopoly consultation, regional affairs of a subsidiary would not be a big problem.

"Then it will be a pleasure working with you," Garen smiled while nodding his head.

"Pleasure working with you too."

Rob also gave a relaxed smile.

"On the other hand, regarding the Sleepless Faces you mentioned just now…" Garen asked about his doubt he had before.

Rob was slightly distracted.

"I assumed you knew. Sleepless Mask is the legend of the mask you are wearing. Legend has it that the original version of this mask was named as Daylight Mask, such that when people wore it, they gain the ability to never sleep. The wearer would be full of energy without needing any sleep. That way, more time could be taken out to do other things."

He explained.

"You would also know that throughout human life, we spend one-third of the time on sleep. If sleep was completely unnecessary, won’t that be equivalent to having one-third more of a life than compared to others?"

Garen understood and nodded his head.

"Hence in ancient times, when a Duke got the mask, he started a long process of imitating time. He used everything he could make use of and in the end, he had replicated twelve of the exact same mask. Undoubtedly, all the finest pattern carvings were the same. However, the functions could not be compared to the original; there wasn’t even a single bit of extraordinary power in it. Under his own disappointment, he hid the Sleepless Faces in an extremely secretive place, then spread the clues on top of each of the twelve masks before he died. Whoever could find all the Sleepless Faces’ replicas might even have the chance of searching for the original mask," Rob described it in detail.

Only then did Garen understand the essential information of this mask. Generally, it would be impossible for an ordinary organization to know about these things. Only those big organizations that had been through historical changes would have had a chance to record it down. Within that short time frame, Rob must have contacted one of the organization’s top levels through the device to quickly explain the context to him.

Rob was indeed a caring person.

"Don’t you worry, we will help you sort out the issues about the mask and Primary Colors."

Garen nodded. Indeed, facing Primary Colors alone, its top levels would be involved in the background, behind their extraordinary powers and he would be put in a situation where he would have to deal with the Nine Head Dragon King while dealing Primary Colors as well; that would not be an easy thing. If it could be less troublesome and much smoother, it would definitely be better.

As for the Secret Technique, without his Soul Primer, if they do not train hard for ten to twenty years, they should not even have the thought of getting half its result. With that, they would only be able to enter a smaller part of the martial arts world. After that would be the martial artists' world, which would seem like an illusion. Even entering the martial artist levels would be extremely difficult, not to mention the courageous Grandmaster of Combat.

He had to collect all the masks as soon as possible, before the attack of the Nine Head Dragon King. The more potential points he gets, the higher the possibility of him shortening the time to strengthen himself. Now, this was Garen’s real aim.

What he needed most now was time.

"If so, I will quickly jot down the information I have, but a lot of things need more than just a bit of information to completely describe it all."

Garen said softly.

Rob nodded his head.

"As an individual, I believe your sincerity is not fake. That, you can rest assured. I will quickly get the two masks out for you. And the protectors from your hometown will arrive shortly."

"Then I can relax," Garen nodded. Regarding the protection from his hometown, he was not very worried about that.

Grano was made into a gathering place for witches, where even the secret party of Vampires would not dare to kill humans freely, and not to mention a group of elite human killers. As higher level intellectuals, his parents had a broad relationship with the locals. And because of their relationship with the city councilor, they were willing to do a few good things for the locals; their fame wasn’t bad. Hence, in public and in private, the local witches would never allow any outsides attack the local’s public figure, which could trigger panic.

Even more so, his own arrangements should have preventative measures. At first, he arranged for the Arisa Sisters to protect his family. After being chased for many years, they were very happy to sneakily attack unwelcomed strangers.

Hence they predicted that the team sent to Grano by White Phoenix would do more damage than anything. The background circle knew on the inside that most would call for a cease-fire. Nobody was willing to be involved in a war between races.

More so, that was the truth.

Chapter 673: Approach 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Cynthia region, Italy

Gremlin was dressed in a white suit, he got out of the white race car, and looked left and right.

There was a large round plaza behind him, with many black copper statues in it, some children and tourists were milling about, and occasionally there were pigeons rising and falling in the plaza, cooing as they went.

Gremlin glanced back as he rearranged his suit, walking rapidly to a small house in front of him.

Bang bang bang.

He knocked the door directly.

With a clacking sound, the door opened from inside.

"Quick, come in." A middle-aged woman opened the door and talked to him, her skin was dark, and she looked very plain and honest.

"Sorry for disturbing you." Gremlin nodded, and strode inside, passing his car keys to the woman. The woman, on the other hand, went outside to drive the race car into the garage.

The whole building was grey-black, and there were many spots on the walls, indicating its advanced age. It was not that different from a normal citizen’s home.

Gremlin went upstairs within a few strides, the room door on the second floor was open, and he stood at the door as he looked inside, seeing a white-haired old man carefully trimming the bonsai plants that filled the living room to the brim.

The old man wore a long grey-white shirt and matching trousers, his hair was slightly long, tied into a ponytail behind his head.

"How are thing progressing recently? Come in and sit." The old man heard the footsteps, and asked without turning around. His hands were still trimming the bonsais carefully.

Gremlin stood at the door, lowering his head and waist slightly in place of a bow.

"Father, something very bad happened, and I incurred extreme losses." As he spoke about of that, his expression was not particularly great.

The old man nodded, turning around and glancing at him.

"I heard about it as well, your base was done in. Looks like you messed with an important opponent. How do you plan to solve this?"

Gremlin had a script ready since long ago.

"Lotus Pearl alone probably isn’t enough, I hope you can send someone else to support her."

The old man frowned.

"That’s slightly troublesome, you have to know that I’m not the only elder in the group."

"Of course I know that." Gremlin nodded, "But even if you’re not in charge, Mr Titan would surely grant you a favor…"

"I won that favor with my life back in the day." The old man interrupted him. "Now that Rexott has interfered, this is no longer a simple matter and problem of dealing with the Nighthawks."

Gremlin said nothing, staying quiet with his head lowered as he awaited his father’s decision.

The time ticked by, and neither of them spoke, there was only the snipping of the bonsai trimming.

After a long time, the old man finally sighed.

"That person is looking for the twelve masks, the Sleepless Faces, perhaps you can try to tackle it from there. Also, some of the techniques that he has are very useful to the group’s supersoldier plan, you might be able to convince the higher-ups using this." The old man reminded him in a low voice. He turned around to look at Gremlin, "You are my only son, do not disappoint me."

"Yes, Father." Gremlin nodded deeply.

When he heard the old man speak, he already knew that all these reasons were for naught, the true key was that the old man had agreed, this meant that he would support his son in front of the group’s higher-ups, and that was all that mattered.

Walking out of the house, Gremlin took a deep breath, and finally felt his body relax.

The destruction of his base was nothing, it was just some money, if he ran out of money he could just earn more, but if something went wrong with the branch that he was personally in charge of, that would truly be fatal.

Once one reached a position like his, money and all that had become irrelevant, the more important things were position and power.

The Nighthawks were no more than a tiny obstacle in his journey to the top, if he could not even overcome this, then there would be nothing left to say about the problems he would encounter in the future.

Although he comforted himself like that, whenever Gremlin thought about his hundred-billion-dollar investments gone just like that, he still bled inside. Most of the White Phoenix’s funds were in there, if his father weren’t a high-level elder in the group, he would probably have been knocked down due to the incident.

As for the team he lost in Grano, that hurt him even more, those were all the direct subordinates he could mobilize at will, and now he had lost every last one of them.

"Garen of the Nighthawks!!" He repeated that name through clenched teeth in his heart.

　****************

Berlin, Germany

In a very ordinary black building.

Garen caressed the Demonic Book notes in his hand, his expression dead silent as he looked at the Nighthawk higher-ups standing in the room.

Baldy was there, Hera was there, Angel was there as well, and so were some other higher-ups that he was not familiar with but who all had considerable positions, they were all the true core of the Nighthawks. They were also the first batch of elite Nighthawks that Garen had personally taught and raised himself.

"Six left."

Under the bright light of day, Garen looked at the six people in front of him with a sharp gaze.

"Of the twelve I taught in the past, only six remain, standing in front of me now."

He sat on the smooth black wooden chair, his gaze sweeping over the six of them again and again.

"We lost two in the operation before, and now in three short days, Lotus Pearl took out four of you??"

"I made a mistake as the leader." Baldy stepped out and said with his head lowered, his voice muffled.

"The battle with the Primary Colors ends here for now, soon someone will arrive to take over, you guys go down and rest properly, after some time I want to train you personally." Garen waved his hand, lazy to say any more.

"Take over?" Baldy Kaedun exchanged a glance with his wife Hera, and they both saw confusion in each others’ eyes."

"There will be someone in charge of handing Lotus Pearl personally as well, you guys relax, alright, you can back down now." Garen was too lazy to explain it to them, if he did not know perfectly well that he could blame Baldy and the others, with his temper, these people would soon have quite the punishment in store.

Although Baldy and the others were confused, they still retreated out of the room obediently.

Once everyone had left, Garen sat alone in his room, the battle with the Primary Colors had already affected his family, so he needed to settle this as soon as possible, in order to prevent his family from getting hurt further.

After he came back from the White Phoenix’s base, he had passed all the non-essential information regarding the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist to Rod, so that Rod could pass it to his superiors, and in exchange, the Rexott Group had indeed sent their core team of guards, the War God Squad.

Their name was very cliched and lame, but they were indeed a terrifyingly powerful team, as the team sent to take over the battle between the Primary Colors and the Nighthawks wholesale, the War God Squad had terrifying moves and all sorts of talents, most of their members were elites just beneath the special class mercenaries, and their leader was a special class mercenary who had faced Lotus Pearl before, codename Dragon Turtle. Such a team was extremely rare, even within the Primary Colors.

"I’ll leave Lotus Pearl completely to you guys." Garen seemed to be speaking to himself.

"Relax. Since the group gave us this mission, we will be wholly responsible for it." A small and skinny man walked out from behind a vase to the side of the room, he twisted his body eerily, and all the bones in his body actually began to crack, until his height of less than 120cm quickly grew to 150, 160, 170, finally reaching 180cm!

This man was wearing elastic white clothing, his head completely bald and hairless, his skin hair, and green veins visible all over his limbs.

Just now Baldy Kaedun and the others had been in the room for so long, but they never noticed this person at all, his camouflage skills were practically terrifying.

Garen appraised this person carefully, he was Dragon Turtle, and he did seem to be training some method to control his blood qi inside his body. It seemed like this world was not completely void of martial arts after all.

"My main problem is that I can’t find Lotus Pearl, her hiding skills are truly impressive, and that just happens to be not my forte," Garen spoke honestly, his martial power was terrifyingly powerful, but his opponent did not show up at all, hiding in the crowd like a needle in a haystack.

"I fought Lotus Pearl before, back when he was a man." Dragon Turtle licked his lips, "He is indeed powerful, but we Rexott are not something Lotus Pearl can handle on his own. Do not worry."

Garen nodded.

The other person was part of the team sent by the Rexott Group to help, taking over the vengeance between the Nighthawks and the Primary Colors completely. But even so, he still had to make sure that such a big group did not go back on their word, there was also the possibility that the two sides would band together to split up his resources.

"As long as you can find her, I will personally handle everything else."

Vaguely, hints of cruelty emanated from Garen’s body, and Dragon Turtle’s pupils dilated slightly.

******************

A hidden branch, in the Rexott Group

In a fancy, luxurious office that seemed like a hall

A golden ceiling, silver floors, and complicated silver patterns carved everywhere. Several large chandeliers hung all over the hall, creating a regular hexagon.

Under the sparkling white light.

Rod and another blonde man sat opposite each other at a long table underneath the chandelier.

Other than them, there was no one else in the entire huge office.

"Speak, what are you planning by using the one opportunity I gave you to mobilize Dragon Turtle secretly?" The blonde man put down his knife and fork gracefully, picking up the napkin beside him to wipe his mouth, and then looking up at Rod, who was also eating.

"Have you looked at the information I gave you? Big Brother." Rod said straight-facedly, putting down his cutlery as well.

"I’ve seen it, but I don’t understand your solution to it at all." The blonde man nodded, he had beautiful features, and a cold and graceful aura, but what was most special about him was the scent of danger he emitted, like a wild beast. He was one of the few people to make it to the top of the Rexott Group all on his own power, a terrifying character.

"The Nighthawks and the Primary Colors were never at the same level, I don’t need to explain to you which to choose, right? After I stabilize the Nighthawk King, I’ll team up with the Primary Colors and surround him, isn’t it the better choice to split him among us? This will also benefit our relationship with the Primary Colors."

Chapter 674: Approach 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Rod nodded in understanding.

"This is indeed a very good choice. However…" He raised his head and met his brother’s blue-black eyes. "However, after I saw that Nighthawk King with my eyes, I felt something very strange, he rushed into the White Phoenix’s base all by himself, and utterly destroyed the whole place within a dozen or so minutes, even a wall of alloy a dozen centimeters thick could not stop him… But that was not the scariest part, the scariest part is that calm and controlled air of his. It was because of that air that I chose him over the Primary Colors."

The blonde man frowned, "Rod, I always thought you were a logical person."

"Listen to me, Brother." Rod raised his voice, "The relationship between the Primary Colors and ourselves will not improve due to something like the Nighthawks alone, neither will it turn for the worse. The competition between groups cannot be decided so simply, forget the Nighthawks, even the entire White Phoenix is nothing more than an experimental company to the Primary Colors, their losses are just the losses of one faction."

"You are ever so childish." The blonde man looked condescending, "Following your emotions and making a choice on an impulse, do you think you won’t incur losses like that?"

He picked up the glass and sipped some of the dark blue wine gracefully, then he put it back down.

"The Nonia Airport Project, the Brazilian resources negotiation, the Morpheus incident last time. I always have hopes and expectations for you, Rod, but you disappoint me time and again."

Rod’s face instantly flushed red.

"This time is different, I guarantee that!" He immediately remembered Garen’s mysterious figure, as though he was in control of everything. The matters that his older brother mentioned were all his past failures. But this time was truly different, that feeling… that strange feeling…

"That’s enough." The blonde man closed his eyes, "You must understand, I don’t have all the say in the group either, although the resources you sent back this time were considerable, to ask us to officially make enemies of the Primary Colors on that alone… I can tolerate your impulsiveness, but the others will not."

He paused, "Grow up, go and learn something for real, don’t always mix with those trashy parasites." He looked at Rod solemnly, "You are my, Parolan’s brother, remember that. You are not young anymore."

He stood up after saying that, walking away from his seat and towards the door at the side.

"I won’t support you anymore in this matter, consider this a lesson. Failure is not scary, the scary thing is being unable to learn anything from it."

"But Brother…" Rod stood up abruptly.

The man waved his hand, saying nothing more, and quickly vanished down the side door.

Rod’s expression was twisted, but there was still an indomitable spirit in his eyes.

He’s always like this, since they were young, always like this! There was an unknown impulse in his heart, something he could not name.

"Since you won’t support me, I’ll do it myself!"

It was not as though he had only been messing around these past few years, he had also accumulated some foundations and connections of his own, and as Parolan’s younger brother, naturally many people in the group were willing to give him face.

This was not only an acknowledgment of his own opinion, it was also an opportunity for him to truly prove himself in front of his brother!

He hesitated for a moment, and instantly took out his handphone, quickly dialing a number.

"Is that Sally? Get Seasnake out there, the mission on that side is temporarily on hold, and Seal as well, all of them move! Let’s show the Nighthawks we mean it!"

After a pause, "Also, just stop the drilling at the oil plant, and pull out all our funds. Find a seller and sell it off, use the price we estimated before, and do it as soon as possible, a little bit of loss is fine." This was his heaviest investment, resisting the almost physical pain he felt from it, Rod clenched his teeth. If he wanted to settle this matter, he would need a considerable sum in funds. The oil plant plan held all of the funds he had collected over the years, but if he wanted to settle this, and without his brother’s support, he had no choice but to mobilize everything he had.

"But… if we pull back our funds now, we will incur heavy losses. We’ve been doing this for so long, and invested so much money into it, as soon as we get the oil…" There was hesitation on the other side.

"Obey my orders!"

"...Very well."

Without his brother’s support, it would be impossible to get the Sleepless Faces from inside the group without sufficient funds.

Putting down his phone, Rod’s expression held an unprecedented determination.

"I will show you, that I am no longer than useless Rod from before…"

*******************

The setting sun emitted a red glow, like a huge scarlet ball, half of its mass peeking above the horizon.

The top of the rolling stone hills was dyed with a pretty red color, reflected on the surface of the lake beside it. The hills were all bald, covered with stone and soil, not a tree to be seen. There were rolling green fields between the bottom of the mountains and the water, under the shadow of the hills in the sunlight, their original lush green looked slightly dark.

A blonde man dressed completely in white walked in the shadowed fields quietly, he had handsome features and a steady but sharp aura. It was Garen, who had just arrived in Berlin.

He raised his head to look into the distance, there were also fields and mountaintops beyond the lake, and again, the top half of these mountains was dyed red in the twilight.

"Where is this?" He frowned deeply, the fields he was treading underfoot felt wet and damp. Looking down, he saw that he was somehow barefoot, treading on the grass without shoes.

"Black Sethe?" he asked quietly. There was no response.

Walking to the lakeside, he crouched down and scooped up some water with his palm. The water was warm, and he could even see some small fish staring up at him curiously through the water.

"We meet again." A familiar voice suddenly came from behind Garen.

"Nadia!" He stood up abruptly, turning around, and saw that a young girl had appeared on the grassy field without him noticing.

The girl was wearing a familiar mask, one half crying and the other half smiling, her long black hair was silky and smooth, drifting slightly to the left in the wind. She wore a short black skirt like a normal girl, black tights, black shoes, a black top, only her undergarments seemed to show a hint of white.

Her pitch-black attire formed a stark contrast with her shining white skin. Her slender figure seemed even more sleek and pure against that long hair.

But no matter how she looked, that strange male voice allowed Garen to immediately identify her as the Nine-Headed Dragon King Nadia.

"The vector is approaching even more rapidly…" Garen stared at her.

"Very soon, I will be here very soon." Nadia’s voice under the mask grew deeper.

Garen did not reply, this was not the first time the two of them crossed swords, both of them more or less understood the other’s character, there was no need for nonsense.

Garen’s hands abruptly tapped the pressure points on his own chest.

His body expanded as though inflated with air, and glowed slightly with a strange black metallic sheen.

Of the Seven Star Life's Secret Points, he instantly went from the first to the fourth star.

Whoosh!

A current erupted around him, blowing all the grass around him into prostration.

On the other side, Nadia directly whipped out two sharp silver thorns, putting her hands together, the two thorns rapidly expanded and extended, somehow turning into a huge sword, three meters long. The blade and hilt were three meters together, and made her figure, that was less than 170cm, seem even more petite, while making the weapon seem even heavier and larger.

With a whoosh, the blade swept into a large silver circle, pointing at the ground diagonally, and every bit of land or grass that touched the blade seemed to be cut in half with scissors, instantly snapping into two.

The white shadow flashed.

Clang!!!!

Garen gripped the large blade with both hands, his body tilting and turning, moving his hands so that he could grip and overturn the blade, but he instantly felt his hands empty, the blade pulling away.

"Ominous Space Path!" Nadia roared suddenly.

Garen closed his eyes, his arms grabbing abruptly towards the front. He felt a sudden pain in his face and shoulder, but his hands also grabbed Nadia’s shoulders.

The fourth star’s terrifying power grabbed onto his opponent’s shoulder blades so hard they cracked.

"Die!!"

He howled, and put his hands together suddenly.

Bam!!

His palms crashed into each other fiercely, but all he had left in his hands was a black shirt.

Opening his eyes, he saw Nadia wearing her white undergarment, landing lightly on an empty space more than ten meters away with the long sword in her hand.

Garen touched his cheek, there was a tiny scratch there that hurt slightly, but it was also in the midst of healing rapidly. After the fourth star was activated, his recovery power had also reached such a high level.

He moved his hands about a bit. Garen raised his arms straight to shoulder height, countless currents slowly gathering in his hands.

"These past few days, I’ve always been thinking about that martial arts you used back then." He put down his arms, the vapor gathering in his palms, forming two white whirlpools.

"Perhaps I cannot reach the level you spoke of, but I have obtained something as well."

Boom!!

A spray of soil and grass exploded underneath his feet, revealing a huge crater. He seemed to become an after-image, appearing in front of Nadia as though he had teleported there.

"Cloud Dragons!!"

There were several white dragons made of cloud vapor twining around his palms and arms, a terrifying power coursing through Garen’s large body, his palms crashed mercilessly into the huge blade.

The moment when his palms met the blade, an invisible soundwave erupted, and the terrifyingly high-frequency tremors began to rapidly take apart the materials making up the blade in the blink of an eye.

Crack… Boom!

The large blade exploded and broke as Nadia watched on in shock.

Roar!!

The nine white Cloud Dragons on Garen’s arms roared as they rushed at Nadia, these Cloud Dragons were completely white, but strangely their eyes were all pure blue, a blue so pure it seemed to shine from within their bodies.

Half of the blade spun over Nadia’s shoulder, crashing into the mountain behind instantly, and exploded in a mist of red.

The dragon figures quickly rushed at her face and eyes.

"Split!" Nadia abruptly roared into the sky, her loud voice echoed with the terrifying roars of the Nine-Headed Dragon, and nine horrifying dragon shadows appearing behind her. They snaked towards the white Cloud Dragons.

Chapter 675: Mask 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The black and white dragon figures crashed and tangled with each other, forming a large whirlwind of black and white, surrounding the two of them in the center.

Baroom!!!

The area both of them were standing at exploded abruptly, a grey mushroom cloud shooting in the air, the cloud vapor spreading across the ground madly, covering the lake and fields that were previously there.

The ground was shaking and splitting around them, revealing so many terrifying cracks, each pitch-black and seemingly bottomless.

Barroom!!

There was another intense explosion from the center. A white shadow shot out like lightning, crashing hard into the red mountain peak, and after that intense collision, half of the mountain top split off and crashed down loudly, bringing up a cloud of smoke and dust.

Nadia flew out of the dust cloud, a scarlet red flame in her hands, there was a huge golden dragon eye opening slowly in the middle of the flames, ferocious and terrifying.

"Burn!!" she yelled.

The flames in her hand expanded fiercely, forming a cloud of flames that shot up high. Led by the dragon eye, it shot towards Garen at the mountain peak like an arrow.

Roar!!

A tremendous dragon roar rose into the sky, the red clouds of flame extended to several hundred meters and then rapidly condensing, actually trying to form a huge red One-Eyed Dagon.

Just as the dragon’s form was about to solidify, Nadia’s expression froze abruptly.

Her body began to fade, starting with her feet.

"Too bad…" Underneath the mask, her eyes seemed to smile, "I got carried away, and forgot that this is merely a projection."

On the mountain peak, Garen was embedded into the stone, covered in blood. He opened his eyes with difficulty, staring at Nadia in the distance.

The red dragon’s terrifying aura turned into a material power, pressing down hard on his body, rendering him immobile.

"The next time we meet, you will die." Nadia’s voice came from the distance.

Roar!!

The One-Eyed Dragon spanning several hundred meters long in the sky roared at him once, and erupted into a red cloud, dissipating rapidly.

His vision went dark abruptly, and when Garen opened his eyes, he found himself sitting cross-legged in the pitch-black silent room, his body bleeding profusely but soundlessly, tinging the whole room with the smell of blood.

‘You got hurt again.’ Black Sethe instantly noticed something amiss.

"Cough cough…" Garen covered his mouth, abruptly coughing out thick blood. "Just a bit more, hahaha…"

This time, the power of Nadia’s projection was at least above thirty points when fully erupted, even with the Seven Star Life's Secret Point strengthening him, he was still overwhelmingly defeated. That last hit, especially, was completely overpowering, he could not even put up a fight, that heavy pressure made all the blood qi in his body freeze completely, unable to flow.

‘You can still laugh about it…’

Bang bang bang!!

Instantly, there were more eruptions of bloody mists around Garen’s body, this was the terrifying after-effect of activating the fourth star.

He resisted the pain, and quickly added his potential points to his Vitality.

Bang bang!! The blood sprayed everywhere again.

The after-effects and his injuries kept acting up, the wounds all over his body were stuck in the middle of healing and exploding, as his potential points were added to his Vitality one by one.

Garen also quickly took out the Void Nucleus he obtained from before, putting it aside, this thing could help heal him as well.

Black Sethe kept quiet the whole time, watching Garen fight against his injuries silently, until half an hour later, when the explosions on Garen’s body finally stopped.

The silent room was filled with a choking smell of blood, and there was blood all over the floor and walls as well.

‘Nadia grows ever closer, and her powers grow stronger as well, how do you plan to solve this?’ Black Sethe spoke.

"Phew… Do you have a plan?" Garen lay on his back, ignoring the blood on the floor, his entire body exhausted as he panted for breath.

‘Rather than a plan, I might have a way to delay her.’ Black Sethe said quietly, ‘If the experiment proves successful, I might be able to temporarily reduce her approaching speed, this way her projections will not grow so much stronger so quickly either, and you might have time to think about other methods.’

Garen knew that he could not continue like this, Nadia’s power grew stronger with every passing day, and almost every few days, she would challenge him. Such strong battles burned away his potential points, but even more troublesome was how they took up his time and energy, plus he had no idea when she would show up, if she suddenly appeared while he was fighting an enemy…

Garen calmed down.

"Tell me, then, since you’ve already mentioned it, there must be a better way to stall her."

‘Void Creatures are not like us, and Nadia is a classic traitor, so I can’t completely guarantee that this method is correct either, it still requires a little experimenting.’ Black Sethe quickly darted out of Garen’s body, countless wisps of black smoke forming a red-eyed human figure.

‘Recently I discovered an interesting phenomenon, the power left on those masks of yours seems to have so effect on that coin, I’m not sure if it’s a good or bad effect, but after I observed it carefully, I noticed something.’

"What is it?"

‘The Sleepless Face masks seem to have some isolating effect on the vector ability emitted from the coin.’ Black Sethe explained, ‘The Sleepless Faces are mysterious masks that emit a force field so that you don’t need to sleep, and the vector emitted by the coin needs to reach the dark territory that we cannot usually touch, yet this emission will sometimes be twisted and cut off by the effect of the Sleepless Faces.’

Garen checked his wounds this time, his body was grievously injured and together with the after-effects, they took up four potential points to heal, no matter how many potential points he had, he could not waste them just like that. The fights were getting more and more frequent as well, their difficulty rising in tandem.

He liked to fight, but he was not in the habit of seeking death.

"The Sleepless Faces can cut off the coin’s vector emission?" Garen frowned, an item created in this world could affect something of the Nine-Headed Dragon King? He was highly doubtful.

‘Just try and you’ll know.’

Garen took the mask off his face, the coin and Demonic Book were taken out at the same time, and left inside this silent room.

He stood up, walked to the wall furthest inside the room, and lightly pulled out a secret box from the wall, the Dragon Head Coin was inside, his incomplete Demonic Book placed underneath the coin.

‘Try putting the mask on the coin.’ Black Sethe stood beside Garen and advised him.

Garen put the mask in his hand over the coin lightly.

Hiss…

There was a strange sucking noise, but it seemed almost like an illusion. Garen was shocked, even with his hearing ability, he could not tell where the sound was coming from.

All of a sudden, he seemed to see the mask’s mouth move slightly, and then everything went silent.

"This mask…" It was his first time properly appraising the mask he had been using as a potential points provider.

‘This mask must have quite the background, but we don’t need to look too deeply into it, it’s fine as long as it works.’ Black Sethe nodded, ‘Now the coin has been isolated, although I don’t it know how effective it actually is, it must have some effect. You still have another mask as a substitute, right.’

Garen frowned and did not say anything, just staring at the mask carefully as he seemed to think about something.

He turned around, returning to where he had been lying, and picked up a black purple Void Nucleus from the floor. This irregularly-shaped Void Nucleus was only as large as a fist, and looked like an unknown metallic mineral, it had coarse and irregular edges.

Garen took the Void Nucleus back to the mask, and took the mask off the coin again.

Bam!

He crushed the Void Nucleus in his hand, grinding it into a very fine powder, and then he poured it onto a clean patch of the floor, wiping it over the floor evenly.

Then he put the mask onto this mound of powder.

Black Sethe watched his movements, and seemed to understand what he was doing.

After a moment, Garen picked up the mask lightly.

"As I thought!" Garen’s expression lit up in understanding.

Under the influence of the mask, the powder had formed a strange image, although it was just very little of the powder on the top of the mound, with Garen’s eyesight and ability to discern things, he could still clearly see the tiniest changes.

‘This is the effect of the mask.’ Black Sethe saw it too, ‘The Void Nucleus and the coin exist at the same wavelength, they have countless connections and influences with that wavelength, since the mask can affect the powdered Void Nucleus, that means it can also affect the coin.’

‘I can sense that this effect will not be very strong, probably because this mask is only a forgery.’ Black Sethe continued, ‘Then what if you stack two masks? You can try it out.’

Garen nodded.

After more than ten minutes, Garen took the other mask from another secret location, and put both masks over the coin.

An unspeakable sensation immediately wafted from them.

‘Something seems to have changed…’ Garen frowned.

‘Looks like it has some effect.’

"Why don’t we just destroy the coin?" Garen asked something he had been meaning to ask for some time.

‘Destroy it? The material existence is unchanging, it just changes from one form to another, from gathered to scattered. Energy and material are often one and the same, the coin is still now a piece of gathered material used for tracking, but once we destroy it, the shards also have the same tracking effect, they will also be much harder to handle than the whole coin.’

"Can’t we chase it out of this world altogether?" Garen frowned deeply.

‘Unfortunately, we can’t.’ Black Sethe negated that idea. ‘Maybe a good way would be to find more Sleepless Faces.’

With that he turned into black mist and darted back into Garen’s body. When he spoke to Garen as a black figure, he was just controlling a substitute, in truth he never left Garen’s body.

‘More Sleepless Faces should be able to form a decent force field, that would have a certain effect, right now the effect is too weak.’

Garen nodded in understanding.

‘If you want to utterly isolate the vector with the Sleepless Faces, and avoid Nadia’s attacks or her tracking in this world, perhaps you need to find the true original mask of legends.’ Black Sethe went straight to the point.

"The Primal Masks, huh?" Garen understood.

****************

Several days later…

Garen sat in his study, looking at the two black boxes in front of him. Rod was sitting opposite him, looking rather pale and haggard, and quite exhausted.

The morning light shone in beside them, falling at Rod’s feet, reflecting off his black leather boots.

Two subordinates stood guard outside the door, one of them closing the door lightly.

"Here are two Sleepless Faces in exchange, we’re already handling Lotus Pearl’s side, we’ve already more or less figured out where she’s hiding and placed that area under lockdown, do you want to see it for yourself, sir?" Rod said quietly.

Garen picked up a box lightly, opening it and looking at the slightly black mask lying in a bed of black silk inside. He touched it lightly with his finger, feeling a cool air dart into his finger, before he put down this box, satisfied.

He picked up the other box, and opened it using the same steps, touching it with his finger. Suddenly, Garen frowned.

No energy flowed into his fingers.

"What’s the matter?"

Rod frowned as well.

Chapter 676: Mask 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen did not reply, he just picked up the mask and observed it carefully.

"The mask is real, but…" The potential power inside had all been sucked away.

This discovery made Garen’s heart jolt slightly, this meant that someone other than the Black Uniforms knew about the secret of the potential value.

"Nothing, it’s just not quite what I expected." Garen put down the mask, his expression recovering.

"Then all that’s left now are Lotus Pearl and the information about the remaining masks." Rod’s brow relaxed as he said in a soft voice, "According to our latest information, there is also one in Germany, while investigating, our people found out that there used to be a cannibalistic tree, it’s not as tame as the Snake Tree, instead it’s a truly terrifying Cannibal Tree, we had gotten this information from the famous adventurer Kenna, apparently the mask is buried underneath the Cannibal Tree."

"Kenna?" When Garen heard this name, he instantly thought of that adventurer he had released in the end back in Africa, he had let the few of them go since AG asked him to, and settled the incident with killing Levi and obtaining the Stone Clock of Fortune.

He did not know how Kenna’s friend was related to AG, but the matter ended like that.

"You heard of him?" Rod laughed, "Speaking of which, that Kenna is a pretty interesting fella. He seems to be involved in a lot of legends everywhere."

************************

Bam!

A gunshot.

"Run!!"

In a valley in Germany, two men in camouflage were chasing a man and woman relentlessly.

Of the two, the man had short brown hair, his face covered with scratches and scars. The woman was dressed in skin-tight black clothes, her movements agile as she occasionally ran while plastered to the valley’s mountain walls, like a monkey.

"Damned Mole!" The man panted as he cursed.

He was Kenna, after hearing about the Cannibal Tree in Berlin, his old habit acted up again, and he could not help but give chase, unfortunately, he ended up unearthing an extremely large drug manufacturing organization -- Halo.

After stumbling into Halo’s bounds, he discovered a shocking truth, the true Cannibal Tree was being controlled by Halo, other than drugs, they were actually researching an extremely dangerous air pollutant virus, and this virus was based off the Cannibal Tree’s sap.

After he met a woman working undercover there, Cole, the two of them planned to wreak havoc on the base together, but to their surprise, their plans were discovered first, and now the two of them were on the run.

It took at least a day and a night to reach the nearest town from here, they were surrounded by flat forest floors, and there was surveillance everywhere, so it was practically impossible to escape. Hence, the two of them were in such a tight spot. Faced with the powerful drug cartel, they were just normal people with a little combat skill, so they were no match at all.

Bang bang bang!!

Three consecutive shots rang out, and Kenna dodged by the slightest of hairs, rolling onto the ground. He then rolled into a crevice in the mountain wall, after Cole helped him up, they darted into a cave in the wall, and disappeared quickly.

Of their pursuers, Mole, who was in the lead, reloaded his gun, his eyes sweeping the quiet valley like a hawk. These woods looked like a normal forest, and was the left-most part of the valley, there was also a small stream nearby, gurgling away.

He could barely see anyone at all, so he gripped a pendant hanging in front of his chest, and closed his eyes.

After a moment, he opened his eyes abruptly.

"Over there! Let’s go!" He ordered at his subordinate next to him.

The other person followed closely without a word.

Mole was the strongest captain in Halo, he was immensely skilled in tracking, and that was also his foundation to stay relevant in the organization.

The two of them had been chasing Kenna and Cole for half a month now, twisting back and forth, and now they had been led into the valley by those two, playing hide and seek for so long. It was practically an insult to his reputation in the organization.

Kenna and Cole hid in the cave, carefully and quickly spraying a small bottle of custom-made liquid to mask the scent they were emitting.

"Guess we’ve temporarily avoided Mole’s tracking, his tracking is based on the scent particles in the air, since we’re hiding it to this extent, we definitely won’t be found."

The woman Cole said quietly.

The two of them were pressed against each other tightly in the small crevice in the stone wall, and they used a large stone plank to fill up the entrance to the area, this was also a result of Kenna’s being inspired by the Stone Clock of Fortune incident.

The two of them were pressed tightly against each other, Cole’s protruding chest pressed into a seductive shape.

Her face was red as she met Kenna’s eyes unknowingly.

"Who knows how long we have to stay here…" Kenna tried to make small chat, the two of them had supported each other through many life-and-death situations over the past few days.

"Mole will soon send large parties out searching here…" Cole said quietly.

Their breaths were about to touch. Cole could clearly feel Kenna slowly bulging down there, and her face grew even redder.

"There must be a way… as long as we…" Before Kenna could finish, Cole blocked his mouth with hers.

Their tongues touched, madly intertwining.

Their interactions over the past few days had long since bred an admiration for the other in both their hearts, Kenna’s ability to joke even in the face of life and death, and his calm demeanor, as well as Cole’s determination and flexibility in the face of adversity, had both become the most attractive traits in each others’ eyes.

After some tossing and turning, the two of them hugged each other tightly in the cramped space, their clothes falling rapidly, the bra strap snapping outright, as though time was slowing down.

Kenna seemed to have returned to the most unforgettable time in his life, when the love of his life was still alive, he hugged Cole in his arms tightly, and pushed himself in deeply, merging the two into one.

The pants that should have been intense were suppressed in the crevice.

Mmgh!

Cole could not help a groan at that sudden force.

Their sweat mingled together, spreading everywhere together with the smell of that custom-made liquid.

After goodness knew how long. The area in the crevice fell silent again.

The two of them lay together in each others’ embrace.

"I won’t be scared even if I died the very next moment…" Cole said quietly.

After Mole and his boss found out about the Cannibal Tree’s secret, they sent out many elites with special powers, Mole was just one of them, but his body was much stronger than average people’s. It seemed that he had been strengthened by the virus obtained from the Cannibal Tree. This virus was terrifyingly contagious, and all who were infected had to obey the root of it all, the mother. Meanwhile, the one who absorbed and infected the mother, was none other than Mole’s boss, the boss of the entire drug cartel Halo, Allen Hill. And Halo seemed to be related to a very famous international group as well.

"Don’t worry, there must be a way…" I will never let the virus spread! Kenna comforted Cole, his gaze finally turning determined.

Cole’s mission was to investigate the Cannibal Tree’s general location, and to destroy the root of the virus. That was her job as a spy of the international police. It was also her revenge for her older brother’s death at the hands of Halo.

"There’s no way, unless we find the source of the virus, the Cannibal Tree, it doesn’t matter how many samples we destroy."

The two of them had considered many plans, and destroyed many of Halo’s samples of the virus. But they still could not prevent even more samples from being shipped all over the world in anticipation of some dastardly plot.

After they were silent for a long time, Kenna hugged Cole tightly in his arms.

"There’s no choice, looks like we have to go to that person." Kenna said heavily, "To be honest, unless we have no choice, I really don’t want to approach that person."

He recalled his experience last time, with the mysterious AG, the ancient witchcraft, the attack of the strange beasts, and that powerful man who eventually killed the Levi, that leader of the militia, powerful and brutal, dangerous and terrifying.

If it weren’t for the little connection he had with AG, he would have died at that man’s hands long ago.

That man would surely be very interested in the Sleepless Faces… that legendary antique of old.

Kenna decided. Even if he knew it was dangerous to make contact with that person, it was for Cole, he could not just watch her die. If he could stop her revenge, he just had to help her with all he had!

In the incident with the Stone Clock of Fortune, he was chased to the edge of his life by that man, that was practically a nightmarish monster, so scary it made him shake!

Then he thought about the Halo boss, Allen Hill, the monster who had turned himself into something neither man nor ghost.

"We have no other choice now, although I really don’t want to approach that person, now he’s our only hope." Kenna took out his satellite phone, quickly searching up the number he wanted to forget the most.

"Who are you talking about?" Watching Kenna’s movements, Cole frowned slightly. Halo was the most mysterious and strongest organization in Germany, they controlled the number one mercenary group in Germany, and was even more powerful and mysterious than the Bailey Group and the others in second and third place. What other organization could match up to such a power? And one in Germany, no less?

"Don’t worry." Kenna did not elaborate. He just wrote a long and detailed message, explaining everything simply, emphasizing the Cannibal Tree and the Sleepless Faces as the two key terms, and then looking at that number, he pressed ‘send’ hard.

Soon enough, the words ‘Successfully Sent’ appeared.

Kenna eased his breathing, and began to wait quietly.

**********************

The outskirts of Berlin

Inside a study in a mansion

Garen sat beside the table, looking at the screen on his phone, a hint of a smile on his face.

There was a recently received message indicated on his phone, with an unknown sender.

He picked up the phone, and upon reading the contents of the message, his smile deepened.

"Looks like this is a great chance to intervene…"

"Oh?" Rod looked confused.

Garen handed Rod the phone, and within ten minutes, they found out whose number it was sent from.

"The sender is Kenna, it’s his satellite phone." Rod received the information from his subordinate, and said solemnly as he put down the phone.

"Although I don’t know where he got my number, but… regardless of the method, as long as we achieve our goal…" Garen laced his fingers.

"We’ve determined the location, do you want to go there?" Rod raised his head to look at Garen.

"Of course."

Chapter 677: Interference 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Valley in the outskirts, Morraso Province, Germany

Three mountains squeezed together, forming a valley shaped like two sides of a triangle(1), there were neat green forests in the middle, and a small stream twisting down the yellow dirt roads, going through the entire valley.

It was noon, and the clear sound of an engine came from the valley road, a convoy of military green jeeps was neatly driving down the yellow dirt roads.

The white clouds swayed slightly in the wind, the remaining sky was completely blue. The sun shone through everything, such that nothing was hidden.

Garen pulled back his gaze, looking at the driver in front of him.

"There’s still another half hour or so, boss."

The one driving the car was one of the Nighthawks, Lotus Pearl was handed to Rod’s subordinates, Rexott was communicating with the Primary Colors, Lotus Pearl was also testing the waters with Rod’s subordinates, Seasnake and Seal, it would probably be some time before they reached a decision, even if they said they had already gotten Lotus Pearl’s general position.

Garen nodded. Moving his gaze outside the car, he watched as the valley fell back in front of his eyes. He could see grey-brown houses by the roadside, or even farms and fields.

"Tell me about this Allen Hill."

Rod sat next to him, and laughed.

"He’s a friend of mine since young, but we’re not that close, when we were young we had a lot of fun together, but once we grew up, many things changed. We haven’t met for many years as well, I didn’t know how he’d developed, if it weren’t for this investigation, I would not know that he had so much hidden away. To think he’s the boss of Germany’s number one, Halo."

He reminisced.

"I remember he was always a very capable and ambitious guy, he was always smiling, but no one could guess what he was hiding inside. He kept his cards close to his chest."

"How strong is his faction?" Garen went straight to the point.

"The main reason Halo can be number one is that they are themselves a special forces mercenary group. Well, I call it a mercenary group, but it’s actually just three people, Allen Hill himself should be Halo in the flesh, then there’s Mole, and the last one is Su Lanjing." Rod introduced them all.

"The name sounds Asian?"

"That’s right, an Asian immigrant to Germany, there are many like that, you know that." Rod shrugged.

Garen nodded, when Rod came out with him today, he had just brought one person with him, a black woman codenamed Black Date, she looked very efficient.

Garen, on the other hand, brought ten Nighthawks in three cars, ready for anything.

The two of them chatted about the Halo organization’s situation, the driver chipping in occasionally. The car twisted and turned with the road, and finally slowly stopped in front of a large grille gate made of wood.

The large grille gate blocked the road, and there were two men in green standing guard in front of it.

Seeing the cars approach, the two of them walked up to them one after the other, the first one chatted with the driver of the first car, and the other picked up his walkie-talkie, seemingly talking to someone through it.

*************

On the right side of the valley road, there were two inconspicuous figures sprawled on a slanting grassy field by the side of the mountain.

The two of them watched the situation down on the road from a distance, one of them was Kenna and the other Cole, both of them wore simple grass-woven hats. They had a large broken branch covering over their bodies, and each of them held a small telescope.

"They’re here," Kenna said in a soft voice, looking at the convoy below. "I have no idea if it was a right choice or not to lure the Nighthawk King here."

"This might be a new development." Cole comforted him calmly beside him, "If you hadn’t informed the Nighthawk King, then Mole would not have been summoned back so suddenly, and we would not have been able to get away from there so easily."

"Perhaps. But I keep getting the feeling that things will get even worse…" Kenna frowned tightly.

"Just stay back and watch. Find a chance, it would be best if we could break away from the valley barricade, we can’t stay stuck here forever," Cole said softly, this valley seemed normal, but in truth, the whole valley was surrounded by Halo’s people, they searched everywhere, and had many surveillance machines in hidden places, even some of the animals and insects here had been tampered with, so it was not easy to get out.

The two of them lay on the grassy slope, watching as the people from the Halo base behind the gate invited the green jeep convoy inside.

A blonde man with a crew cut walked out, laughing loudly, and hugged a man who had gotten out of the convoy tightly. The two of them seemed to be close, chatting about something.

"Shit… They actually have people who are close with Allen Hill!" Kenna’s expression changed drastically.

"Don’t panic… It’s not as bad as you think." But Cole noticed a tiny clue.

************

"Hahaha!! Rod Crusoe! How many years has it been?" The blonde crew cut laughed as he enveloped Rod in a bear hug.

"It’s probably been four years, what a long time. I think the last time I saw you was in Chicago." Rod laughed as well. There was a large contrast between their sizes, he was 170cm, more than 130kg, compared to the other person, he was a bean sprout.

The blonde crew cut was about two meters tall, looking at his powerful muscles, his shoulders considerably wider than Rod’s, he should be at least 170 or 180 kg.

"Now that you’ve come to my turf this time, I must greet you well, why don’t you introduce us? This is?" Allen Hill turned around, his gaze sweeping across Garen who was behind Rod, just a light glance, and his gaze froze, focused on Garen’s body that was about the same size as him. As for the other person’s strange mask, he narrowed his eyes slightly, but did not ask anything.

"This is Garen, Garen Thomas, my friend." Rod hurriedly smiled as he patted Garen’s shoulder while he introduced him. "He came over this time to see what the famous Halo organization is like."

"Mn, you mentioned that over the phone, relax! I’ve got everything arranged. Rod’s friend is my, Allen Hill’s friend." Allen Hill thumped his chest and laughed loudly, he was just wearing a white open-chested shirt, white long trousers, and leather boots, looking nothing like a person who spent most of their time in the valley. He looked more like a normal tycoon on vacation in a seaside city.

"Then I’ll be troubling you." Garen nodded and smiled.

Every few steps they took, there were people from Halo standing neatly in two rows beside the road. There was one person in charge of leading Garen’s and Rod’s subordinate aside to rest, while the three leaders went through another large door, walking straight into a forest path on the left of the road.

The path was covered with white pebbles, it looked especially delicate and fresh, twining through the woods and stretching inwards.

Rod and Allen Hill walked ahead, talking about their childhood memories, while Garen stayed back purposely to watch the surroundings.

There were inconspicuous bird nests, bee hives, between the tree branches, in the grass, or even the armadillo that flashed past. He could sense tiny man-made surveillance equipment on all these plants and animals.

Garen’s eyesight was outstanding, through the mask, his eyes could clearly see the traces of these surveillance equipment.

The three of them went through the woods, reaching a white mansion built deep inside the woods.

The black metal door opened automatically, guards came from either side to check some unknown equipment, and then they saw a black statue facing the back of the door turn slightly. It was a statue of a young girl holding a water vase, the vase’s mouth faced the three of them from the side, and a red light lit up inside before extinguishing immediately.

The three of them walked past the metal door, lush blooming gardens on either side, the green vines and the red and white flowers fighting for attention, dense and beautiful.

Walking through the beautiful twisting garden, and to the end of the pebbled road, what appeared before the three was a white castle-like estate with a pyramidal roof.

Two pretty women dressed as maids opened the door respectfully, bowing.

"Welcome, Mr Rod, Mr Garen."

The crisp voices showed that these two were no older than 25. Their maid uniforms were obviously altered, it looked as though there was just a simple piece of black and white cloth covering their upper bodies, while their lower halves were barely concealed by a little bit of skirt, extremely revealing.

"Welcome to my kingdom, hahahaha!" Allen Hill laughed confidently, "Don’t think this is a simple estate, the truth is there’s something deeper to it." He stretched out his finger mysteriously and pointed downwards.

"Underground?" Rod cocked an eyebrow.

"Exactly!" Allen Hill nodded with a smile, "I have the newest hallucinogenic powders here, do you want to try some? I guarantee it’s pure. It’s not like the stuff on market." This was a drug processing company anyway, he had plenty of that stuff.

The three of them walked into the estate, sitting in the luxurious golden hall, beautiful near-naked maids offered them fruits, cakes, and drinks. And then they left under Rod’s reluctant gaze.

"They’re all top quality…" Rod licked his lips.

"Hehe, they’re a hundred percent obedient, if you like them, I have a pair of jewels here as well! Twins, they’re extremely rare in this world, the sisters have a certain degree of telepathy, satisfaction guaranteed!" Allen Hill introduced in a low but confident voice.

"Oh?" Rod’s eyes shone, that was his favorite type, but since Garen was here on business, he resisted the urge to immediately enjoy himself right now.

"Let’s settle business first." He gulped, picked up a drink and finished in one swallow.

"Business?" Allen Hill stopped smiling, waving his hand and indicating that he was all ears.

"My friend Garen wants a tour of your base, he’s an extremely passionate collector, and is highly interested in the legendary Sleepless Faces." Putting down his drink, Rod briefly introduced their reason for coming here.

"Sleepless Faces? You mean that thing…" A hint of understanding flashed through Allen Hill’s eyes, "But I don’t have much to do with that thing here. If you want the best drugs, you’ve come to the right place. If you need the world’s best beauties, come here, and I can also satisfy your desires. But if you want that thing, there’s nothing I can do." He splayed his hands, shrugging, "Sorry I can’t be of more help to you."

Translator’s notes:

Lit. shaped like the word 人

Chapter 678: Interference 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Alright alright. We're all friends so we don't need to hide things from each other. Rexott, I have my own intel and network. I‘ve already heard of some of the research you're talking about," Rod confessed, "The mask is buried under the roots. You can send your people to pick it up and as an exchange, everything is negotiable."

The smile on Allen Hill's face slipped away.

"Frankly speaking, I didn't discover the mask there. That much is the truth. As to where I obtained the rumors regarding the mask underneath the tree? Such a rumor is very suspicious. Rod, we're all old friends. You know that I've never lied to my friends and would help you all to the best of my capabilities! However, I'm really helpless on this issue."

The atmosphere in the living room became stale.

Rod quickly smiled to ease the mood.

"Since you insist that it isn't there. I'll believe you. Perhaps there's some sort of misunderstanding in the rumor."

"That's more like it," Allen smiled once more, "I'll bring you guys to visit my latest water processing line later. It's definitely one of the best in the world! All of you can buy it directly from me and I'll sell you at a loss! Since we're all…"

"The only reason I came here is for the mask," a deep voice suddenly interrupted their conversation.

It was Garen.

He who had not spoken at all from the very beginning had ruined Allen Hill's moment as he stared pointedly at Allen Hill through the mask.

Allen's smile froze and Rod's smile looked very awkward as well.

"I've told you that I don't have any mask here. Where did you obtain such a rumor?" Allen frowned as he stared at Garen, trying to see the face under the mask.

"Where I heard it doesn't matter. What matters is you need to hand over the mask to me. I can owe you a favor," Garen said softly. Although his voice was soft, it gave off an oppression so strong that everyone felt it was very forceful.

"I've said that there's no mask here. Do you understand human language?" Allen Hill's face turned sour without any hesitation.

"Calm down calm down!!" Rod immediately tried to calm both of them down, "We're all allies here so there's no need to make the situation worse."

"Since Rod is here, I'll do him a favor and give you another chance," Garen's gaze turned cold, "Hand over the mask."

"Or else what?" Allen Hill stood up as he casually ripped off his shirt, revealing his muscles. He pushed Rod away. "How dare you threaten me under my territory?"

"Give me some face. Calm down!!" Rod finally shouted, "We're all allies! Can't we sit down and settle this nicely?"

Allen Hill started to laugh coldly as he ignored Rod's yelling. He walked directly to and stood in front of Garen and prodded Garen's nose with his finger.

"Out of respect to Rod, you! Get the fuck out! Now! I will overlook anything that made me unhappy a few moments ago."

Garen stood up and both of them stared at each other in the eyes. Garen's height was similar to Allen Hill's.

Boom!!

Suddenly a thunder-like explosion roared.

Allen Hill, who had been standing in front of Garen, was sent flying out like a cannonball. His body crashed onto the villa's left wall and was stuck in it with his limbs spread wide.

Ahh!!

As the female servant screamed, Rod's jaw dropped as he didn't know how to react at all. As he was about to walked up to them and stopped them from quarreling, Garen's right hand moved at lightning speed and gave him a good punch. His right hand was like a sledgehammer as it descended on Allen Hill's body. That instant explosion made him shiver from head to toe and his ears were still buzzing from the explosion even now.

Ugh…

Allen Hill moaned as he held his head and climbed down from the wall. He wasn't injured from the attack at all.

However, the moment he stabilized himself, he was then picked up by Garen by the head and slammed into the wall once more.

Boom!!

A hole was punched through the villa's wall, revealing the sunlight from the outside.

"Kill him!!" Allen Hill shouted as he struggled. He was trying his best to get away from Garen's grasp but to no avail. His modified strength was no match for Garen.

"Kill him!!! Su Lanjing!!" He screamed.

He was then held up in the sky by Garen.

Boom.

A faint gunshot was heard.

Garen turned around as his hand that which was holding Allen Hill up was shot with a dark red bullet, which seemed to be glowing red.

Suddenly, a sparked flashed and the black bullet exploded.

Garen didn't react to the explosion as he carried Allen Hill towards where the shots were fired.

The micro explosions from the bullets were completely ineffective against him.

Although Rod had seen Garen's horrifying side against White Phoenix, he still couldn't believe his eyes when he saw it again.

Allen Hill started to squirm in Garen's grasp like an eel and landed softly on the floor.

As he stood up firmly, he glared at Garen. His right hand expanded and the layer of skin strangely peeled off, transforming his right hand into a black squid-like tentacle. The tentacle was a few meters long and was as agile as a whip as it came after Garen.

The sticky fluid that came off from the tentacle dripped onto the floor. White smoke started to appear and a rotten smell started to spread around the room.

Clap!

Garen grabbed hold of the tentacle with one hand and pulled it with all his might as he slammed Allen Hill onto the ground like a heavyweight.

Boom!!!

The floor was pierced through and a crater was formed in the cement floor as rubble flew everywhere.

"Have mercy!! Have mercy!!!" Allen Hill begged with a rather intelligible tone. A huge amount of red and white fluids were flowing out from his body. Some of them even splattered the wall, rotting into it holes of different sizes.

Garen stopped his action and threw Allen Hill to one corner like a ragged cloth.

This guy had undergone through some biosurgery and turned himself into something inhuman. However, his strength was hovering somewhere around two points, which equaled to about one ton of force. What made him terrifying was the sticky fluid with a strong rotting capability.

Even Garen, who had seven points of Vitality, felt his hand was on fire when he grabbed hold of the tentacle. It was as if there were countless small worms burrowing into his skin and it was very uncomfortable.

He casually wiped off the fluid on his hand. He then noticed that the door of the villa had been breached as a swarm of mechanical weapons aimed at him. There even were sniper rifles' red dots covering his entire body.

"Consider it once more. I'm not interested in your research. Hand over the mask and I'll let this off out of respect for Rod," Garen stared at Allen Hill who was trying to get up.

His control was very good as the fluid didn't hit anyone in the vicinity. Instead, only the furniture and sofa was stained.

Cough cough cough….

Allen Hill was coughing badly as his eyes were filled with blood. As his head had been hit severely, his skin had ripped apart, revealing his white skull. White fluids kept flowing out from the side of his lips, which seemed to be a fluid with stronger corrosion.

"We'll stop here for the day."

Garen was lazy to search for the mask himself, hence he looked at Rod.

The latter was filled with hopelessness. Originally, he planned to deal it out peacefully and wished to discuss with Garen in hope that he had full authority in this matter. He didn't expect the situation would turn out like this.

"Let's go," Garen patted his hands. His shirt was completely clean as if he didn't fight someone at all. His black suit was in perfect condition.

On the other hand, Allen Hill's white jeans were ragged and smeared with dirt.

Two of them walked out of the door.

A black woman appeared behind Rod out of nowhere. She stared at Garen, then Allen who was on the floor before she followed behind Rod without a word.

The gunners who were by the door aimed anxiously at Garen, Rod and the woman. Some of them were so nervous that they gulped, fingers stiff and trembling.

Allen Hill who was on the ground secretly opened his mouth as he aimed at Garen's back. Inside his mouth was a rolled green tongue similar to that of a frog as he glared at Garen sinisterly.

Pew!!

A faint shockwave was directed at Garen's back.

Roar!!

Garen turned his head as the dragon's shadow flashed, creating a shockwave around him. It was as if the roar of a monster had pushed the dark green tongue behind him away from his back and diverted it to the oil painting on the wall.

Garen scoffed as he stared at Allen Hill who was on the ground. He then walked out of the main door while Rod and the woman followed tightly from behind.

The gunners who were by the door were terrified by the roar. Their legs gave in as they trembled on the ground.

As Allen Hill stared at Garen's back, he tried to hold himself up but to no avail as his legs were trembling very hard despite his attempts to regain control of them.

He was trying his best to suppress the fear in him but the fear instilled by the roar kept reappearing in his mind.

"Damn it!" he slammed the ground as he fell to the ground once more.

Two people came down from the second floor of the villa.

One of them was Mole while the other was a female. Both of them were in white shirts and their expressions were horrified.

"My custom made bullets can't even pierce through his skin…" the lady seemed to be in her thirties. She had average facial figures and slightly yellow skin. She was obviously from the East.

"I admit defeat…" Allen Hill moaned painfully, "Nighthawk King…" He was trying so hard to suppress the fear in his heart that he didn't realize his voice was trembling.

"Are we just going to hand it over to him just like that? The mask has completely fused with the roots. We can't take it out without damaging it!" Mole walked over to hold up Allen with a pale face.

"Give it to him! I don't want to see him anymore! He's the definition of crazy....!" Allen Hill didn't realize that deep in his heart, he was so traumatized that he couldn't win Garen at all. That man's strength was like an inflating balloon, which kept getting bigger and bigger. The more he thought about it, the more he didn't want to get himself into it.

Unconsciously, the seed of fear had been planted deep into his soul by Garen.

Chapter 679: Increment 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On the journey back, the sound of the car engine would grumble into the car through the half-open window, allowing cool air to flow into the car.

Garen sat in the back of the car together with Rod without any bodyguards. Rod knew that the safest place to be was beside Garen.

"Frankly speaking, we don't have to make such a scene. He would've accepted our proposal if I'd spoken nicely to him," Rod smiled wryly.

Garen glanced at him and laughed.

"I represent the combat club and the Nighthawks. More importantly, I am representing myself as a powerful individual while you're representing Rexott. No matter if it's you or me, both of us are stronger and have a larger background than him. Do you think he would fight back? He wouldn't even dare to speak up."

"No matter how you look at it, he was once my best friend…" Rod sighed. This was the first time he'd seen Garen's prowess close-up. As a commoner and a man, he was very eager to obtain such an overwhelming strength as well.

"Oh right. Garen, I heard that you are trying to take in the second batch of disciples. I was wondering if you could take me in?" he looked eagerly at Garen, "Your martial art, I was wondering if I could learn it?"

"Of course," Garen relaxed and smiled, "I invented two major sects, which are the Two-Faced Water Bird Fist and Shooting Shadow Secret Technique. You're free to choose either one of them. Didn't I give you a set of information last time?"

"I've studied it for a long time but I still don't get it?" Rod lowered his head in shame, "There are a lot of aspects that I managed to scratch the surface of."

"Coincidentally there's a training meeting soon, you can join us. The two major sects that I've created will require my guidance before you can enter the elementary level. No one can just learn it that easily," Garen nodded.

After interacting with Rod for several days, Garen had a few vague impressions of what kind of person he was.

This guy didn't seem to have any common sense and would act based on his feelings. As a decision maker, he frequently made the wrong decision and the consequences were sometimes dire. Furthermore, Rod didn't have any shrewdness. Simply put in a rather blunt way, he was not ambitious, had no clear objective and would change his mind when he felt like it. It would be impossible for him to achieve something big.

However, the good part was that he treated everyone sincerely and didn't have any hidden intentions.

That was the reason Garen was willing to interact with him. No one would like having a friend who had hidden agendas all day long.

"That's great! Don't worry! I may be bad at everything but I'm very confident in my will!" Rod thumped his chest in affirmation of his confident words.

"I hope so…" Garen shook his head.

"What's with that gaze!?" Rod was unhappy.

***************

At a slope by the hill, Kenna and Cole looked at each other as they watched the team of cars and the Halo Base below preparing to go to war. They felt that they'd miscalculated their plan.

"Perhaps the Halo are frightened?!" Kenna couldn't help but speak out.

Cole smiled wryly.

"It's not that… They're frightened of being attacked once more… Didn't you hear the alarm earlier?"

"That owner is the one that will attack if things don't go his way.." Kenna nodded, "What should we do now? The cannibal tree research will be destroyed…"

"It's not that simple. Don't worry about it." Kenna shook his head, "The mask and the Cannibal Tree have fused together as one. In addition to that, based on my initial hypothesis, the Cannibal Tree is using the mask as its core. If one were to remove the mask, it would definitely kill the Cannibal Tree. Allen Hill will not give up this easily, as this is equivalent to taking away his life!"

"Does this mean they will eventually fight?"

"Definitely," Cole nodded in confidence, "I fear that Halo hasn't realized what actually happened. If they were to realize it, they might really fight to the death with the Nighthawks."

"I think we should update the Nighthawks as soon as possible," Kenna inhaled deeply.

"There's no need for that," Cole shook his head, "It's best to let Nighthawks suffer some losses. Once both parties have been weakened, we will have the chance to rise above them!" She smiled shrewdly.

Kenna knew that she had remembered her brother who had been killed by Halo. He reached out his hand and gently hugged her.

"We shall do as you wish. We will wait and see."

"Yeah."

************

Evening hour.

Garen was sitting quietly inside the secret chamber. The blood stains in the room had already been cleaned up by a specialized mute female servant.

He closed his eyes tightly as his body emitted a blue aura invisible to mortals. This aura spread throughout every inch of the room as it suppressed the black aura emitted from the walls.

As a commoner who had trained himself to this level, even if he had the help of his ability, he didn't know how many life and death situations he'd been through. One could say that he was very lucky to be able to reach this state.

It was technically similar to the Nine Head Dragon Queen Nadia. However, her experience was much worse than his.

Garen closed his eyes tightly but he still could feel the token inside the wall before him releasing a faint aura. That aura was weak but tough, like a small stream in a field which flowed steadily without any hint of drying up.

"This is through suppression with the help of the mask. The coin's aura becomes stronger when Nadia is near," Garen muttered.

He opened his eyes, stood up and walked slowly to the other end of the room. He reached his hand out to the usual place on the wall to pull out a small box, where the coin and Magic Code Notebook were hidden.

Furthermore, three additional Sleepless Face Masks were stacked together on top of the coin. With the superposition of the magnetic waves of three masks, the changes became more and more obvious.

He took the two newly obtained masks, closed his eyes and nibbled the corner of the masks.

Two huge amounts of cooling aura immediately flowed out of the mask, as if a flash flood had occurred.

Glancing at the attribute pane in his vision, his potential points were skyrocketing.

It took some time to completely absorb the aura within the mask.

After absorbing the two masks which he’d obtained from Rod, his potential points had skyrocketed from one hundred plus points to three hundred plus points. Although only one of the masks contained potential points, it was able to give him two hundred plus potential value.

Garen dropped the mask back on the table and turned to at his Attribute Pane.

Garen Thomas.

Strength 7. Agility 7. Vitality 7. Intelligence 7. Potential 36248%. Soul Limit 30.

Soul Seed: Northern Trident Frost Fire True Water Evil Technique.

‘Void Hunter: Grade 1.'

‘Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Grade one elementary level (Total of five grades, with three grades of derivative grades, a total of eight grades) ‘

‘Seven Star Life's Secret Point: fourth grade (maximum of seven grades).'

‘Violin Skill: Grade 2, Proficient Grade (Total of three grades).'

The real core that he had been mastering had turned into Seven Star Life's Secret Point and Hellfrost Peacock Technique.

The Hellfrost Peacock Technique required something called White Peacock Stone and he didn't know where to obtain it. On the other hand, he wasn't so worried about the Seven Star Life's Secret Point as all he needed was enough life force and regeneration.

After pondering for a while, Garen realized that the current limit of his Seven Star Life's Secret Point was the fourth star. The fifth star wasn't something he could activate just yet as his body would explode before he could attack. This wasn't the flaw of his technique but the limits of his body.

The theory behind the Seven Star Life's Secret Point was to excite the acupoints of the body temporarily. This allowed a sudden outburst of the potential locked within. It was supposed to be a double-edged sword but for Garen, who possessed extraordinary regeneration and Vitality, he was able to use it consistently.

The other secret methods were no match for this one as it could be superimposed onto Secret Techniques, bringing out his true strength.

However, this secret method had its limit.

When Garen was devising this secret method, it was based on multiple Secret Technique sources and self-discovery. He found out there were nine major acupoints, seven major light acupoints, and two major hidden acupoints. While these acupoints had a trending line, each and every one of them had a limit, which was the body's genetic limitation.

For example, a typical human's genetic limitation was 460kg of strength. Without the Seven Star Life's Secret Point, he could exert about 100kg of force and with it, the maximum he could raise it to was 460kg. In the future, no matter how much stars he could open with the Seven Star Life's Secret Point, he could never exceed this limit. If he were to exceed it, his genes would instantly collapse and his body would implode as it simply wasn't strong enough to sustain such a force.

The Seven Star Life's Secret Point was Garen's accumulation as a martial adept. This horrifying secret method was able to release the limit of a human's latent ability temporarily, giving off an incredible amount of inner pressure. This inner pressure could then be released to increase his body's physical attribute.

Analogically, it was similar to a fully expanded balloon with a hole that slowly released the pressure of the balloon. With every activation, there would be an additional hall which increased the expenditure of his potential points, in return for an incredible increment of his physical attribute.

However, the condition was that he couldn't exceed the total amount of potential points he had stored, which was the genetic limitation. There wouldn't be a second time if it wasn't enough for the first time.

Hence, to the others, this secret method was a technique that should be used when one wished to perish together with the opponent.

Garen was able to create this Masterpiece Demon Technique from the Secret Techniques that utilized the concept of perishing together with the opponent.

"I currently have three hundred plus potential points. It's best to prioritize Seven Star Life's Secret Point and increase my strength and vitality first. This way, my genetic attribute will increase and I'll be able to reach the genetic limitation of thirty points by activating the second star or third star. I don't have to worry about any side effects from going overboard too. If I were to activate the fourth star, even if I were to win by a slight margin at the end, I may be weakened before I am able to kill off the enemy. This may allow the enemy to kill me instead. As my Vitality increases, the number of stars I can activate increase as well. Although I may not be able to exceed the thirty points limit, I at least can hold out longer."

After some consideration, he focused his gaze on Vitality.

Vitality had always been used for regeneration. As Garen continuously added in potential points into it, he was lacking a bit more to achieve eight points. While these minor changes didn't show up in the Attribute Pane, the changes made with his ability were directly applied to Garen's body needs. It would appear when he wanted it to appear and the current leap was from a single digit to double digits. With this increment, it was natural that the small changes wouldn't show.

Chapter 680: Increment 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As the attribute points surpassed five points, every increment would require twenty potential points. All of his attribute points were currently at seven points.

Garen focused his gaze on Vitality.

Instantaneously, his Vitality had jumped up to 8 points and his potential points had dropped from 362 to 354.

"Continue," Garen continued staring at the Vitality pane.

After surpassing eight points, there would be a new change where every attribute point would require 60 potential points. In the Totem World, he'd relied on multiple massacres to obtain a huge increment. Now that he had arrived at this point the second time, Garen felt the same pain as he saw his potential points draining at a great speed.

Immediately, the potential points dropped down from 354 to 294 as his Vitality increased from 8 points to 9 points.

He tried to sense the condition of his body and he realized that he shouldn't have any problem activating the fourth star. His body had greatly improved after increasing two points of Vitality. He previously could only maintain the fourth star for ten minutes or so. Now, he felt that he would be fine even if it was for half an hour. He even felt that he had reached the requirement to activate the fifth star. With his current attribute, if he were to activate the fifth star, he would reach the genetic limits of thirty points, which was about the same strength of Nadia who appeared last time.

"The fifth star that will push me to the genetic limit…" Garen muttered as he quickly pressed onto the acupoint on his chest with his right hand.

Tap tap tap!!

His body started to expand rapidly after multiple clear taps from the afterimages of his fingers.

His skin immediately turned black as his veins crawled all over his bodies like small snakes, including his face. His muscles which had already covered his entire body was now even more obvious.

"This is the fourth star… It's much less suffering," Garen moved his body and noticed no discomfort.

"Let's continue."

Slap!!

Afterimages of his fingers appeared once more as he instantly tapped multiple points at his abdomen and shoulders.

"Fifth star!!"

Hah!!

Boom!!

With a deep buzz, he could no longer hold in his aura as the air started to disperse from his skin. The whole secret chamber was filled with mist. A wind blew strongly and even whistled loudly.

It was a horrifying scene.

Garen's muscles at the shoulders condensed and expanded into two huge muscle hooks. It was as if there were two additional hands on his shoulder facing outwards, that looked like two huge solid pauldrons.

The black veins and muscles tore his shirt apart. The shirt was ripped into pieces as it landed on the ground.

He heaved a long sigh as he stretched out his right hand. The skin by his palm was purple and his veins were the width of tree branches as they thrummed along with his heartbeat.

"This is the fifth star… My current strongest limit…" Garen exhaled once again.

In this state, if he were to slightly contract his muscle, he could move the muscle which was at the size of a human head. The whole room could hear his heartbeat roaring and his breathing was endless as he pulled oxygen into his lungs and expelled out the air.

He took a step back and accidentally brushed the wall with his hand.

With the slight touch, sparks were ‘gently' created as if there were two solid metals creating friction against each other while leaving behind a clear dent.

At this level, he was much stronger than he was in the Secret Technique world by multiple times.

"I can only last five minutes…"

He exhaled as his qi and blood reduced in speed. His body shrunk back to its normal state as well.

‘Your secret method…. hurts yourself first before hurting others,' Black Sethe gave his honest opinion, ‘I've watched countless similar kinds kill themselves from above. It's a technique similar to that of devils which hurt themselves.'

Garen didn't say a word as he looked at his Vitality.

Five minutes in his extreme state wasn't exactly safe enough for him. He wasn't sure if he could defeat Nadia in such a short time to ensure his survivability.

With determination, he focused his gaze on Vitality again.

His Vitality, which was already nine points, jumped once more and entered ten points!

Sixty points of Potential points were reduced once more, reducing from 294 to 234.

"With this much of Vitality, I may be holding myself in the fifth star, which is equivalent to all attributes to reach the thirty points genetic limitation. Compared to adding other attribute points, this is much worth it in the short term."

Garen calculated the number of gains and losses he obtained and was rather satisfied with it.

‘This secret method of yours allow you to reach the genetic limitation for a short amount of time. Perhaps you are able to withstand Nadia's attack for now, but if you don't completely seal her marking aura, she will become stronger and stronger. Nadia's upper limit isn't some strength you've encountered last time,' Black Sethe reminded him, ‘The strength of an Army Level isn't something you can imagine.'

"I understand," Garen responded, "At my current level, the Seven Star Life's Secret Point is sufficient. It would be impossible to go beyond the genetic limitation with such a short amount of time. I need to find other ways."

‘This secret method of yours… Only you are able to use it… It would require you to use up your body's potential once you've reached the third star, which happens to be your body's lifespan. I don't know what method you're using to replenish your body's potential, but this technique definitely cannot be used by others. Mastering the Secret Technique is the better way. No matter how strong your body is, you are not able to balance the nature of the universe. The true purpose of pursuing Secret Technique is to move the universe with your body, not just for self-enhancement. You have to know that you're currently temporarily…'

Before he finished his sentence, clang!!

Suddenly, a huge screech of metal clashing together was heard. The Secret Chamber's wall had been hit by something.

Garen could only feel that his ears were ringing. The space around him started to tremble and a white light appeared in front of his eyes instantaneously. It was so bright that even he couldn't see anything in front of him clearly.

A familiar aura charging towards him at high speed.

Clang!!!

Among the ringing metal collision sound.

A terrifyingly huge aura came at him!

"Die!!"

"Nadia!!"

Without much time to thin, Garen pressed onto the acupoints with both of his hands, activating the fifth star.

Hah!!

The aura spread everywhere wildly as he defended with his hands.

Within the light, two overwhelming powers clashed against each other.

There was no sound but only trembling within the space, which exceeded humans' listening abilities.

The secret chamber was shattered by the overwhelming power and exploded into countless black pieces, revealing the pure light from the outside.

Garen pushed forward with both of his hands and went into an empty space.

It was then his eyes were slowly getting used to the surroundings.

He was standing in a space which was purely white. There was nothing around him. Everything was completely white from the top, bottom, left and right. The black pieces that were from the secret chamber had disappeared to somewhere.

Nadia was in all black, similar to how she was dressed previously. Black short skirt, long black stockings, her long hair was flowing freely. She had a thin waist and big bust, which was the perfect figure for a woman. It was just that the mask which was half laughing and half crying which made people feel uncomfortable.

"We meet again…" Nadia's deep male tone came from afar.

Although the two of them were a distance of tens of meters apart, the voice could be clearly heard as if it was spoken just beside his ear.

"You really have gotten stronger," Nadia stared at Garen through her mask.

While both of them were in masks, Garen's mask was covered with densely packed eyes. Within the dream, it's as if the eyes were alive as they kept wiggling about, staring at Nadia who was in front of him. However, that was Garen's icy blue aura which he couldn't suppress that had leaked out from the mask.

The strength of the fifth star, the upper limits of his strength…

"It's not just me who has gotten stronger. I see you've gotten weaker…" Garen gently touched his left eye socket.

Kaboom!!

Almost instantaneously, both of them disappeared, each forming into white and black figures. Their figures drew clear lines amidst the white light.

Boom!!

His fist and her knife clashed with each other. The knife was moving up and down rapidly as it tried to saw off the black fist that was harder than diamond.

Garen growled as he blocked the mark knife with his left hand and punched with all his might with his right hand. His right shoulder expanded, so much so that it was almost twice as big.

It was an absolute strength!! A strength that nothing could withstand!!

Garen's face was as hard as metal and sparks were formed as he flung his right hand in the air. It was the extreme effects of friction between the air and his hand. His scorching red fist, which was covered with sparks flew towards Nadia's head.

His right fist was the same size as Nadia's head.

"Swallow Killing Slash!!!"

Nadia growled as well as she withdrew a small dagger from her long sword. The dagger was covered with a layer of electricity and had blocked Garen's fist.

Clash!!

Two of their overwhelming forces burst, forming a very clear shockwave as it spread out with them at the epicenter.

The black dagger in Nadia's hand kept vibrating. As two Secret Techniques at their most advanced state clashed against each other, they vibrated, forming friction with an incredibly high frequency that no human could hope to hear.

"If only I could use Projection…!!" Nadia felt that her strength was being suppressed and her gaze looked rather panicked under the mask.

"Die!!!"

Garen pushed forward and the vibration of his right fist pushed away her mark knife, allowing his fist to move forward!

Boom!!

Nadia's head was instantly crushed. She screamed at the top of her lungs as she melted into countless shadows.

"I'll be back!!"

Nadia's voice still remained in the space.

Suddenly the white light surrounding him turned dark.

Garen slowly opened his eyes.

He was in his original position, standing in the secret chamber, in front of where the suppressed coin was located. With the superimposed electromagnetic waves emitted by the masks, he could feel the mysterious energy concentrating at one location.

The black dragon-shaped aura on the coin was restricted to an area the size of a fist as it kept flowing within.

‘It seems to be much easier this time,' Black Sethe had just realized he'd been under attack.

"Of course," Garen clenched his fist, The limit of strength, the overwhelming strength which could destroy everything made him nostalgic.

The absolute and most powerful strength!!

As he felt his own heartbeat, he couldn't help but feel very satisfied with himself.

Chapter 681: Obtain 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"How strong is an army level individual?"

Garen asked as he walked out of the secret chamber.

‘You were close to an army level when you activated your fifth star…' Black Sethe pondered for a moment before responding.

"Then why is there the need to learn the Peacock Technique?" Garen casually put on the shirt on the hanger by the door.

It was already night time outside.

The silver moonlight shone through the window and settled on his face.

‘Secret Technique isn't just strength,' Black Sethe muttered.

"That's because that strength isn't powerful enough," Garen rebutted.

Black Sethe went silent. Recently she’d been reacting strangely and would keep quiet instead of speaking up.

However, Garen understood that the illusion created by his overwhelming increment in strength, the feeling of being able to force everything to go his way was nothing but an illusion of the strength that overflowed from his body.

His current limit was still thirty points. This wasn't just because of the genetic limitation, it was his soul limit as well.

A weak and fragile soul would not be able to handle a powerful body. Similarly, a weak body would not be able to contain a powerful soul.

A weak soul would be easily affected by the status of the physical body. One would most likely lose oneself and become a beast. On the other hand, a weak physical body would not be able to contain a powerful soul. If one were to fully utilize the strength of the soul, one would die as due to the overexertion of one's body.

"I can only reach the limit of a human by purely increasing the strength of my physical body. I still sleep, need oxygen to breathe and these are all my disadvantages. By practicing Secret Techniques, I can mimic other advanced beings and obtain their advantages so that I could completely eliminate any weaknesses that I have."

Garen had finally woken up from his obsession with strength and he suddenly felt that his body had become taller and stronger. After activating the fifth star, his body was affected by the potential points once more and had become even stronger. Perhaps this was the aftermath of achieving ten points in Vitality as well.

Just as he’d upgraded himself, a battle arrived at his doorstep. Under these circumstances, Nadia was easily defeated by him.

Perhaps this was due to the masks' suppression on Nadia, which prevented her strength from reaching the limit of thirty points of strength. For her to go against Garen who had thirty points, she was completely oppressed and Garen managed to win the fight with a decisive punch.

He gently touched his forehead where he'd been struck by Nadia's Ominous Space Path. The Ominous Space Path's unique feature was that she would counter the attack without fail if he were to attack her.

Garen was blocking the opponent's huge sword but his forehead had been slashed by it. However, as he was in the fifth-star state which allowed him to possess the upper limit of strength, his whole body was as tough as an alloy or even better.

It was because of this that he was able to withstand that slash.

"How can I defend against such an attack...?" Garen stood under the moonlight as he pondered.

"There are three ways. Firstly, I should not let her have the opportunity or time to draw her sword at all, then this technique would be useless against me. However, that's impossible. Traitors are a subset of Void Creatures and they can appear at any moment. No one would be able to predict when they will appear or disappear."

Garen walked towards the window and opened it to allow the cold night air to enter the stuffy room.

"The second approach is to decrypt the mystery of this technique and find a way to counter it. There is no perfect technique in every world but this is something I'm not able to do at the moment." Garen shook his head as the Ominous Space Path was the strongest technique he'd ever seen. To be able to counter-attack while being attacked and attack through spacetime. All the mystery was packed in that instant and his five senses weren't able to process everything in that instant. Hence he wasn't able to understand its mystery.

"Then the third approach would be distraction…" Garen reached out his hand and looked at his ashen palm.

Fantasy Fist was a horrifying fist technique that would misguide the opponent's target. If he could use it against all living beings…

This fist technique could be used on humans as its principle was to affect and oppress the nerves in the brain. If he could find a way to extend this effect to the soul, perhaps he could lift the original limit to beyond living beings.

However, he didn't possess the knowledge to modify the technique at the moment, as he was too unfamiliar with the nature of the Void Creatures.

If this were to be completed, he would be able to distract Nadia's power and misguide her to attack other places or even other targets. This was distraction.

After thinking of ways to counter her technique and not achieving anything, Garen looked back at his Attribute Pane.

He had 234 potential points remaining and it would have very little effects if he were to use it on his attributes as he couldn't exceed that thirty points limit no matter what. He should use it for other stuff.

He had a few options. He could add them to the Secret Technique but he was unable to increase the core of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique and he would most likely encounter the same situation if he were to change to another Living Secret Technique.

He could use it for what he had been doing all these while, which was to recover his injuries to prevent any incidents.

Another option was to focus on one attribute point. When it reached a certain height, a unique feature would appear.

For example, when his intelligence reached twelve points in the Totem World, it had the effect of Double Critical Attack. It wasn't a strength that could be achieved by using the Seven Star Life's Secret Point. He would need to possess such characteristics in order to achieve it.

With the Double Critical Attack, he would produce twice the amount of strength with his fists. What seemed to be a single fist would have the strength of two fists superimposed onto each other. It was the effect of disrupting the nervous system at a high level.

That was the first time he'd obtained an ability from his attribute. Even when other attributes had reached twenty points, he didn't obtain anything at all. Up until now, he knew that twelve points of intelligence would give him an ability.

After pondering for awhile, he chose to increase his Intelligence.

He focused his gaze on Intelligence and it immediately jumped from seven points.

It reached eight points at the cost of 20 potential points. Sixty potential points to reach 9 points and another sixty potential points to reach 10 points.

Once the Intelligence had reached 10 points, he had spent 140 potential points, leaving behind 94 points. Once the attribute had reached ten points, it would require a hundred potential point to increase it, but he currently had only 94 points.

"I need more potential points," Garen had completely absorbed the potential points from all four masks that he had obtained and he wasn't sure how long it would take for him to slowly recover. However, he could immediately obtain a mask from Halo and it might be able to push his Intelligence to 12 points, which would give him the Double Critical Attack effect.

With that, his strength would be improved greatly.

************

After a few days. It was a sunny day.

The water of a fountain kept flowing down like a multi-layered cake. It was like a three-tiered mini waterfall.

There were two small metal birds playing around on top of the fountain. It was very life-like.

"The item is underneath there and we can't get any closer than this." Allen Hill's face was pale as he stood in front of Garen and Rod, pointing at a huge tree in the forest.

The tree was black, had no leaves and there were countless thin vines coming down to the ground around it like a banyan tree. The tree was slanted slightly to the left as if it was about to topple over.

Three of them stood inside Halo's secret garden, looking at the mysterious cannibal tree in front of them.

"The cannibal tree possesses a strong attack and it is very poisonous. Our people will be attacked by the vines if they get close to it and none of us are capable of resisting the poison," Allen Hill explained.

"How about your protective suit?" Rod frowned.

"It's no use. Except for killing the tree from afar to obtain the mask, we've tried everything and failed. Unless it is a very thick protective suit made out of a unique material, it would be eroded within a very short amount of time," Allen Hill glanced at Garen, waiting for him to suggest something.

"I've promised you before that we will obtain the mask without killing the cannibal tree…" Rod smiled wryly as he looked at Garen eagerly. Frankly speaking, it was Garen who agreed to it instead of him. In order to save time, avoid any unnecessary trouble and create more enemies, Garen chose a conservative solution which both parties agreed: To obtain the mask without killing the cannibal tree.

Allen had agreed to bring them to where the cannibal tree was after Rod’s vouch. Deep down, he knew that even if he were to reject him, he wouldn't be able to stop Garen anyway, so he agreed in order to look like the bigger person.

"You guys can think of the way. We're helpless from this point on," He retreated to one side and looked at them. He had already prepared himself that the cannibal tree would be killed. He wouldn't dare to push this issue onto Garen so naturally, Rod would be blamed for this. You could say that he had already hated Rod.

"I'll go for it," Garen was in a black stretch vest and exquisite black leather jeans, contouring his streamlined legs.

He glanced at Allen Hill as he grabbed and cracked both of his hands and exercised his shoulders before walking towards the cannibal tree which was a distance away.

It was morning and the weather wasn't that hot yet as the sun was only half the way up. Only a small ray shone onto the garden, landing onto Garen's right side and the ground, which made the grass greener than usual.

What made is strange was that with the cannibal tree as the epicenter, there were no other green plants within tens of meters in diameter. Only black dirt and white bones were present.

As the breeze blew, it couldn't be confirmed if it was the breeze that had made the cannibal tree's vines moved or it had started to move on its own.

Suddenly, it was as if the tree felt threatened that it had started to vibrate.

‘Wait!' Black Sethe's voice suddenly appeared.

Garen stopped and stood still. "What's wrong?" He frowned slightly. No matter if it was a cannibal tree, it was just a big tree.

‘This tree feels very strange after being affected by the mask,' Black Sethe didn't know what exactly was happening as well, ‘Be careful.'

The few people behind Garen was staring tightly at him. Although they didn't understand why he stopped moving, Rod and Allen Hill had their own thoughts as they stared at Garen, waiting for him to get near to the cannibal tree.

Garen, who had stopped moving, started to move once more.

Suddenly, his vision went blurry and the sky turned dim all of the sudden. The guards nearby had disappeared as well.

Garen frowned as he felt an intense headache.

He turned his head around and realized that Rod and Allen Hill had disappeared. He was the only one left in the garden.

He turned back and he could faintly see a girl in white dress peeking at him around the big tree.

The girl's face couldn't be seen clearly as most of her face was blocked by the vines. Only one of her eyes and long black hair could be seen. Her eye was huge and didn't blink at all.

Unknowingly, the sky was filled with dark clouds and it was now incredibly cloudy.

"It's the Dream World," Garen was very familiar with the sensation as he often entered into this realm. This allowed him to detect the abnormalities around him. He believed that he had been hypnotized by the cannibal tree and had entered the dream world. It seemed that the mask's effect had made this tree rather strange.

He looked at the girl by the tree as he took a few steps to the left, trying to see the woman's face clearly.

However, the girl kept revealing only half of his face. As he moved, the girl moved as well.

"What a boring game," Garen smiled coldly as he walked towards the cannibal tree.

The distance was getting shorter and shorter. Ten meters, nine meters, eight, seven, six, five…

Immediately, Garen stopped.

Chapter 682: Obtain 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He raised his arm and to his surprise, he saw lines of worms crawling beneath his skin.

The lines were squirming slowly between his skin and muscle, like fishes swimming in water. It seemed like some sort of a worm.

"Is this an illusion?" Garen closed his eyes and opened them once more and saw that the lines in his hands had disappeared.

He continued walking towards the cannibal tree and the vines nearby started to move. They were so dense it looked like a person's hair.

Sizzle…

Countless vines gathered together and swiftly knitted many black butterflies which spanned several meters wide.

The butterflies fluttered their wings gently as they pulled at the black vines and floated before Garen.

Cling!

Suddenly, thin gaps were opened in the middle of the butterflies' bodies, as if they had opened hidden mouths.

Slash!!

Garen shoved his hands deep into the mouth of a butterfly and tore it into halves with his hands.

"Don't you have anything that's more powerful? Bring it on," Garen smiled coldly as he prowled towards the Cannibal Tree.

That girl appeared once more and stared at Garen from the left side of the tree with one of her eyes.

Garen reached out his hand and tried to grab the woman's face but to no avail. He was stunned, as he didn't expect to fail at capturing her with his speed.

"It's time to end this game," he raised up his right hand. His hand started to swell and his skin immediately turned black green, giving off a metal like sheen; he had activated the first star.

He aimed at the cannibal tree and grabbed it with all his might.

Ahh!!!

A loud cry could be heard.

Garen's vision turned blurry as he pierced through the cannibal tree's trunk with his right hand under the neutral scream.

When he regained consciousness, he was already standing in front of the big tree. The sky was bright and he could hear the voice of Rod, Allen Hill and the guards behind him.

His right hand was pierced deep into the tree trunk. Fresh blood was slowly flowing out of the tree trunk.

Plop…

Garen took out his hand, lowered his head and looked beneath his foot.

The soil opened up automatically, revealing a part of the black mask.

He crouched down and tugged the mask out with all of his strength. The familiar cool aura immediately flowed into his hands. It was the Potential Points.

'You killed an invisible creature,' Black Sethe finally spoke, 'However, this invisible creature doesn't seem to possess any strength. Other than the cannibal tree's corrosive and poisonous characteristics, it only possesses a little bit of illusive capability. To you, it may be nothing, but for others, it is an incredibly threatening being.'

Garen finally understood what had happened. The invisible creature existed in a world that no humans could see. Hence he had a hard time understanding their existence.

He then quickly returned to where Rod and the others were. Both of them stared at him as if they'd seen a ghost.

"I've got the mask," Garen waved the mask in his hand, "Why are you guys staring me like that?"

Rod pointed at Garen's shoulder. His finger was slightly trembling as if he had seen something horrifying.

Garen lowered his head and saw a worm-like thin line squirming in his shoulder's skin. It looked like a living being that kept squirming in his left shoulder.

'It's the curse of the invisible creature,' Black Sethe explained at the right time, 'Some of the invisible creatures will cast a curse upon those who offended them. However, in your case, you just need to purify it with the Void Core and you'll be fine. Even so, it's something terrifying for commoners. These thin lines are called Gluttony. They will first keep eating your muscles and then drill into your organs until you die.'

Understanding the whole situation, Garen took out a small piece of black Void Core and gently pressed it onto the thin line.

Green smoke started to appear.

Sizzle…

The thin line gave off some smoke and soon the pieces disappeared as if it had been absorbed into his body.

"This item looks very strange. It looks like some sort of parasite!" Rod finally gave a sigh of relief.

"Let's go," Garen held onto the mask as he walked out of the garden.

Rod followed behind closely.

Allen Hill, who was behind him, stared at him with a complicated gaze. Garen had done it. He had obtained the mask without killing the cannibal tree. It seemed that he didn't actually dig it out but that the cannibal tree had given it to him on itself.

He turned around and looked at the cannibal tree. It looked spiritless and seemed to be heavily injured, but it was much better than being toppled over.

"What's the status on Kenna and Cole?" he whispered to Mole, who had just approached him.

"We haven't captured them yet, but I fear that they're still looking for opportunities. It's definitely them who leaked out the news for the Nighthawk King to come here all of the sudden." Mole whispered. They were quite lucky this time. If not for Rod who acted as a connection, the Nighthawk King might have forced things to go his way and Halo's losses would have been great.

"Are you sure Kenna and Cole are not related to the Nighthawk King in any way?" Allen Hill whispered.

"I've done my research. Kenna was almost killed by the Nighthawk King once in Africa. For unknown reasons, he'd decided to let him live," Mole replied confidently as intel and tracking were his forte.

"Then we will kill them! I'll lead the way!" Allen Hill had decided to divert his vengeance onto them. Not only had he sustained internal injuries from Garen, his precious cannibal tree was injured as well. Furthermore, the mask underneath it had been taken away by force. To add insult to injury, he had to cooperate throughout the process instead of fighting back. This angered him to his limit.

Garen who had walked far away then shifted away his focus as he smirked.

He didn't care about Kenna's objective of using him. As long as he'd achieved his own objective, it was enough for him. It didn't concern him in the least whether Kenna was alive or not.

************

Time flew and one month had passed by in a blink of an eye. Germany's weather had gotten colder as it entered winter in November.

White snow blanketed the Berlin suburbs. The mask Garen obtained from the cannibal tree only possessed eighty plus points, which wasn't a lot. It seemed that the cannibal tree was absorbing this energy as well and had used up most of the potential points, hence it didn't have much left.

Eighty-two points had been added to the ninety-four points that he had and in total, he now had 176 points. This was enough for him to add one point to Intelligence, achieving 11 points.

After reaching ten points, each attribute would require an astronomical amount of potential points to increase it. One attribute point would require one hundred potential points. It would be easy if it was in the Totem world but in this world, it was extremely tedious.

Garen had no choice but to start searching for the location of the next mask after he used up the potential points. Fortunately, the fifth mask that he had obtained from the cannibal tree had a rather good suppression effect on the dragon-shaped coin after its magnetic waves were superimposed onto it along with the other masks. The frequency of Nadia's attacks had been greatly reduced and her strength was temporarily weakened. However, Nadia soon started to use a different method and was closing in on Garen once more. Her strength had improved and this forced Garen to search for the location of the new mask.

According to the intel provided by Rod, the sixth mask was located in the Global Forest Belt - Memphis Forest.

The Memphis Forest was an area unique to this world. It was like a green belt encircling the planet, spreading into the endless horizon. Rumor had it that the mask was located at the edge of a moon river. A moon river was a river which was shaped like a crescent moon and there were at least ten of them in the Memphis Forest.

As he was about to move out to Memphis Forest, news regarding the Lotus Pearl had arrived.

Rod had negotiated with the Primary Colors and they'd decided to give up on Lotus Pearl, and with Seasnake and Seal's help, they'd finally killed their target in one of New Zealand's ports.

*************

Squeak... Squeak…

At the outskirts of Berlin on a small road, the thick white snow was trampled upon, creating a crisp crunch.

A man in a grey coat was walking on a road that had yet to be plowed as he puffed out small clouds of breath through his mouth.

On his right, there were tall grey villas and on his left was a densely packed snowy pine forest. Traces of black dirt could be seen underneath the white snow. The snowy road in front of him led to an unknown location and behind him was a road and a small entrance connecting to it. By the entrance, one could see a black jeep parked there.

This man was holding a black bag. He walked forth, turned left and entered the stairs of one of the villas, before pressing the doorbell lightly.

Ring~~~

The doorbell kept ringing.

After a while, the door opened with a click. A middle-aged female servant who looked rather sincere and honest opened the door. She nodded her head, gestured him to enter and didn't say a word at all.

The guy seemed to know who this female servant was.

"Thank you, Marquilli," he carried his bag in before taking off his coat and hood, revealing his shiny bald head as he passed the coat to the servant.

With one hand holding onto the bulging bag, he changed his shoes and headed directly to the second floor.

As he stepped onto the black wooden flooring upstairs, he walked straight towards the room on the right and gently knocked on its door.

"Please enter," a man's voice could be heard from the inside.

The man opened the door and saw a handsome golden haired man sitting inside. He had been about to put down his phone and glanced at him sideways. From his angle, he could faintly see the information on the phone's screen.

It seemed like a conversation between him and his family.

The seated golden-haired man was still smiling gently.

"I've brought the items," he immediately diverted his gaze as he didn't dare to peek further.

"Alright, it's the deal with Seasnake's subordinate, right?" the golden-haired man was Garen, who had been stationed in Berlin for quite a while. He'd practically stopped going to university and had invested his full attention in obtaining the masks. His explanation to his family was that he had opened a company on his own and university was of little use to him. He just needed it to obtain the certificate.

Garen had looked through the course of Gullivier University and he had already submitted his thesis and research reports. As long as he passed, the university didn't care what he was doing with his life.

Baldy placed the black bag on the table in front of Garen.

He opened the zip and took out a black plastic from it. He then unwrapped the plastic as he placed it on the table.

A faint musky odor slowly diffused around the room.

Within the bag was a human head.

"This is Lotus Pearl, representing Mr. Rod's sincerity," Baldy stuttered as he spoke softly.

Chapter 683: Search 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Lotus Pearl…" Garen put down his phone, staring at the forehead of the girl's head that had been placed on the table with her eyes wide open.

This girl's appearance was extremely hideous, with a huge sarcoma growing on her right cheekbone, and due to the lack of blood circulation, her face was excessively pale. Her eyes were very small, and there was still a hint of the ruthlessness from when she was still alive.

Stretching out his hand, Garen lightly caressed Lotus Pearl's cheeks. They were soft, almost indistinguishable from a real human's.

"Bury it in front of Jay's grave."

"Understood," the baldy nodded, then wrapped the head back up before leaving.

Garen rested his chin with one hand and knocked on the table with the other.

Knock knock knock.

Almost immediately a bell could be heard from outside the door, and the mute maid Marquilli opened the door, pushing in a white service cart. The cart was covered with a white piece of cloth and was emitting a mouthwatering aroma. All the dishes had been recreated from Garen's memory, made by the gourmet chefs handpicked by Garen himself and the dishes were specially made just for Garen in his favorite oriental style.

Following behind the service cart, a black-haired girl walked in. The girl was wearing a black latex bodysuit, had smooth and silky shoulder-length hair, and a pretty face. She was the female leader of the Primary Colours team, who had led the way for Garen from before.

Underneath her disguise, she was actually a young girl who was not even 20 years old.

After she'd brought Garen to the White Phoenix base, allowing Garen to destroy it, the Primary Colours put a bounty on her head. Hence, she didn't dare to go anywhere else and had no other choice but to stay with Garen. Ironically, the most dangerous location had now become the safest for her.

The hostility between the Primary Colours and the Nighthawks was mainly due to the conflict between Gremlin and Garen. However, after the merger between Garen and the Rexott Group, the Nighthawks have become a monstrous force on the same level with the Primary Colors, which put a lot of pressure on them, especially since Rod's brother was an influential member in the top ranks of the Rexott Group.

The Primary Colours had internal factionalism, as Gremlin's strength was growing increasingly isolated, it became much safer to stay by Garen's side.

"Simone, how's it going?" Garen smiled at this young chief. Although she was only 19 years old, she had been one of the Primary Colour's top elite reserve members.

"What do you mean 'How's it going'?" Simone sat in the chair placed in front of Garen's table, "Those kids you have to train have already arrived outside, when are you going to go and meet them?"

"There's no rush," Garen shook his head, "So, what are your plans?" Simone was one of the elites picked out by the Primary Colours, meaning that her talent and foundation was not something other average humans could replicate. Luring this kind of talent to his side, it was perfect for an assistant and a successor. Since Jay's death, Garen had started to feel the void of not having an assistant.

"My plans?" Simone was taken by surprise with that question. She didn't have parents and had been raised by her aunt since she was young, and her step-brother was a drug lord so their relationship wasn't close. In the Primary Colours, everyone suppressed their emotions so there weren't many friendships, and she only had a friend in London. After considering all of this, she didn't have any good locations to take shelter in and therefore had chosen to stay by Garen's side.

"If you don't have any plans, why not just stay here and train with me?" Garen raised his arms into a fighting stance while smiling at her, "Your innate talent is great. As long as you manage to control it, you'll gain access to that hidden strength."

Simone stared at Garen, almost as if his two hands were glowing, giving off a warm, mesmerizing halo that held her full attention.

"You're trying to manipulate me again!!!" she tried her hardest to look away, but she couldn't take her eyes off of him.

"This isn't manipulation," Garen murmured tenderly, "I'm only trying to help you make a decision."

Simone started losing all strength in her body and her mind was getting a bit hazy. After a while, she passed out.

The maid at the side was looking on with a weird look, though she still continued to place the dishes on the table. She could not understand the language and the accent the two were conversing in.

Garen had a habit of eating in the reading room, one that he'd had for a long time.

"Carry Ms. Simone out for some rest," Garen ordered.

Marquilli nodded, then propped Simone on her shoulder and walked out of the room.

Garen was once again alone in the room.

Everything was going according to plan. Most importantly, the suppression of the Nine-Headed King Nadia was starting to have an effect; the masks were proven to have a suppressing effect on his coordinates. Unfortunately, either the coin's strength was too great or the mask mimics' strength was too weak; after Nadia started to get used to it, her strength had slowly been returning and she was slowly becoming stronger again. These days, the continuous confrontations with her and her suppression had put him in an unfavorable position.

'You need to find the remaining masks,' Black Sethe's voice started ringing, 'At the same time, you need to finish the Demonic Book as soon as possible as it may be able to construct your second soul seed. Once your second soul seed has been constructed, you might be able to break through your current strength limit, reaching an even higher level. Remember, no matter what, your soul is your foundation.'

"This I understand, the two must be done at the same time," Garen answered softly while starting on his meal. Beef strips with gravy, steamed minced meat, stir-fried potato floss, braised eggplants...

All these dishes made Garen feel as if he was back on Earth. Every time he has meals like this, he would always get this strange mixture of familiarity and unfamiliarity.

Outside the window, it seemed that it has started to snow again, although it was almost completely silent, Garen could make out the sounds of the snow landing on the pavement on the road outside.

He looked out the window at the white, bubble-like snow was slowly drifting down towards the earth.

In the blink of an eye, more than 20 years have passed while living in this world, a world where Blood Breeds, Witches, and technology could coexist. The threat of void creatures was slowly approaching, complicating the overall situation of this world.

After silently finishing his meal, Garen had the maid clean up. He sat in the room for a bit more before slowly getting up and walking out of the room, up to a pure white wall on the same floor. He then lightly tapped it a few times.

Bam!

The wall started to move to the left, creating a doorway into a dark, hidden room.

Closing the room door, Garen turned on the light, illuminating his surroundings.

He walked up to the wall at the other end of the room and lightly pressed his palm on the wall, which started to vibrate.

Abruptly, a hidden drawer compartment sprung out from the wall.

Inside the compartment lay the Demonic Book and the dragon-shaped coin placed under the mask.

The Demonic Book was placed on top, and while the paper quality was obviously average material, it seemed to have been corrupted by his soul's aura when he was writing. The entire Demonic Book now appeared to have the texture of human skin, almost as if it was made from human skin itself.

Grabbing the pen sandwiched between the pages of the book, Garen walked back to his reading room and closed the door. He started to flip through all the things he had written down up till now.

Two-Faced Waterbird Fist, Shooting Shadow Secret Technique, Fantasy Fist, Slaughtering Hand...

He'd only just started writing on Slaughtering Hand; after all, this was a demonic technique from Black Sethe that even he had not fully mastered. When he was writing, he only wrote down the parts which he had a mastery of, something like a categorization of his self-understanding and knowledge system.

'Write down the secret techniques from your dark side, and by combining them and creating one true core, that will be the demonic technique seed, one that is most appropriate for you. Once you manage to master this created demonic technique, you'll most likely be able to construct your second soul seed,' Black Sethe uttered in a low tone. Recently, he sounded more and more silent, didn't talk much and would constantly cut straight to the point.

"This is a process for removing all impurities," Garen nodded.

He picked up his pen and started jotting down his knowledge on the Slaughtering Hand.

As the clock continued to tick, two hours passed quickly and Garen's notes were more or less completed; he'd finished recording down the way to train and develop the Slaughtering Hand and his own understanding on the technique.

Just as he finished writing his last statement, he felt as if the entire Demonic Book has transformed into a beating heart.

Lub-dub!

It was almost as though the entire room was beating along with it, making even Garen feel like his heartbeat was being affected by it. He felt as if at that moment, his heartbeat has synchronized with the Demonic Book.

He closed his eyes, and the Demonic Book within his mind seemed to have done the same. As the remaining vibrations slowly dispersed, the two covers of the Two Demonic Books started to emit a dark aura.

Garen decided to record all of his secret techniques from his dark side as well.

He started to cautiously count the amount of dark side secret techniques he had trained before in the past.

One of the most invincible evil techniques from his past life suddenly popped up in his mind.

"Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique…"

Picking up his pen once more, Garen wrote the name of this technique into it. As soon as he finished writing, the Demonic Book seemed to start glowing blue, the blue of glacial ice.

******

Crash!

A vase was shattered on the floor.

Gremlin's face was lined with veins. As he gulped in deep breaths, his throat was quivering constantly, and he looked so furious that he almost looked deranged.

In a golden room illuminated by numerous lantern lights, two of his underlings were standing right in front of him. Despite being suavely dressed in suits, the two were sweating bullets; their foreheads were completely soaked in sweat as they both bowed down, not moving a muscle.

"Lotus Pearl died?! I just had a call with her less than half a day ago and now you guys are telling me she died?" Gremlin did not suppress a single iota of his rage.

Lotus Pearl was one of his best soldiers, and despite weird personality, her talents as an assassin were one of the best. Even when compared to others, her skills would be considered unparalleled.

But now, she'd died…

It felt like a fire was scorching his heart.

"Garen… Thomas!!" he roared in fury.

"Team leader… The top has sent down a notice, do not clash with the Nighthawks anymore…" one of the underlings stated, cautiously choosing his words.

"Scram!!"

Gremlin lashed out in a fit of rage.

With a loud slap, this underling was knocked to the floor, and he scrambled out of the room while holding his cheek in pain.

"Do you think I'm out of ideas just because you kissed up to Rexott?" Gremlin chuckled with a manic expression.

Chapter 684: Search 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Lotus Pearl's death had dealt a large blow to him. She'd been one of the spec-ops soldiers on him and his father's side, and she could even be considered the top-ranked in terms of strength in the group. She had been so easily defeated by the enemy. Even if the assailant were Rexott's Seasnake and Seal, it was obvious that Rexott was helping the Nighthawks. The brother of Rod, Garen's friend, was a member of the most feared groups in Rexott, the Big Four, more commonly known as the Four Shadows. Rod's brother was the head of the Four Shadows, and if they were compared to Titan in the Primary Colours, the two were at the same level. They've clashed numerous times in the past, but both were always on par with each other. Against this kind of monstrous existence, Gremlin had no way of countering against it. Unless his father personally joined the fray, there would not be anyone from the group willing to clash with them just for the sake of his family's influence.

Looking at the last underling.

Gremlin forcefully suppressed his rage.

"What is the Nighthawk King doing now?"

"According to our reports, his and Rod's side are currently searching for the Mask of Sleepless Faces from the legends. On the surface, it is said to be because Garen likes to collect these types of antiques, but we think he may have other hidden intentions," the underling answered quickly.

"The Mask of the Sleepless Faces?" Gremlin repeated softly, "According to the legends, there are certain types of mysterious antiques that were said to have some sort of special power, and that kind of power can allow one to achieve superhuman abilities. Is that true?"

"According to our investigation, they most likely have some sort of use for them, but this information was mainly leaked from the Men in Black that recently left after seeing the Nighthawks' new high ranks and it hasn't been proven yet. We also have not developed a fundamental concrete judgment standard for these antiques and relics as of yet," the underling answered, seeing as his boss' mood was slightly improved, he added one more line, "Should we initiate a more practical investigation? If the NIghthawk King is so passionate about this, there must be some correlation."

"Do it, also try to investigate the secrets under Nighthawks' control, whatever they call secret techniques or secret methods. It would become valuable information if we manage to get it in our hands. We cannot let this leak to the public." as Gremlin thought about all the mysterious methods used by the Nighthawks, he started to feel furious again. A way to allow normal humans to achieve the ultimate level of martial arts, it was undoubtedly something he had to get his hands on. Once he acquired the method of doing this, he might be able to rise up even higher within the ranks of the Primary Colors.

******

Bailey Estate, Germany

Kabb was gently cradling her baby, intimately pinching his cheeks.

Sitting on the white semicircular balcony, she could hear familiar footsteps coming from behind her. Kabb looked back, seeing a familiar silhouette.

"Medis, are there any updates?"

"According to the latest reports, Garen goes into a secret room in his villa for a period of time every day, though we have no information on what he does inside."

Medis walked up behind Kabb. This young man was sly and cunning, had a pretty face, and in terms of reconnaissance, he had many tricks up his sleeves. He was even able to gather so much information on the Nighthawk King.

He looked at his boss' son, whose chubby face was looking around in amusement. He then continued to speak.

"We attempted to investigate the internal members of the Nighthawks. According to the results we've gotten , the whole Nighthawks group and the Combat Club should all be under Garen's control alone. These methods seem to be as you hypothesized, boss, it should be the work of the special strength from the masks."

"I heard that Garen is planning to go to Memphis?" Kabb smiled while she continued to play with her son. "Where did you obtain the information about the secret room?"

"Yes, it was said that they were going to search for the masks, and this was also deduced from the movements of Rod's men. This kind of large action operation can't be that easily hidden. They made no effort to hide it as well," Medis nodded, "Regarding the Secret Room, I've used an unconscious investigation method, scheduling my people to observe the movements villa from the corner of their eyes. I told them not to observe Garen himself, but rather to focus the mute maid. As a maid in charge of serving Garen, there are a lot of things she would not be able to hide about the villa."

"Great work. Pay extra attention to Garen's schedules next," Kabb replied softly, "Primary Colour's Gremlin has been suppressed but he will definitely seek revenge, especially since he lost one of his strongest soldiers when Rod started to side with Garen. With the addition of Seasnake and Seal, two experts, alongside Garen himself, this is no longer a force that we can reckon with. We need to remain on Garen's good side if possible. Use the safest methods to continue your investigations of the secret room."

"Understood," Medis nodded slightly to show her acknowledgment.

Kabb pinched her son's face.

Poot!

The chubby kid spat a bit on her face.

"Hahaha, this kid's got guts! I like it!" Kabb started laughing out loud. Medis couldn't resist but to laugh along with her.

******

Writing the Demonic Book proved to be more of a challenge that Garen had originally thought.

Under careful scrutiny and analysis of his memories, these secret techniques he'd once thought he had completely mastered and understood now seemed to have a plethora of minor difficulties and problems. All of these were things that he'd missed in the past, and a lot of the steps that he thought he completely understood had multiple difficulties hidden within them.

When writing about the Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, he kept running into problems one after the other, accumulating a total of more than 10 issues.

As he was thinking about how to resolve these problems, the changes in the Demonic Book became more and more obvious.

Now that Garen had already written down around half of his secret techniques, the Demonic Book seemed to have synchronized; almost as if it was a living plant, it started to grow along with whatever Garen wrote.

Maybe once he finished writing this Demonic Book, it would be the most suitable time for him to develop his demonic technique. Then, through his own understanding of the demonic technique, he would be able to master the demonic technique even faster and achieve the creation of the soul seed that would allow him to exceed his limits, which was his ultimate goal.

This was happening abnormally smoothly, unlike his progress on the other side.

Regarding the training, all the volunteer pupils that were recommended by the Nighthawks were all spoiled brats. They were all crying to go home or wanting to give up before the first session of training even ended.

However, they were answered with a slap from Garen, knocking them out.

What a joke, these people were all hand picked by Garen, and most of them had decent innate talent and backgrounds. If he just let them go back, wouldn't that be a waste of his time?

Garen just directly used violence and brute force. He had the aid of the Nighthawks and the Combat Club in the background anyway, and with Rod's Rexott Group backing him as well, he had nothing to worry about.

******

Bam! Bam! Bam!!

A coordinated and rhythmic sound of strikes echoed through the gymnasium.

A group of students, clad in full black training gis, formed an orderly circle. In the middle of that circular formation stood Garen and a female student, Simone.

Simone repeatedly dragged her body back up, persevering despite her cheeks already looking as swollen as two red steamed buns. Trickles of blood were dribbling from the corners of her lips.

Under the bright yellow light, Simone once again lunged towards Garen.

Yaaaa!!!

She let out a deafening roar, almost as if trying to boost her strength. In reality, nothing out of the ordinary happened and in a flash, everything was flipped around and the muffled thump signaled that once again, she was down on the ground.

Simone was again flung to the left by Garen with a single slap. As she tried to stand up once more, she stumbled a few steps before collapsing onto the floor. Her legs could no longer support her own body weight.

"Was this the Close Quarters Combat that you were so proud of?" Garen's top half was nude, and he was wearing only a pair of black trousers secured with a shiny black belt. His pale white skin starkly contrasted his aesthetic, sculpture-like muscular build, and his muscles flowed with every move.

"During these 4 days, I had you guys go through some basic training, it wasn't simply to torture you guys," Garen surveyed his surroundings. These people all had backgrounds in top-ranked families and firms from America and various other countries. They were candidates to become seeds like Dahm and Hochman, but since they were from different locations all over the world, they would bloom into different flowers.

"You guys will have 3 choices: the Two-Faced Waterbird Gate, the Shooting Shadow Gate, and the White Cloud Gate…"

He decided he would once again impart the White Cloud Gate's Mammoth Secret Technique, planting its seed in this world. In reality, the Mammoth Secret Technique should no longer be called the Mammoth Secret Technique, but the Divine Statue Technique instead. It used the Divine Statue Technique as the core and combined it with the essence of the Black Water True Technique to create a shockingly powerful skill. It was a top-class secret technique that he relied on to become the king of the Secret Technique World.

The Divine Statue Technique was a legitimate secret technique with absurd power, but what was strange was that when Garen was writing the Demonic Book, he accidentally wrote in the Divine Statue Technique. Unexpectedly, this technique had some qualities of a demonic technique, and once he used his soul aura as a primer to set the foundation, it would allow the subject to experience rapid growth and reach a very high level of strength. However, it would have very strong side effects, hence its resemblance to a demonic technique.

Garen renamed this technique as the Demonic Statue Technique. This reminded him of the Behemoth Gate.

Everything started from the White Cloud Gate; that was where he started, and that place also had a soft spot in his heart.

"We already know what are the Two-Faced Waterbird Gate and the Shooting Shadow Gate, but what is the White Cloud Gate?" one of the students asked loudly, who had a heroic appearance. His name was Caesar, and he was the second-in-line to inherit his household name, which was one of the oldest and most respected households in Europe. As compared to the stunning achievements of the first-in-line, he seemed to be overshadowed in every aspect. He was one of the few students out of this batch who actually took an initiative in learning.

Recently, word of Garen's Combat Club had sent tremors throughout America. Dahm went all over the place organizing combat-based tournaments. Just a short while ago, he'd even worked together with Hochman to organize the World Fighting Tournament with a 50 million euro grand prize. Participants could even claim their traveling expenses from them. This attracted various experts from all over the world to participate.

Henceforth, the names "Waterbird Fist" and "Shooting Shadow Secret Technique" spread throughout the world.

Suddenly masters of all sorts of various fighting styles from all over the world were coming out of isolation and heading to America to participate in this tournament. There were adverts everywhere advertising this tournament and also the origins of Dahm and Hochman's fighting styles.

The name of the duo's teachers was not openly revealed. He was referred to by the two companies solely by the name "Holy Fist". The only information revealed about him was that he lived up in the mountains at a place called Holy Fist Palace, and was said to be a saint who had exceeded the limitations of Fist Techniques.

No one knew what "Holy Fist" looked like or who he or she was, and only a few core members of the Combat Club knew the true identity behind their master.

Dahm and Hochman were the embodiments of the Waterbird Fist in the rumors.

Some of the students, who had some insider information, understood that this man in the mask was the "Holy Fist" of the legends. Naturally, they would understand how great an opportunity this was. If all went well, they might have a chance to become the next Dahm or Hochman, attaining countless assets and authority.

Garen looked Caesar in the eye. He was a boy who was only 19 years old and looked as if he was filled with heroic spirit as the personification of vigor.

"White Cloud Gate is a sect that uses the Demonic Statue Technique as a foundation. This gate of secret techniques originated from an ancient form of fist style, completely different from the styles of the Waterbird Fist and the Shooting Shadow Fist. It has more of an upfront fighting style."

Chapter 685: Teach 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"An upfront fighting style?"

Caesar couldn't understand what this meant.

"Isn't Waterbird Fist also an upfront fighting style?"

"That's different," Garen raised his right hand and his arm started rapidly expanding.

Bam!!!

With just one punch, he hit the ground underneath his feet, creating a blast of dust and rubble. A huge half-meter crater appeared under his feet. The dust around him was the cement that was completely pulverized by his strike.

The crater looked almost as if it was a hole that someone had dug out; it was nearly 10 cm deep. With the amount of the dust in the air, multiple students who unintentionally inhaled at the wrong moment started coughing uncontrollably.

However, some of them were not even choking on the dust but were coughing because their throats had started itching from the strength of the shockwave created.

Gulp.

Some of the students gulped in shock.

"This is an upfront fighting style," Garen pulled back his fist. His arm had no signs of damage at all.

The group of students was staring at his arm, trying to find any signs of damage. Yet, they couldn't even find a blemish on the arm.

At that moment, the students were starting to get excited.

If only I was that strong…

That was their desire within their hearts; every man would have a natural desire to become stronger. This type of monstrous fist style seemed to have won over their attention.

Garen was quite satisfied with the effects of his performance. He relaxed his arm and it started to return to its normal size, almost as if nothing had happened, except for the huge crater below him…

"Demonic Statue Technique, the principle is enhancing your body, making it stronger and harder and pushing your strength and recovery ability to the limit in order to achieve a deity-like state at the highest level. Those who want to learn this, please stand to my right."

Garen called loudly.

In an instant, out of the 15 students, 8 of them, all boys, stood to the right. All of them were in high spirits, feeling very excited. Amusingly, all of these boys were all on the skinnier side, and that included Caesar.

Out of the remaining 7 students, 5 were girls, and the other 2 boys were quite muscular. Although it seemed that they were very tempted to choose the White Cloud Gate, they all obviously had their own goals that they were very resolute on, and so they resisted the temptations offered to them.

"The remaining can go back for today. Those who are interested in the Shooting Shadow Secret Technique, gather here at 5 am sharp tomorrow," Garen raised his index finger, "Remember, all of you can only learn 1 fist style. If you start learning another fist style before you master the first one you learned, your progress will be extremely slow and it might even take years for you to even progress to the first level. Be wary, do not be fall for the temptations of greed."

"Yes." "Understood."

The remaining 7 students acknowledged his statement. After witnessing Garen's monstrous strength, none of them dared to treat him disrespectfully anymore. At the same time, all of them had completely acknowledged Garen's teaching methods.

The 5 girls and 2 boys left the gymnasium and walked past the Nighthawk members special defense line. They then drove back to the accommodation area nearby.

One of the girls tried to sneak back to peep on the training, but she was promptly ushered away by the Nighthawks.

Garen waited for the confirmation that everyone else had left, then turned to face the 8 boys before him.

Out of the 8 boys, some of them looked well-mannered, some looked creepy, and one looked sly, but all of them, at this moment, were filled with excitement, looking excitedly at Garen.

"Starting from now, I'll be explaining this technique. Please give me your undivided attention, as I will not repeat myself," Garen sternly observed the students, "This lesson may completely change your lives. I do not know whether you will regret this in the future, but since you're all already here, you can no longer turn back."

"Master! We won't regret it!!!" Caesar stood out and answered loudly.

"What we want is the strength to be able to control our own fate!!" a student who looked sickly and weak also stood out. This lad's name was Lumard, and due to doing excessive drugs, he'd become an addict, weakening his body steadily. Almost everyone in his family has given up hope for him, and he had been sent here as a last resort.

Garen looked into the eyes of these two who'd taken the initiative to declare their intentions and made a mental note to remember who they were.

"Alright! Now, let's start with the 1st part!"

The Demonic Statue Technique had 4 parts to it, the Divine Statue Technique, the Golden Statue Technique, the Metallic Statue Technique, and Bronze Statue Technique. This group of people's bodies were in such a frail state, they had to start training from the most basic Bronze Statue Technique.

This time, Garen did not have enough life force to support all of them; after what happened with his Slaughtering Hand, although he could still accumulate some life force, the amount has drastically decreased. This measly amount could only achieve the effect of extending life.

Hence, he had to be much stricter in their training as compared to his training with Hochman and Dahm.

Garen's true motive was to cultivate his own team of people, as in this world, it was difficult to work alone. He needed even more forces to be able to live an easy and relaxed life.

He was too focused on himself in the Secret Technique World, so when he fought with Cayduran in the end, he had been taken by surprise by a nuclear bomb, which led to him losing his first physical body. If he had a strong enough force and networking, this kind of issue wouldn't have happened. He would have gotten the news long before these things could happen, so he wouldn't have been taken by surprise.

This group of students were the seeds that he'd picked out, all of them blessed with certain conditions and requirements. With the right guidance, they would eventually bloom into beautiful flowers.

The training lasted for 4 hours. The Bronze Statue Technique was one of the most basic and fundamental "training secret techniques", combining the Mammoth Secret Technique and an adapted Breathing Secret Method. This made the students scream out in agony; all of them finally understood the true meaning of pain, and it felt as though their hearts were cramping terribly. They were lucky that they had undergone preliminary training by Garen, as the pain they endured from that managed to toughen their physiques, otherwise, they would have all passed out from the excruciating pain.

Garen used High-Velocity Oscillations as a core method to directly stimulate the students' blood and qi, forcing them to abide by the Breathing Secret Method and combine it with the Mammoth Secret Technique. This had great effects, as in the process, he could slowly merge the soul aura primer, making them latch on to Garen's Soul Seed while doing their own training.

He recently found out that ever since the soul seed aura has been planted into Hochman and company, as Hochman, Dahm, and the other Combat Club members continued to train, his own soul seed had started to have interesting changes as well, as if it had become stronger in tandem.

After completing the session with this group of students, he had his men bring them back to their accommodations. He even had professional masseuses and nutritionists to take care of their bodies for them.

As Garen left the gymnasium and started to drive off, he made his query to Black Sethe.

'Simple, even soul seeds have different levels,' Black Sethe answered in a carefree tone, 'After years of research by the warlocks, we have found out all the different types of realms a soul can exist in. Although we could have researched even deeper, even with this amount of information was sufficient for us to utilize for a long time.'

"A soul's realm? What do you mean?" Garen asked while still driving.

'The average soul is at the first level, it's very normal, and its strength is differentiated by its color. There's nothing much more I can say about this, and you've originally started from this level so you should be even more knowledgeable in this area.'

Garen nodded.

'The second level is the soul seed level, which is your current level. The reason it's called a seed is that it is highly concentrated and condensed into one single spot. Of course, it also implies that there's a possibility of it sprouting in the future. This level starts to have various different special effects, such as the ability to be able to change your body's vitality, improving it to adapt to the world's rules. This is the second level.'

'The third level is the true soul level, which is what I and the other warlocks once achieved. At this level, one can be considered a higher being, and your lifespan and even time itself will be greatly extended. With a true soul, you could survive in the Mother Stream, and even if you have died, if there's an opportunity in the future, you would have a small possibility of reviving yourself. At the true soul level, the soul's core cannot be put out or destroyed, hence the name true soul. It cannot be disintegrated by the Mother Stream, and even if you do reborn through the Mother Stream, you'll be able to flawlessly remember everything from your past life. Your soul has its space-time attributes so it is somewhat similar to a true soul, but it is far less powerful.'

Black Sethe gave a very detailed explanation.

'There are supposedly even higher levels of souls, but I have never attained them myself. There might be a few top-level warlocks that might have had a chance to reach it, but even the 3rd level is already impossibly difficult. We further separated each level to even smaller phases according to the bottlenecks in progress, creating tens of new phases in between each level in order to keep track of our growth and progress. You are currently at the basic of the soul seed level, so it's still too early to think about all of this.'

Garen nodded; as he had predicted, since the soul seed was called a seed, there was a possibility of it sprouting.

'When you've reached the true soul level, you will gain a true name for yourself, which is the written pronunciation of the name of your soul and must never be leaked. It has unimaginable power, in other words, the longer your true name, the stronger your soul is. Well, it's still too early to be talking about this.' Black Sethe brought it up, then decided that it wasn't the correct time for this talk.

"Soul, soul seed, true soul, 3 levels…" as Garen mumbled this repeatedly, his heart starting to yearn for it.

"How many more phases does my soul seed require for it to progress further?" he asked.

'It's still too early to tell. What's more, the progress of a soul cannot be that easily predicted, We've only managed to research one of the paths to it and there are still numerous unknown possibilities, so you shouldn't think too much about it now. Beings with true souls can effortlessly destroy even someone of the demon lord class, the strongest level among us Warlocks. There are a lot of Endor true souls hidden in the Mother Stream, but those are the ones who could not revive and are stuck in an unconscious state. They're just the remnants of our civilization from the movement of the Mother Stream, largely different from real beings with true souls.'

He paused, 'Actually, according to our theory, everyone has a true soul. In the Mother Stream, all souls will start to disintegrate until it becomes extremely small until it cannot continue to disintegrate. Then it will become a soul that cannot be disintegrated, which is what we call a true soul. If a living thing's intelligence and senses cannot permeate the deepest part of the soul, the innermost core, once exposed to the Mother Stream, that intelligence and senses will be completely wiped out and used as materials to create a new soul. However, if you can reach the true soul level, you can retain all your memories and continuously repeat the cycle of life unless your true soul is destroyed by someone.'

'Even among warlocks and void creatures, there are barely a handful of these kinds of existences. You should pay no attention to it. In comparison, your soul with its space-time attributes has an advantage. This kind of soul is not that strong but can adapt to the rules of time and space, and escape the fate of being wiped out, retain memories of past lives, and can withstand the power of the Mother Stream. Although it can still be damaged, it is far stronger than average souls.'

Chapter 686: Teach 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen nodded.

However, in his heart, he kept looking back to when he started on this journey.

He knew that his soul's space-time attributes weren't truly natural, but something that he gained from that strange red stuff, even his innate talent had been a byproduct of that.

After listening to Black Sethe's explanation, he started to suspect that he'd been the test subject of a higher being's experimentation on creating a soul with space-time attributes or possibly a byproduct from medication stimulating an evolution in his body. Whatever it was, he had definitely been 'created' by accident. It was all luck, yet it was his fate.

As long as he didn't suffer damage that could completely destroy his soul, he could continue to live on just like someone with a true soul.

Returning to his villa, his maid Marquilli poured him a cup of freshly squeezed juice and helped him hang his coat on the coathanger.

Garen went directly to the secret room and habitually checked on the demonic book, the masks hidden in the room, and of course, the most troublesome item, the coin.

Everything was where they should be, the five masks stacked neatly in a pile on top of the coin. The magnetic fields emitted by the masks were enveloping the coin to create an egg-shaped barrier.

Just as he was going to conceal the secret compartment once more, he discovered a change that stopped him in his tracks.

"This is…" Garen held up the first mask on top.

The mask originally did not have any markings or blemishes, but this time, he found a small marking on it.

At the bottom right corner of the mask, there was a marking in the form of a small black dot. It was very sharp and clear, looking almost like a punctuation mark of some sorts.

He used his hand to gently rub the surface. There weren't any bumps, and it didn't feel like it was artificially added to the mask.

He quickly looked at the other masks, and all of them had similar markings. The markings were similar in structure yet slightly differed from one another.

'As the energy fields strengthen to a certain degree, there will definitely be more clues,' Black Sethe uttered softly.

"According to the rumors, after one gathers all 12 of the masks, they will reveal the location of the prehistoric mask... Maybe the rumors were true. We're probably the first person to gather so many masks as originally, these masks were all split up and held on to by various big organizations and antique collectors," Garen pondered.

"Sleepless Faces, it seems that there's more to this than I thought…" Garen added.

"How is your training in the dream world as a void pursuer?' Black Sethe suddenly asked.

"Why do you ask?"

'If you've reached the level where you can freely move in the dream world, that means you have reached the level of visions,' Black Sethe explained, 'Once you've entered the visions level, you will be able to see things that you couldn't before. This may be helpful for finding out more clues about the masks.'

"Vision?" Garen repeated.

'Yes, the dream world is filled with disillusionment, but at the same time, it also functions like a radio that can receive a lot of weak signals. Some signals may contain some white noise and useless clutter, but some are able to reflect actual reality. Dreams are actually another perception sense of a human other than the conventional five senses. Hence, if you can fully wield and hone these senses, you'll be able to gain a lot of valuable information.'

"The dream world as a perception sense?" this was the first time Garen had heard of something like this.

'You can start trying to observe your dream worlds. Anyways, Nadia is currently being temporarily suppressed by the masks and the date of her attack is still quite far off, so you might as well use this buffer time wisely.'

Putting down the mask, Garen slowly deliberated on what Black Sethe has said, referring back to his memories of his dream worlds. Evidently, his dream world was sometimes constructed based on his own desires and imaginations, or from external influences. However, there were times that the dream world managed to reflect reality. What an interesting discovery.

'Over the next few nights, I'll be expending my energy to guide you in your dream world, I've already had quite a bit of time to recuperate, I should have enough strength now,' Black Sethe said.

"Why have you suddenly become so kind?" Garen was suddenly suspicious.

Black Sethe paused for a long time at this question, sitting in silence for a while.

"It's fine if you don't want to tell me," Garen broke the silence.

'There's no point in hiding it,' Black Sethe laughed, 'I am about to disappear.'

Hearing this, Garen was completely stunned. As time passed, he had completely gotten used to Black Sethe's guidance, both as a teacher an as a friend. Now, he completely trusted that Black Sethe was helping him without any selfish intentions.

After a moment of silence, Garen asked.

"Is it because of the Slaughtering Hand?"

'Yes,' Black Sethe calmly answered, 'Since the Slaughtering Demon Technique was abandoned, I'm being overwritten by the new secret techniques,' He laughed bitterly, 'I live within the Slaughtering Hand Secret Technique, I am nothing but a past memory of the Bloody King, I do not have any means of surviving independently.'

"Is there a solution?" Garen asked.

What answered him was a long silence.

Garen didn't say anything, he just placed the mask back into the hidden compartment and walked out of the secret room.

Maybe it was because of Black Sethe's company that he no longer feels lonely as he did before. To be honest, he didn't want Black Sethe to leave at all.

"If I continue to train the Slaughtering Hand would that guarantee that your existence?" Garen softly asked.

'You're willing to continue training?' Black Sethe instantly replied in a joyous tone.

"If I just maintain it at the first level, it's a simple task," Garen said calmly.

'I knew that playing the sympathy card would work! Hahaha!' Black Sethe laughed proudly.

"On second thought, continuing training seems so troublesome… I should just give up on it…" Garen playfully said.

"Don't!! Just name a price! I'll do whatever I can to fulfill it for you! When have I ever cut you short, believe me!" Black Sethe shouted in panic.

The two continued to banter, as Garen walked through the corridor, heading towards the reading room.

In a pitch black space.

Black Sethe was floating in the center of the space, his red eyes glowing. Only he knew that the moment the Slaughtering Hand was changed, it had destroyed the fundamental pillar of his existence. Even if Garen continued to train, there wouldn't be any use.

He silently stared at his increasingly transparent body, and couldn't help but let out a bitter smile.

Maybe if I just silently disappeared without a word, that would just be my fate as a memory…

To begin with, he shouldn't have asked for so much.

Maybe one day, if he calls me and I do not respond, he would remember my existence as a memory…

"Black Sethe, can you see it, they seem to be some sort of numbering system." Garen was already at his desks, drawing out the symbols he saw earlier.

Ignoring his own thoughts, Black Sethe moved behind Garen in the form of black gas and looked at the symbols on the table.

'It does look like some kind of numbering system,' He carefully observed each symbol on the table, 'We don't have enough clues yet, so it's hard for us to come up with any solution at this moment. Are there any other clues from the Men in Black?"

"If we gather even more stuff, maybe we can get even more clues," Garen frowned.

'There's another way. You can enter the dream world and learn the technique of using Visions. Maybe then you might be able to see a piece of the masks history,' Black Sethe suggested.

"History?"

'Yes. On a lot of items, there are traces that we cannot perceive normally using our five senses. Just like a painting on a piece of paper, although we can see it with our eyes, we are unable to hear it with our ears. There may be traces of these kinds of things that require a specific sense to perceive, and it most likely exists in the dream world. Hence, we might be able to get more clues if we go to the dream world,' Black Sethe tried to explain it in simpler terms.

"So how are we going to do this?" Garen asked.

'After you enter the dream world, you need to first differentiate the illusions from the reflections and refractions of reality. This is the first step, but take it slow.'

Garen thought back to the dream world technique he'd learned so far.

Black Sethe's dream world technique undoubtedly gave him a lot of help; from being unable to move at all at the start until now, where he could move freely, it was almost as though he'd reached a higher level.

He carefully sorted out the contents of the technique once more.

Focus your mind. In the dream world, it was very easy to be disoriented or distracted. The method was to find a point to concentrate on, for example, a body part.

You could not look for something based on the surroundings of the dream world. Since a large portion of the dream world was based on illusions, many parts of the dream world were constructed from the blurry memories dredged from the human body. If you paid too much attention to the details, it would cause the dream world to be broken. If certain details weren't in your memory, if you paid too much attention to a missing detail, it would cause your attention to be forcefully shifted and the dream world would be destroyed.

After you can guarantee your complete focus, you can start to use the corner of your eyes to rapidly observe the surroundings in the dream world. You cannot stop at any point, as if you do, you will start to shift your focus, breaking the dream world.

The entire dream world is essentially a very badly made illusion, so there will be many imperfections. Once you find these imperfections, you will start to distrust the reality of everything you see in the dream world, causing you to be disillusioned, destroying the dream world.

After you are able to observe the dream world, you would need to find the entrance, or rather the starting point to your own dream world, by realizing that you are dreaming. If you are able to feel when you have entered a dream, it would be even better. That was in preparation for the next step. Due to the high level of focus, this would produce a weirdly clear consciousness, so this process would be much simpler. However, if you started directly at this step, you would have a low chance of success, as you would easily lose your focus and attention without preparation.

'Now what you need to do is the 4th step,' Black Sethe guided him in a low tone, 'From this step onwards, if you succeed, only can you truly master the art of a void pursuer.' he explained, 'The other people of Endor and I viewed dreams as a process of inserting our consciousness into our souls, slowly going deeper and exploring the soul's deepest parts. This allowed us to access our true souls, then imprint all our memories onto it. That is the soul's most microscopic particles, the same particles that cannot be destroyed or disintegrated.'

"I understood what you meant, the dream world is essentially the process of us putting our consciousness into our souls. The deeper we get, the more we find out about our soul's hidden potentials. So the dream world is, in actuality, technically a level of the soul," Garen nodded in acknowledgment.

'Yes. You need to start from the starting point of your dream world, walk around intricately observing every corresponding detail around you, strengthening the dream world in the process. This will decrease the possibility of disillusionment, allowing you to remain in the dream world for a longer time.'

Chapter 687: Dragged in 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Practicing a technique based on dreaming was a troublesome task, as it wasn't something you could master in one try.

Garen cautiously asked about the details regarding the dream world technique, and also the methods for resolving the possible issues and problems he might face. If he managed to master the vision technique, according to Black Sethe, it would have some obvious effects on him in various aspects. After achieving Vision, he would be able to drastically increase his field of view, allowing him to see many things that normal people were unable to see.

He kept the symbols he'd drawn neatly in the desk drawer and locked them up.

'Let's try it out in the first dream world today,' Black Sethe advised.

Garen nodded as he made his way towards his bedroom. After greeting his maid, he went straight to the bathroom for a cold shower. After refreshing his body, he went straight to his bed and lay down, trying his best to relax his body.

Lying face up on the bed, he put on his noise canceling ear muffs. Staring up at the checkered black and white ceiling, he slowly closed his eyes, breathing slowly.

As his consciousness started to blur, he was also getting more and more sleepy.

The key to entering the dream world was to be in a comfortable position. You simply could not move your body or exert any strength.

After a short while, Garen started to feel his body getting lighter as if the bed itself was starting to float, and it entered a narrow black tube. It felt like he was being compressed by the strong force.

He tried looking around, but all he could see was that he was encased in a weird, brownish, gooey substance, almost as if he was completely immobilized by mud. However, there seemed to be none on his body.

This strange tube seemed to be alive, making small movements every few moments. He could vaguely hear a lot of different sounds; sounds of humans, cars, airplanes, even insects. It was a chaotic jumble of different noises.

After a long time, Garen finally saw the light at the end and his entire body suddenly flew out of the tube, entering a small dark room that looked similar to his actual bedroom.

Black wallpaper, black wall lamp, black and white checkered sofa, black and white checkered bed frame, a mini bar counter, and a giant 92-inch flat screen television on the wall.

As Garen landed in the bedroom, he turned around. What was behind him was a room door left ajar that was slowly closing. Through the shrinking gap, he saw a dark abyss.

Click.

The door was closed.

'That is the door of your heart. Since it was closed, it means that your dream world is also closed. This is a psychological defense mechanism for defending against invisible creatures, but don't rely too much on it,' Black Sethe's voice rang in Garen's ear, but it felt as if it was played through a voice changer, with the voice constantly changing like a melody. Sometimes he sounded sharp, sometimes he sounded raspy, with his pitch constantly going up and down, it sounded very surreal.

'This place is your bedroom, or at least the bedroom in your dreams. Pay attention to the details in this area, we'll set this point as the rally point for today's training,' Black Sethe continued.

Garen nodded. He could clearly feel that he was in a dream, as his body wasn't as agile as it was in the real world and his consciousness was also a bit fuzzy. The surroundings in his vision were very blurry, almost as if they were constantly changing.

'Let's start by strengthening your dream world. Try to focus your sightline, start to focus on every detail of the areas nearest to you, but do not focus on something for more than two breaths. Otherwise, you'll start to lose focus, causing the dream world to change,' Black Sethe said softly.

Garen started looking around his surroundings and decided to start with the small bookcase right next to him.

The bookcase was filled with books, from books on philosophy to history, geography to science, computers to art, there's a book of almost every genre on the shelves. However, they were just put there for display purposes; in reality, Garen hadn't read any of them before.

He started from left to right, scanning through the bookcase, imprinting the rows of black leather books into his mind.

'Find the things in your dream that are illogical, those are distractions that you should remove,' Black Sethe reminded him.

Keeping that in mind, Garen continued.

History of the Earth… Andrew's Growl… Astronomy and the Sky… The Life of Edolas…

One book after another passed in and out of Garen's sightline.

Suddenly, a book's title stood out.

"Reinhardt placed an apple on…" the cover of this book was very strange. The name etched on the edge looked as if they were ripples on water, and couldn't be read clearly. The words after "on" were blurred, almost as if it was constantly changing.

Garen moved his hand over to grab the book, placing it on his palm. It turns out that it wasn't a book at all; flipping it over, it was a deviled egg plate.

What a joke! Why would a plate be placed in a bookcase? It was simply illogical.

Garen now grabbed this plate with both hands, attempting to snap it.

At that instant, the plate softened and transformed into some sort of living slime that escaped from his grasp. It somehow burrowed its way through the wall on the right and disappeared. The wall now had a crack that wasn't there at the start.

'Don't mind it. That is something from some unknown place. When in a dream world, you may encounter various creatures from other worlds or dimensions. It's very difficult to capture them, but you'll get used to them soon,' Black Sethe softly said, 'Your mission now is to remove the distraction factors from your dream world.'

Garen felt somewhat amused.

His current consciousness level was slightly blurrier than in real life, and it was also the case during his battle with Nadia. It was largely affected by external factors such as suppressed rationality and reason.

Continuing to look through the bookcase, he found nothing of interest.

He then moved on to the black cloth sofa that had a tiger-like furry texture and pattern, which seemed to be quite fluffy.

Garen attempted to sit on it, slowly pressing his weight onto it.

Hyaaaaa~~~~

The sofa let out a strange moan, almost as if it was alive.

"I don't think sofas are supposed to make sounds like that,' Black Sethe said.

Garen nodded in agreement.

The shadow of the sofa suddenly lunged forward, speeding directly towards the room door. Almost like a stream of black water, it rapidly seeped through the gap at the bottom of the door, disappearing without a trace.

'That was another guest from another galaxy, these guests can also be pretty useful. If you want to go visit another galaxy or enter a world in another dimension or time, they can act as great tour guides. All you need to do is grab on to their tails.'

"We can go to other galaxies with them?" Garen started to take interest in the topic.

'Yes, though I need to mention that if you do that you'll have to live in the dream world forever. If you blindly follow these tour guides away from your original location, you will be easily lost in space-time or in a different dimension, unable to find your way back. Then, you'll have to live the rest of your life there, or maybe in the eternal emptiness of another galaxy, or maybe some rip in space-time between galaxies, staying there forever until your soul dies out.'

"Then why are they in my dream world?" Garen sat on another sofa.

'No idea, these visitors all have their various goals, but one thing's for sure, their intentions are never good,' Black Sethe answered.

"Alright," Garen stopped asking questions.

After checking the sofas, he started exploring the smart television mounted on the wall.

He tried to turn on the television, but nothing happened. There seemed to be blue sparks flying about at the sockets.

He started touching the display of the television which looked smooth, but when he touched it, it felt strangely bumpy and uneven. Other than that, it seemed to be normal.

Garen then moved his focus over to the television frame. Eerily, the frame was actually a thin yellow snake. The snake was even still alive, flicking its red forked tongue at Garen while hissing.

Hiss!

The snake suddenly lunged towards Garen, flying towards his face.

In a state of panic, Garen reflexively reached forward to grab the snake.

'Don't touch it!!' Black Sethe shouted.

However, it was too late; Garen had already grabbed on to the snake tightly. In a blink of an eye, he started to feel that everything around him was becoming blurry as if someone had just flashed a bright white light at his eyes. He also felt like he was moving at high speeds through something.

After an unknown amount of time, he honestly did not know whether a long time has passed or if it was just a brief moment.

He suddenly noticed that in front of him was a huge, pitch-black vortex, almost like a whirlpool, slowly spinning. At the center of it was an endless abyss of darkness. He was being dragged directly towards the vortex by a strong force.

The vortex occupied almost the entirety of his field of vision, almost making it feel like it had the size of the solar system or even the Milky Way. The enormity of the vortex made him freeze in his tracks. A strange feeling of attraction was luring him towards the vortex, almost making him have the urge to just move directly into the vortex.

'Wake up!!'

A sudden sharp noise came from behind him.

Garen furiously shook his head, feeling a strong pulling force from his back, dragging him away from the vortex.

Whoosh!!!

Garen forced his eyes open. He was still lying on his bed, though his whole body was sore as if he'd just undergone an intensive exercise routine. It completely didn't feel like he had just woken from his sleep.

'You were almost dragged into an unknown universe by a creature from another dimension,' Black Sethe's voice groaned from beside his ear.

"If I really went into that vortex, what would have happened?" Garen asked as he stood up and wiped the sweat off his face.

'Vortex? You saw a vortex?' Black Sethe seemed to not know what Garen saw in the dream world, 'I have no idea, you'll probably start seeing the scenery from other dimensions or universes I guess,' Black Sethe answered after a brief pause.

'This kind of thing will happen quite often, so please be more cautious. In the dream world, some of these things can be very cunning, so you shouldn't believe everything they say, but you shouldn't completely ignore it either. You have to be able to distinguish the truth from the lies yourself. As for entering another dimension or universe, it's a very dangerous thing especially for you. Your soul with its space-time attributes is these visitors' favorite prey, so they will do whatever it takes to lure you into their universe.'

"I felt a strange sort of attraction towards that vortex just now," Garen frowned.

'That is for sure, as you enter another dimension or universe, it causes certain benefits for your soul's consciousness. A trip to another universe while being conscious is not something you can do no matter how powerful you are, though it would definitely be a precious experience. However, it is a one-way road; once you enter, it's highly likely that you'll become lost in it forever, never being able to return.'

"What would happen then?"

'To put it simply, you'll be put in a vegetative state. Your body will still be alive, but it will no longer have a consciousness.'

Chapter 688: Dragged In 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Previously, Black Sethe's words had made Garen feel disconnected from the dream realm, but this had worsened his impression of it. He now looked at it as though it was some sort of dangerous environment.

'To normal people, the dream realm is indeed nothing dangerous because they only wander through the realm while barely conscious, and this would not be able to attract the interest of other dimensional galaxy creatures. However, if the current you were to dive deep into it, the focus and conscious effort that you put in will be much greater than any ordinary person's, and such an obvious prey will be just as distinguishable as a campfire in complete darkness.'

"I'm feeling very lethargic now."

'Indeed, that's because your consciousness has followed the snake for a very long distance. Take a rest, that will be it for today. You'll need more training after this, as the Vision technique can only be trained when you have reached the depths of the second level of the dream realm. The current you can't even reach the point of actualizing the first level,' Black Sethe's voice slowly softened, he too seemed to be very fatigued.

After half a month.

America Natiya State.

On a highway running through barren yellow plains, there was a white car that was slowing down on the left shoulder of the white highway, which then came to a halt in front of a gas station.

The door opened and was then slammed shut.

A young, beautiful lady with a tall physique exited the vehicle.

The lady was wearing sunglasses, tight purple jeans, and a white tee-shirt. She turned around and murmured to another beautiful lady in the car before she made large, purposeful strides towards the gas station.

The sun blazed down upon the road as dazzling sunbeams blinded all of its travelers. As the heat from the sweltering road radiated in waves, some people would be sweating buckets. Strangely, the lady who had exited the car was not visibly sweating at all.

"What month is it, for it to be this hot..."

The teenage girl in the car was indeed Arisa, who had left Grano with her sister. She was currently dressed in a thin shirt matched with light blue jean shorts, and her outfit accentuated her slender, long legs. One of her ears was fitted with an earpiece, which was playing some music.

"This is the southernmost region, it's normal for it to be hotter than other regions, plus the weather forecast has also predicted that tonight's temperature will dip into the negatives. The difference in temperature will only grow further apart," there were two more people in the car, and the one who had just spoken was a middle-aged man wearing summer beach-pants who was dozing off in the back seat.

The other person was a lady dressed in white office attire. She had long, blonde hair tied into a neat braid, and coupled with her cold stare, she gave off a stern, sharp vibe. Both of them didn't look like they were beyond thirty or forty years old.

The lady glanced at the man.

"My last trip to Natiya State was sixty years ago and back then, the temperature differences weren't this bad. This is probably caused by the recent pollution and vegetation issues."

Arisa spoke softly from the side, "Sixty years… Lord, you Blood Breeds really do make us envious. Despite the decades you've lived through, you don't look a day older."

The lady looked at Arisa and gave her a warm smile.

"You lot aren't bad either; your sister has already hit the top-tiered standards among humans, and she's almost comparable to those specialist mercenaries. To be able to do this as a human is already very impressive. After all, one's talents are limited."

"Of course, my sister is really strong!" Arisa stuck out her tongue and gave out a prideful grin, "Mr. Pritto, how far are we from Lars?"

The man closed his eyes as though he was sensing something, and reopened his eyes after a moment.

"There aren't any traces of him nearby, meaning that he should be more than thirty kilometers away from us. We can rest easy for now."

"It's too bad, I'm sure we would have been much safer if we'd remained in Grano," after Pritto had met with the Arisa siblings, he had been pulled into the two Blood Breed forces' war, though he always felt that they did the sisters wrong. Hence, during the chance opportunity where he was pressured to fall out with Lars, they had to leave Grano and rush towards the Light Party's main camp in Natiya State.

As the conflict worsened, the Secret Party's advantage was strengthened, and they swarmed the Light Party strongholds en masse. Though it was unclear how they'd acquired such a tremendous number of members,the Light Party's forces in Grano's Faya State have also begun retreating diagonally towards the southernmost parts of America, giving up Central America entirely to the Blood Breeds of the Secret Party.

As for the leader of Light Party who bore high hopes, the first Death Apostle Ashen Castine, she had remained silent without any action or reaction.

Of course, in the eyes of the regular people, the two parties' conflict appeared to be a conflict of interests between the shadow forces of two large organizations. Or perhaps it was a conflict between two extremely-wealthy organizations and was not related to any civilian.

That was indeed the case, no matter if it was the Secret Party or Light Party, they both adhered to the rule of not overexposing the Blood Breeds, and thus anything that happened would be covered up with a layer of rationalization.

On the other hand, the witches relied on the strength of their many alliances and had announced their neutral stand on this matter. In fact, they were also considered to be a large-scale organization as they were led by the Death Apostle, Lion Mother, hence even the Secret Party would not offend them too recklessly.

As the Light Party retreated, Grano lost its usual security, and so the Arisa sisters also chose to leave Grano so that they wouldn't affect other civilians. Little did they know, Raffaele was the leader of the witches. Raffaele could not insist on protecting them due to pressure from the Secret Party, and as the leader, she could not disobey Lion Mother's decree or the conflict with the Blood Breed's Secret Party would result in multiple casualties among their subordinates, as clearly indicated by her grandmother and other elders.

Hence, leaving Grano has become the sisters' only choice. After consecutively killing multiple vampires and low-level Blood Breeds from Secret Party, Isaros had been permanently recorded on the Secret Party's hit list. For her sister's safety, she had no choice but to flee Grano alongside Pritto and the other Scarlet Moon Blood Breeds.

"It's too bad…. If only…" Arisa heaved a long sigh and stared out the window. Suddenly, she seemed to have startled, as though she saw something unexpected.

"Vivien?! Why is she here!!" Arisa shouted, and immediately flung open the door and ran towards her.

In the gas station, there were two other cars that had stopped for refueling, and there was a small crowd of young teens standing by the side. They seemed to be on a trip, and some of them giggled as they chattered on. Among them, there was Little Vivien from Uncle Thomas' family!!

"Vivien?" Pritto and the young Blood Breed woman didn't react in time, but judging from Arisa's expression, it was obviously someone she knew.

Suddenly, Pritto took a closer look.

"Oh no! That's Lars' men!!"

"Such coincidence?!?" the female Blood Breed was also shocked.

"Get them back on the car!! Quick!!" Pritto closed his eyes to take a hold of the enemies' locations.

Meanwhile, in the gas station, Isaros had also noticed that Vivien was with other people by their cars, as well as her younger sister Arisa running over.

Suddenly a sharp scream was heard from the car's direction.

"Be careful!!!" it was the female Blood Breed's voice.

Isaros could see streaks of black shadows rushing towards her with a glance from the corner of her eyes, as well as a few vacant cars rushing towards the cars in the kiosk.

Bam Bam Bam!!!

Amidst loud screaming, Vivien and her classmates were stunned.

The cars collided with each other, causing a loud collision and in that instant, a few cars were mushed and tangled with one another. The deformed lump of several cars was heading straight towards their group.

Vivien stood there, trembling in terror as she stared at those cars that came straight towards them. Her head had gone completely blank, and although she was trying her best to get her body to move, an overwhelming horror had completely stunned her.

She was just a girl who'd gone on a trip with her friends after her examinations, how could such a thing happen suddenly?

"Kill the witnesses!" called a cold, cruel man.

At this time, Vivien suddenly felt pain on her body; a shadow had suddenly tackled her to the ground from the right, and she'd rolled some distance away.

The immense amount of friction between the tires and the road created a loud screech, and when coupled with the shrieks of brakes, several black tire marks were burnt into the ground. It brushed by the two people and rammed straight into a pole.

Bam!!

The strong crash sent shivers down Vivien's spine. Nothing actually crossed her mind, but she could feel that she was being enveloped by a soft body, and was slowly helped up after a while.

"Dodge it!!" a familiar voice was heard from her side, Vivien felt that she was tugged towards the right with force and began running.

She then saw Elder Sister Isaros dashing towards her with a stunning speed before engaging two black uniformed men in combat. With the loud smack of hands, the two black uniform men were deftly punched. The duo let out a dissatisfied moan and rushed towards Vivien abruptly.

"Run!" it was Arisa's voice.

Vivien's head was completely blank as she was tugged along by Arisa and ran with all her might. The two uniformed men were quickly blocked by other people and no longer chased them.

After running for some time, the two of them reached the white car, hastily clambered in and slammed the door shut loudly before a foreign-looking, beautiful lady in the driver's seat started the car.

Soon, the sounds of doors opening and closing happened behind her and two other persons entered. One of them was Elder Sister Isaros whom she was familiar with. The other man, on the other hand, was a stranger in a beach attire. Both of them had flecks of blood on them.

"Go!!"

"Tommy!! Tommy and the rest were still there!!" Vivien had finally reacted; she screamed but she was being held firmly by Arisa.

Vivien looked back, but she could only see the gas station going up in flames as a strong explosion discharged. The crimson-red flames and black smoke engulfed everything in its path, whether human or vehicle. The cars that have been approaching the gas station all immediately braked, which soon caused a traffic pileup.

The car continued forward and had sped up even more while riding on the impact of the explosion.

"This… What actually… happened?" Vivien suddenly felt like the entire world had become completely foreign to her. Beside her was Arisa who was still holding onto her hands tightly.

"It's alright, it's alright, I'm here, Elder Sister's here… things will be fine…. It will be fine…" she could hear Arisa murmuring softly.

"Why the hell did you bring her along? Dump her by the roadside somewhere!" the foreign lady screamed suddenly, but her voice sounded very soft as compared to the grumbling explosion.

"She is my friend!" Arisa screamed back.

"You are dragging her into this!!" the lady seemed to be very frustrated, bringing one non-combatant was already a hassle, now there was another one, did they not want to live anymore?!

"Lars is in pursuit of us, not only him, there are two more Blood Breeds with levels…" a deep male's voice could be heard from the passenger's' seat.

"I could barely take on one," Isaros spoke softly. In fact, as of now, she was the weakest link among the combatant trio; against the pure Blood Breeds, her capabilities were obviously insufficient.

"Then what about her?" The driver looked at Vivien who was sitting in the passenger seat.

Isaros went quiet for a while.

"I will contact her brother to pick her up, she will follow us for the time being."

The driver couldn't help but grumble.

Chapter 689: Pursue and Attack 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Ca-clack!!

The glass cup in his hand suddenly had multiple cracks in it.

Garen put down the glass in his hand and calmly lifted his head to look at his subordinates who were reporting to him.

His three subordinates were all muscular, strong and looked vicious but right now, they were all shivering and dripping with cold sweat as they bowed in front of him without the courage to stand straight.

"Vivien… was ambushed?" Garen showed a calm expression, but the calmer he looked, the more people felt that Garen was suppressing his anger internally.

One of his subordinates' scalp had gone numb. He felt as though Garen's gaze was gliding across his scalp like a sharp knife, which was painful in a sense.

"According to our intel, she was ambushed by a mysterious man at a gas station in Natiya State, and was subsequently rescued by another group of people, her current location is unknown."

He quickly yet softly reported the issue to Garen as he endured the pain.

Garen nodded

"You may leave now."

The three subordinates felt as though they obtained amnesty as they quickly turned around to leave the room. They closed the door of their car, and one could hear their sighs of relief from afar.

The room suddenly fell into silence.

Garen looked at the dishes presented before him, but even his favorite boiled snails in tomato soup were not attractive anymore.

As he pushed the plates away, he picked up the phone on the table to make a call.

The number was slightly long, and he put in a few prefix numbers before dialing the actual phone number.

Duu….

After a few ringing tones.

"Garen? Why are you free to give me a call?" an elderly, husky voice could be heard from the receiver of the phone.

"AG, how did the plan go on your side?" Garen lightly tapped the table rhythmically, producing some soft tapping sounds. These sound waves dispersed across the room, and as some of those minute soundwaves bounced back, he could ascertain and sense if there were any unwanted things listening in on him.

"I knew it," AG laughed, "Blood Breeds crossed you? You wouldn't have proactively contacted us if things didn't affect you."

"You know me quite well, it seems," Garen's face had an odd smile, "It is as you said, things revolving the Blood Breed didn't concern me previously as I stay in the northern region of America and was largely unaffected, so naturally, I didn't need to take an active stance with you. But…"

"But now things are different?"

"Indeed, things are different now," Garen confirmed.

His original plans for a trip to Memphis were also affected due to this news. After receiving the news on the internal conflict among the Blood Breeds, he needed to re-evaluate the plans again.

"What do you plan to do? We would welcome you with open arms if you decided to join us," AG chuckled.

Garen pondered.

His original main focus had been to look for the masks and settle Nadia's problems first, as those imitation masks could only provide a short-term suppression. Then, he would use this time to write his very own Demonic Book to try to form a second soul seed. With regards to Blood breeds, witches, and the likes, their actions didn't concern him as long as they did not affect him, and he would assume them to be non-existent.

"The reason why the northern region that you're in has never been invaded by any Blood Breed is that it was the holy site where the witches negotiated with the Blood Breeds, and also the place where Lion Mother rests," AG explained briefly through the phone, "But such peace is not permanent; following the need to expand, both forces may not care that much after all."

Garen understood this point, as the book AG gave him before had mentioned similar contents. Through that book, he could conduct academic discussions and communications with AG in absolute secrecy, and it had also given him a much more in-depth understanding of the Blood Breeds.

However, soon after, AG had repeatedly invited him to participate in the planning of assaults against the Blood Breeds, which were all rejected by Garen. He was already occupied with the issues revolving the Nine-Headed Dragon King Nadia, as well as the training of his own dream realm techniques.

"Now, Secret Party is in an advantageous position, if you would like to join the fray, now would still be considered a good time. We can discuss more in the book for detailed plans."

"Alright."

Garen hung up the phone and stayed silent for a while before he stood up and walked towards the bookshelf. He crouched and pulled a small black hardcover book from the lowest row of books.

As he gently flipped through the pages, there was nothing but blank tallow pages.

'Light Party Leader Ashen Castine has been bound by the Secret Party leaders, another Death Apostle-level Secret Party member is currently pursuing Scarlet Moon, we will need to pay close attention to two of the strongest people among the remaining forces,' AG's words appeared on the book's page, 'One would be the Crimson Spear, and the other would be the Radiant Pond. These two people are both the strongest Blood Breeds under the Death Apostles while being a mastermind of the Secret Party and a Light Party Sect mastermind respectively.'

'I don't want to know such useless intel,' Garen interrupted him, 'Help me find out this thing, what forces were the ones who ambushed my sister?'

'I'm afraid I can't help you with this,' AG rejected his request, 'In America, my influences aren't any stronger than yours. Plus, you should be getting more news on this soon. Believe me, very soon….'

'Is this a hint from you?' Garen distrusted this kind of superstitious prophecies.

Ding… Ding…

Suddenly, the phone on his table began ringing. The monotonous yet serene bell peals were coupled with the vibration of the phone, and the phone kept moving with every vibration.

The screen flashed and it showed an incoming call from Isaros.

Garen squinted his eyes and accepted the call with the press of a button.

"Hello?" he tried to sound as gentle as possible.

"Is this Garen? I'm Isaros."

***************

In Natiya State, far away.

At the midsection of a road in the middle of some deserted area, a white car was stopped on the left side of the road. With the car doors flung open, Isaros was standing by the car while her hair was tousled by the wind. As the sun shone upon her face, a slight sheen was reflected off her face.

Isaros was holding her phone as she spoke to Garen.

Meanwhile, Vivien was staring blankly at her phone like a bedraggled cat, with a gaze revealing an obvious yearning for a conversation with her brother.

Arisa was still hugging her arm, as she had no clue what the best course of action would be either.

The two Blood Breeds, Pritto and the lady, were sitting in the front seats.

The two of them were observing Isaros as she made the call, and Pritto was forcing a smile while the lady blatantly looked impatient.

"Garen wants us to change directions and send his sister in the direction of Saint Francs," Isaros suddenly put down the phone, and looked towards the Blood Breed duo with a frown.

"why don't he just go and die!?" without waiting for Pritto's response, the Blood Breed lady just cussed without holding back. "What are we, her nanny? Should we even need to fucking escort his sister to Saint Francs? Has his brain rusted through?"

"Don't you dare talk about my brother like that!" Vivien couldn't help but shout back.

"Your brother is an idiot!!" the female blood breed seemed to have passed an anger threshold and was shouting in fury.

Vivien was so angry that her cheeks were ruddy and she stared at the woman with watery eyes. Her little mouth was open but yet she didn't know how to refute, so she could only shiver in anger.

"The backup that we were waiting for still hasn't arrived, perhaps this is a choice. Using people's influence to flee the Secret Party," Pritto tried to calm the situation on both sides.

"Three low-level Blood Breeds, hundreds of vampires, do you think we can rely on regular humans' powers to flee their pursuit? Stop joking!" the female Blood Breed said as though she heard a really funny joke.

Isaros was speechless, only slightly shook her head, and then continued listening to the phone.

"His people will be here within half an hour."

"For what? To die?" the apoplectic lady snorted.

"Okay, stop talking Kaya!" Pritto immediately held her shoulders to comfort her.

Isaros, on the other hand, was confident in Garen.

To be able to kill vampires and injure Lars with the Silent Killing Technique was all thanks to Garen's teaching. In her eyes, Garen was a mysterious yet strong, weird martial artist. She could say he was half her teacher.

"In any case, we needed to stay here until evening. It's okay, it's just half an hour."

"That's good too, we could dump these burdens on his people and their life and death will no longer be of our concern," the lady Blood Breed Kaya conceded.

"Mind your words!" Isaros couldn't help but shout, "My sister is not a burden."

"Words? What words? You're a burden too, and you dare talk back to us?" Kaya had long been dissatisfied with Pritto's trust in them.

"You!?" Isaros couldn't stand this crazy b*tch's nonstop barking any longer.

"What? Wanna pick a fight?" Kaya was out of the car in an instant.

"Enough! Stand down!!" Pritto finally got angry and shouted. The cheerful guy had finally snapped, and both Kaya and Isaros didn't dare to retort after that instance.

Isaros didn't understand either. Kaya always seemed to be a rational person, why was she raging at everyone she saw?

In that instant, everyone was stunned by Pritto's words and were speechless.

Kaya snorted before she returned to the car.

Isaros' chest kept heaving in fury.

"Arisa, we'll head over to Brother Garen's place once he comes."

"Sure." Arisa nodded; she'd long despised being with Kaya. This lady Blood Breed was hot-tempered and completely despised her and her sister. The arguments have not happened only once or twice these days.

"Ugh…" Pritto couldn't help but sigh, and everyone didn't know what to say.

"Alright, don't be so angry, Kaya's temper is a bit more short-fused, but she's still a kind person. The people who're picking them up will be her uncle, so let's not make things too awkward."

"Did you think I was joking?" Isaros gave him an odd look, "I was seriously considering to go to Vivien's brother's place. My martial arts were partially taught by him, and he definitely has a plan."

Things have turned out this way and a joke had evolved into a fight. If they were indeed going to the Blood Breed's area of influence, even Kaya's territory, then wouldn't she become Kaya's puppet, to be played any way she desired?

"You're not joking?" Pritto finally began speaking to Isaros seriously.

"Of course."

Chapter 690: Pursue and Attack 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Jii!!

Fresh blood spilled out from a person's neck, spraying over several meters away like a miniature geyser.

In the wide plains, a red shadow descended from the sky swiftly and landed upon the grasslands, before it elegantly flicked off the blood on the nails.

Puu!

The last person's corpse fell to the ground. On this area of the plains, there were many corpses from unknown forces, all dressed in armored attires while gripping onto weapons like firearms and daggers. The blood flowed across the soil and dyed the plains a rusted red.

Dahm was wearing a bright red cloak with red nail polish on his pointed nails, while his lips were dyed an odd blackish-purple shade. He was indulging in his great work at this moment.

"Marshal, Leader Mafa is just right ahead, our tracking signal showed that he's nearby," one baldy with a face full of scars reported while smiling, amongst a crowd of followers.

"What about the Four Hunting Generals?" Dahm licked the blood off his fingertips with some satisfaction.

"They're already heading over and should have engaged Mafa's people, but the leader Mafa is a bit hard to deal with, after all, he's from a thousand-year-old family. Some forms of retaliation power will definitely be in place," the bald giant continued answering warily.

"They are all either heavily injured or disabled, what's there to worry? Let's go too," Dahm said as he smiled and nodded.

After such a long period of preparation, their nemesis' ringleader, Mafa Organization, had finally been cornered in this rural area by a meticulous plan filled with step-by-step calculations, which had finally borne fruit. So long as he could kill off these opponents, the entire Mafa Organization would be effectively destroyed, and ready for him to take over.

Suddenly Dahm activated the smart earbud in his right ears to receive an incoming call.

"Bring all your personnel here immediately to this location," a stone-cold voice spoke over the phone without any hesitation which was transmitted over the earbud.

Dahm's smile then became a serious look.

"I'm actually conducting a very important act…"

"Do you not understand me?" that man's voice was cold and cruel, as though it was a suppressed volcano, as it abruptly interrupted him.

Dahm's face went red and he was speechless. After such a long period of planning, he could finally take down a strong rival at long last and expand his own financial empire, but now, in such a crucial moment, he wanted her to retreat?!!

"Yes….!" he was basically shivering all over as he pushed out this word from his throat.

Indeed, she dared not oppose that man, and she couldn't either. This was an absolute order filled with overwhelming power.

The waypoint has been sent to your chip, you have half an hour," clack, and the phone disconnected.

Bam!

The earbud exploded as a result of him tightly gripping it. The shattered pieces were scattered everywhere.

Everyone was frightened, and a few subordinates couldn't help but take a few steps backward, though their faces were still slashed by the shattered pieces. Even so, they did not dare to make a sound and could only endure the pain.

Dahm looked down and picked up a chip from amidst the debris and tossed it to a subordinate specializing in hacking.

"Everybody retreat, and head towards the location there."

The subordinates around her were stunned. This was such a pivotal moment, and if they could get through this, they could completely annihilate the Mafa Organization. The Four Hunting Generals have also formed an enclosure.

"But Marshal, the hunting generals are still…"

Pap!!

The person who spoke up had his skull gripped by Dahm.

Pap!!

His chest cavity was busted open in an instant and his flesh splattered all over the ground. As he screamed out loud, it slowly faded into silence.

Dahm kept his head lowered while putting down his hand. The subordinates around him were terrified to the point of shivering as they knew Dahm's violent, cruel personality had acted up again. Nobody dared to utter a word, not even exhaling loudly.

The baldy beside her already noticed that his irises had turned blood red.

" Heh… hehehe…" Dahm began laughing in a deep tone.

"Did you not hear me? Retreat, retreat!!" He shouted.

His face paled, as he had never seen Dahm ever being this angry. He didn't know who made him this angry, but the only thing he knew was that whoever stood in his path would definitely die.

**********

The rustling plains of the Central Region seemed like a yellowish-green carpet, which seemed wooly yet oddly flat.

In the middle of the plains was a ribbon-like white road with a grey base that extended over the hills and valleys of the plains.

Aside from the long-haul vacation buses that occasionally used that road, a convoy of pitch-black cars stood out and was very attention-grabbing. The convoy's car surfaces were as smooth as mirrors, among the cars in the lead of the convoy.

Among them, one of the cars was slightly larger in size than the rest.

The car's windows were lowered halfway and the warm breeze kept blowing into the car. Laars placed one arm over the car window as he savored the warm breeze greeting him.

"Ahh... The smell of the sun…"

He took a deep breath with a euphoric look.

"The Blood Breeds in the movies are all afraid of sunlight, you'll make people feel uneasy like this, Lars," Another young man with short red hair teased Lars casually while flipping through a book, giving him a side gaze.

"But that's just a movie," Lars laughed comfortably, "The blood Breeds in the movies were all handsome men who can charm a girl effortlessly, but in reality?"

"Speaking of which, how strong are the Scarlet Moon Blood Breeds that we're pursuing?" the red-haired man asked after he'd turned back to his book for a while.

"We have you, Kurt, why would we even need to be afraid of just a few low-level Blood Breeds?" Lars said as he laughed, "You're already close to the advancement of mid-level Blood Breed. As a member of our clan, the thirteen Blood Breeds that have advanced in the recent hundred years would definitely include a seat just for you."

"You're praising me too much," Kurt laughed in embarrassment.

"This isn't a praise," Lars shook his head, "My only concern now is that we'll lose the Scarlet Moons ahead of us."

"That's okay, I can sense that they're not far ahead…" Kurt shut his eyes and sensed something.

The internal conflict among the Blood Breeds was actually coming to an end, though only these pure Blood Breeds would have these sorts of insider news.

The leader of Light Party, Ashen Castine had been imprisoned thanks to the combined effort of the Secret Party Death Apostle leaders, in order for them to create a brand new world and to wipe out the last of Light Party survivors.

What was left was the conflict raised among the non-Death Apostles; the war had slowly been shifted towards them. At this time, different war prodigies excelling in the art of killing have been showcased, catching the eye of the Party.

Kurt was one of them.

Looking at Kurt who was engrossed in his book, Lars continued speaking in a regretful tone.

"To be honest, I have once tried to increase my own level too, intending to break free from the shackles of the Low-Level Blood Breed. Unfortunately, I couldn't break through the bottleneck no matter how hard I tried."

Kurt laughed.

"Actually, you only need two requirements to advance, one is to increase your own blood purity by merging with a purer Bloodline Core. As long as this step is successful, you'll be able to get some Bloodline essence of a higher level. With this small amount of essence, you can then feed the essence with large amounts of blood to let it grow to achieve the goal of advancement."

"Even though I made it sound easy, the actual heritage of the purifying process was actually hard to come by… The Gazing Eyes coupled with the clan's commonly used Secret Technique 'Fresh Blood Cultivation' was still too low of a level," Lars said regrettably, "If I had your Fifth Holy Technique.."

"I have sworn a Blood oath that I cannot share this family's secrets," Kurt shook his head while smiling, "You know the rules set by the Clan Elders."

Holy Technique was a mysterious technique heritage that allows the Blood Breeds to purify their own blood to achieve a higher level. Each clan's strongest heritage techniques were crowned with the title of a Holy Technique but in essence, only the six largest clans had Holy Techniques within the entire Blood Breed society, the Six Major Blood Breed Clans. Among them, all four Death Apostle Clans were in the ranks, while the two top-tiered Upper-Level Blood Breeds took the remaining two seats.

The top five clans were called the Five Staves of Power. Their influence and network were intertwined with every detail of the entire Blood Breed Society's multiple facets. Among the Five Staves of Power, there were three clans supporting the Light Party, while Secret Party only had the backing of one. However, now that there was another Death Apostle clan and one of the main supporters of the Light Party had betrayed them for unknown reasons, it caused the Scarlet Moon Death Apostle to flee with heavy injuries and go into hiding. As for the final clan, they weren't considered an actual thriving clan by the Staves of Power.

On that note, Lars' clan was indeed the Secret Party supporter among the Five Staves of Power.

That was how he could gather so many vampires under his wing, as well as the reason he managed to invite Kurt to pursue the Scarlet Moon Blood Breeds.

"Within the Scarlet Moon Clan's headquarters, the elders have claimed that the legendary Scarlet Moon Holy Technique is nowhere to be found. It's said that the Scarlet Moon Holy technique is a Holy Technique with the fastest speed of blood purification and an extremely high success rate. Perhaps this is why all the major powers are this enthusiastic about searching for and destroying the Scarlet Moon Blood Breeds."

Kurt smiled while reminding Lars on the actual mission objective.

To be honest, he was here for the Holy Techniques too. After all, Scarlet Moon Holy Technique was considered to be a Death Apostle grade Holy Technique, and in this situation where all three Death Apostles were unable to make time, they may very well lose the chance to look for another Holy Technique to advance.

"I have crossed fists with the few people ahead of us a few times, and according to my deduction, the Scarlet Moon Holy Technique would most likely be in the hands of the Blood Breed called Pritto," Lars spoke softly.

"Ohh?" Kurt's interest was piqued, "A holy technique is such an important thing, why would it be with a regular low-level Blood Breed? It's a tad unrealistic, no?"

"That's why Sir Scarlet Moon would place it on a low-level Blood Breed…" Lars smiled as he hinted.

Kurt's jaw dropped but he reacted soon after.

Indeed, when everybody was thinking of such contingency, they would definitely not place such documents on a low-level Blood Breed. If they put in a little effort on this Blood Breed and gave him some means to escape, that would make it very easy for this person to escape pursuit…..

If you think of it this way, then perhaps the Scarlet Moon Holy Technique could really be with Pritto…

Kurt, who was feeling disinterested in this matter was suddenly fuelled by passion. If he had the Scarlet Moon Holy Technique, perhaps he could break through the bottleneck in one go and safely advance to Middle-Level.

"How do we split the Holy Technique once it's in our hands?" Kurt looked at Lars.

"The three of us were the best of friends. The Holy Technique will definitely be shared, but it'd only be among the three of us, how's that?" Lars had obviously thought it through.

About the other vampires that were driving, they were all their direct descendants and were under their control, so they could rest easy. Plus, if them, as a higher level Blood Breed obtained greater advancements, it would trickle to these vampires as a stronger backbone support and would allow them to develop stronger network and influences, which would benefit everyone. Naturally, they wouldn't leak this secret out.

Chapter 691: Pursue and Attack 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Holy Techniques… They used to be such distant treasures," Kurt lamented, "If these were peaceful times, we would never have gotten the chance to come into contact with inheritances that belonged to the Holy Technique level. Nonetheless, an opportunity has arrived now."

"That's right," Lars laughed before his pupils darted towards the front suddenly.

"Oh… Farne has intercepted them up ahead."

"So soon? He always works in a timely manner," Kurt smiled as well, "I can sense that they've stopped. They've probably been surrounded so we should go there quickly. Make sure not to let the Holy Technique escape our grasp."

Both of them laughed quietly at the same time.

*****************

Clang… Clang… Clang… Clang…

Rhythmic peals could be heard ringing across the plains continuously.

It sounded as if metallic objects were crashing against each other, making melodious but somewhat shrill noises.

In front of the white sedan car at the side of the road, Isaros, Pritto, and the others dispersed before surrounding the car. Inside the car were Arisa and little Vivien. Arisa was still alright and kept a composed look on her face. However, Vivien's face was alarmed. She had to keep looking in all directions to reassure that someone was guarding the surrounding areas of the car in order for her to feel slightly at ease.

She was not a rebellious young girl and had never imagined that she would encounter a dangerous situation like this. She could only accept everything passively.

"There's nothing to worry about…" beside her, she could hear Arisa consoling her before the other girl held her hand gently.

"Mmhmm…" she grabbed Arisa's hand tightly.

"Uh-oh… I didn't think that I would encounter you guys here at an earlier time?"

A giddy male voice echoed from outside the car.

Accompanied by the rhythmic beats, ten pitch black human silhouettes seemed to have instantly teleported to the sides of the road by the white sedan.

The silhouettes scattered and dispersed. Each of them had slender bodies and most of them wore black veils that concealed their facial features. The person who led the group was the only one without a veil.

That man had a head of soft silver short hair and was dressed in silvery-white casual Western-style clothes. The rhythmic beats from earlier were the result of him clapping his palms together and making strange metallic noises. The skin on his hands was pale but made metallic noises when clapped against each other.

"I am Farne," the man stopped clapping and smiled while looking at the few people around the car. His gaze immediately shifted towards the two young girls inside the car before Isaros used the side of her body to block his line of sight at once.

"Farne? If you aren't hanging around Karst anymore, why did you run all the way here?" asked Pritto in a low voice.

Due to long periods of leisure and a good life, most of the Blood Breeds had already had lost the powerful fighting abilities that their ancestors once possessed. Other than their bodies' naturally strong physical qualities, all of their other killing abilities had deteriorated ages ago.

However, this was only the situation of the majority of the Blood Breeds. There was still a minority of Blood Breeds that had retained their bloodlust and cruel lifestyles, such as a group of them from the secret party. One of these Blood Breeds was Farne who was standing before them.

"I heard that the Scarlet Moon clan was here so I rushed over frantically. Fortunately, I was able to intercept them on the way here. If I had arrived slightly later, I would have only brushed past my desired Holy Technique, no?" Farne rubbed both of his palms together and made the strange metallic scraping noise again.

Suddenly, his gaze fell on Isaros who was the only human there.

"Oh? Apparently, there's a normal human here? Forgive me, you must be an elite human right? Someone who could participate in my Blood Breeds' internal matters could not be a normal person."

He snapped his fingers unconsciously while keenly noticing that Isaros was the weakest link among the trio.

Although she would not necessarily lose to the other Blood Breeds in terms of combat abilities, it was impossible for her regenerative abilities, vitality, and speed to match those of a true Blood Breed.

Isaros narrowed her gaze before staggering one step backward suddenly.

A scratching noise could be heard before an extremely thin black line instantly appeared beneath where she stood earlier. It was deeply embedded within the thick mud on the ground, leaving only a tiny circular hole there.

When she turned around, she noticed that both Pritto and Kaya's faces have changed like her own, while Farne had lifted his chin slightly and was glancing at the back of the white sedan.

No had noticed that an entourage of black cars had silently stopped at the roadside before groups of Black Uniform members got down. One characteristic that all of them possessed was that they were all donning black veils that exposed only a part of their pale and bloodless skin.

Two extremely eye-catching men walked out from the front of the entourage slowly.

One of them was their old acquaintance, Lars, who was dressed in his usual gentlemanly suit.

The other person was a youth with short red hair who was dressed like a regular refined official document writer. He held a book without a cover in his hand.

"We meet again…"

Pritto's heart fell. The thing that he was most worried about had happened. Their reinforcement troops had yet to arrive but their opponents were already present.

Kaya's uncle was probably still on his way but their three Blood Breed level opponents were already present. This would be dangerous…

Although they had three combat strengths as well which comprised of two ranked Blood Breeds and Isaros who was almost equivalent to a ranked Blood Breed, Isaros's regenerative abilities and physical endurance were far from an actual Blood Breed's.

Moreover, they had to protect the two fellows inside the car as well. This was the worst scenario!

Lars smiled while looking at the three people who were now encircled. His lips twitched slightly when he was about to give his orders. Suddenly, he wrinkled his brows before looking at the front of the road from the corner of his eyes.

Not just him, but the others glanced towards the road at the same time as well.

Another long entourage of sedans was traveling here at an even speed. The car that led the entourage stopped slowly. It was clear that this was their destination.

The car stopped and the door was opened before a slender leg in red leather boots stretched out and stepped on the ground.

"Hehehehe… Looks like I made it in time for a good show, huh…" a voice that was neither male nor female echoed from within the car.

Bang, bang bang!!

All of the car doors were opened and then closed after four men and women with various dispositions got down. There was a large crowd of fierce members behind them that carried various weapons like submachine guns and rifles. The hollow clicking sound of firearms being loaded could be heard from the group continuously.

A man in a red trench coat got down from the car and surveyed the entire area.

"I'm here to meet someone. The rest of you can do as you please."

Looks of extreme dissatisfaction and frenzied bloodlust could be seen on the faces of the people in the crowd. It seemed as though an important event had been interrupted.

"Humans?" the smile on Lars's face disappeared slowly, "There are so many humans here that it would be troublesome to kill all of them…"

"Are you going to do it or should I?" Kurt looked at Farne.

"Humans?" the man in the red trench coat was actually Dahm who had just rushed over. His acute hearing had caught that word. "Are you talking about us?" he glanced from left to right and noticed that the Four Hunting Generals beside him were smiling faintly.

A refined bespectacled man pushed his glasses to readjust them.

"They're underestimating us."

"Underestimating?" Dahm acted as if he had heard something hilarious. Instantly, his smile disappeared. "Looks like you've spoiled my act of goodwill!"

Whoosh!!

He disappeared from his initial position instantly. His body resembled a graceful water bird when he stepped on the ground gently before leaping into the sky with both of his arms outstretched like wings. He floated gingerly towards Farne who was nearby.

"In order to save time, could you I ask you to die please?" the corners of Dahm's mouth were curled and his bright red lipstick made him look abnormally ferocious.

"Are all of the humans so arrogant now?" Farne rubbed both of his hands together and made the metallic noise again. He raised his head towards the silhouette that was flying towards him and lifted his hands before punching his opponent head-on.

His fist and Dahm's finger made contact, but no strength could be felt.

Farne's face was somewhat shocked before he saw Dahm's red silhouette gracefully appear behind him a flash. His speed had increased greatly in a mere instant, achieving speeds that had blinded him slightly when he tried to keep up with his footsteps.

His heart froze.

"Be careful! This person is st… strange!"

Bang!!!

Before he could finish speaking, Farne's entire upper body exploded from the left side suddenly while blood gushed out like a fountain. Half of it splattered on Dahm's body and he closed his eyes as if he was drunk on happiness. He outstretched both of his arms as though he was a musician who was preparing to leave the stage after his performance.

The remnants of the smile on Kurt's face disappeared instantly.

Lars's pupils dilated as if he'd witnessed an unbelievable sight.

Most of the surrounding Vampires that were entangled in the conflict were also dazed before collapsing in large groups at the hands of Dahm, who had taken the opportunity to open fire and wipe them out.

Pritto looked towards Kaya with a strange expression on his face.

"Did your uncle hire him?"

The latter had a similarly shocked expression on her face before shaking her head slowly, "My uncle is still on his way…"

Both of the Blood Breeds glanced at Isaros from the corners of their eyes. However, they noticed that Isaros had a grave expression on her face as if she'd seen the red male figure do something impossible.

"Seize the opportunity to leave." Pritto could feel Kaya writing something on his palm. The area where they'd been surrounded earlier had now become the safest place amidst the chaos.

Pritto nodded faintly and drew himself closer to Isaros quietly. On the other side, Isaros could sense movements as well and understood their plans after a moment of thinking. She moved closer towards the car door as they'd secretly agreed upon.

"That strange person may be a first-rate elite-level human, but it is impossible for him to be a worthy opponent of three ranked Blood Breeds. We can leave quickly while they're clashing with each other." Kaya whispered while moving towards the car door quietly. "My uncle will come to our aid soon."

"I'm very sorry but you are not allowed to go anywhere."

Suddenly, a gentle male voice interrupted her actions.

Both Pritto and Kaya felt their heads turn numb. Neither of them had sensed that someone was behind them. Both of them turned their heads abruptly before realizing that the bespectacled man in white was standing behind a few people. They were completely unaware of the moment he'd approached them.

"I seem to have heard some extremely terrible things earlier…" the bespectacled man pushed his glasses higher while a faint smile appeared on the corners of his mouth. "Blood Breeds? Could it be that those monsters with extremely fast speeds and powerful life forces are actually legendary Blood Breeds?"

As one of the Four Hunting Generals, he was similar to Dahm because his greatest interest and hobby was fulfilling his perverted love of torturing people as well.

"Another insignificant human!" Kaya's expression darkened.

Before she could finish speaking, three well-built men and women appeared in their surroundings. As the strongest and most terrifying death row criminals that Dahm had gathered, each of the Four Hunting Generals had extremely powerful and glorious pasts.

"Oh oh oh… There are real Vampires in this world, huh?" a muscular bald man who was holding an iron rod sneered viciously, "I was wondering how it was possible for the fellow that I caught previously to have such strong regenerative abilities. He could still move after I broke all four of his limbs and removed his eyes and tongue. Apparently, he was a Vampire, huh," a look of sudden realization appeared on his face.

They were the purest thugs and world-class killers. They had gathered here as Dahm's underlings because his cruel nature was fully compatible with their habits. Realistically speaking, Dahm could defeat them in his normal state even if the four of them worked together and perfected their training of the Waterbird Fist. Their extremely terrifying powers led Dahm to group them separately from his other subordinates by referring to them as the Four Hunting Generals which could also be interpreted as the Four Haunting Generals.

"Don't tell me you're not worried about your leader?" Pritto tried to divert the quartet's attention. As a ranked Blood Breed, he could sense a dangerous air around these four people. "He's facing three ranked Blood Breeds…"

His gaze unconsciously drifted towards the other side of the battlefield when he spoke. However, he was shocked to the point where he was unable to continue speaking after looking over there.

Other than himself, Kaya and Isaros who stood on the sidelines and the two girls in the car were also staring at the nearby battlefield with stunned expressions on their faces.

The man in red, Dahm laughed maniacally while entangling himself with three other figures. The repercussions of powerful air currents burst forth when the four of them collided made it difficult for the surrounding Vampires to stand up steadily, much less approach them.

Every time Dahm outstretched his arms and flapped them, ringing explosions could be heard every time his wing-like limbs touched the bodies of the three people gently.

All three lower-level Blood Breeds were being fatally suppressed by him. They could not even need to think about gaining the upper hand since they could not even protect themselves. It was clear that Farne who suffered a powerful direct hit recently could not even reform properly.

"Hehehe, they would dare to collide with Marshall's arms despite being unable to even touch his Dead Waterbird Fist?" The gigantic bald man glanced at the three Blood Breeds on the battlefield with a condescending look in his eyes.

"Idiot! Those are three ranked Blood Breeds! Once they use that..!" Kaya could not stop herself from retorting but was held back by Pritto who did not allow her to continue speaking.

At this moment, changes began to appear throughout the fight between the heads.

Chapter 692: Pursue and Attack 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Blood Breed who was called Kurt stopped suddenly. It seemed as if black halos or whirlpools had formed in his eyes while he stared daggers at Dahm who was laughing maniacally.

Human hypnotism was a Blood Breed's natural talent and ability! It was also a suppression ability that could restrain a human's true genes completely.

At this moment, Dahm's movements suddenly slowed down. Black light flashed in the eyes of the two other Blood Breeds simultaneously while they glared at Dahm.

"Control him! This man is too strong!" Lars yelled loudly while his face remained pale. His hardened skin was completely useless against his opponent because a single touch would cause the blood in his body to explode and burst out involuntarily.

However, if the hypnotism could control their opponent, his strength would then be useful to them!! This would serve as a huge boost to the powers of these three people!

Even now, a sliver of fear remained on Farne's face. This man in red was too frightening. Farne was still traumatized by the attack and could feel that he was losing control of the blood in his body just by touching the other man.

"This is bad! There's something hidden in his consciousness! I can't control him!!" yelled Kurt in a panicked state suddenly, "Retreat!!!"

"Not good, the Marshall is about to go crazy!! Retreat quickly!!"

The bespectacled man's face changed at once.

"What do we do about these people?!" yelled the bald man frantically.

"Don't care about them! Go!!"

The Four Hunting Generals seemed as if they had seen something terrifying at almost the exact same moment. Each of them ran frantically in a different direction. The people around them who carried firearms were openly fighting with the crowd of Black Uniforms who wore veils over their faces. However, their opponent's regenerative abilities and frightening speed had forced them into an unfavorable position. Soon, once they realized that their head had fled as well, they dropped their weapons quickly and ran away from the area.

Pritto and the others stared at the Four Hunting Generals and numerous subordinates who had forsaken their leader and fled. They were unable to react towards this strange situation for a period of time.

Ahh!!!!!

Moments later, a sharp scream could be heard from the leader who was standing on the outskirts of the battlefield suddenly. The shrillness of the scream caused everyone's eardrums to ache while buzzing noises made it impossible to hear other sounds.

Boom!!!

At the center of the area where the Blood Breeds and Dahm were fighting, a shroud of blood red mist expanded and exploded suddenly and covered the entire battlefield instantly as if it were smoke.

Terrifying bright red smoke twirled around Dahm's entire body at the epicenter, as if he was a supernatural being who had just walked straight out of hell. An intense bloody smell permeated the air and diffused for more than a hundred meters.

He lowered his head while a ferocious look appeared on his face.

"Controlling and… Controlling again!! The thing I despise the most… is when others control me!!!"

The three Blood Breeds were sent flying by the violent blood mist before they rolled over and hit the ground below them. Kurt was the only one who was in slightly better shape while the other two resembled torn cloth dolls whose limbs had been twisted into strange arcs. They coughed up large mouthfuls of blood from their mouths involuntarily. Extended periods of bleeding had caused their terrifying regenerative abilities to slow down.

Kurt ground his teeth and glared at Dahm's somewhat blurry figure which remained in the center.

"Retreat!!" he finally clenched his teeth and spat these words out.

To think that three ranked Blood Breeds would be forced to retreat while facing a normal human! This was a humiliating decision and he could already imagine the ridiculous rumors that the Blood Breed society would spread around after discovering that this trio had retreated.

"Retreat?" a strange voice that was neither male nor female echoed beside his ear.

Dahm's face appeared in front of Kurt immediately. His face was directly in front of Kurt's, making it possible for him to clearly see that his opponent's eyes were bloodshot. It was almost impossible to see the whiteness of his pupils as they seemed to be covered in layers of spider web-like blood vessels.

Kurt's face turned pale at once.

He lowered his head while still in a trance and looked at his own chest before a perfectly straight pale arm stabbed through it and clamped down on his beating heart tightly.

Bang!!

Dahm clawed at Kurt's face with all five fingers of his other hand at the same time. His fingernails dug deeply into Kurt's brain before he gouged his entire face out. He used his immense strength to smash Kurt against the ground and a deep pit was formed there while soil was sent flying.

On the other side, Farne and Lars watched on in horror as Kurt was brutally clawed to death. They wanted to move but their bodies would not respond to them at all. While the bloody mist continued to waft in the air, it seemed as though the mist had coagulated their blood, making it move as slowly as sticky glue.

For Blood Breeds who fully depended on their blood, this was simply fatal!

"Don't… Don't! Don't kill me!!" yelled Lars in fear.

"I surrender!! You killed Kurt even though he was the Blood Breed who would inherit the Holy Technique. You will definitely be pursued and killed by the clan! However, I know how to evade the attack!! Let me go!!" yelled Farne on the side as well.

But the current Dahm was unable to listen to reason anymore. Both of his eyes were blood red when his figure flashed like lightning and swept past both Farne and Lars instantly.

Bang bang!! Two dull noises could be heard before both of their heads exploded immediately, just like balloons that had been filled with too much air.

The Vampires around him who had not reacted in time instantly became Dahm's punching bags. Their blood red figures were tossed back and forth horizontally. Massive explosions would occur every time he touched them while the blood mist restrained them from moving.

Dahm laughed maniacally as he sank into a completely irrational state.

Bloody flesh and severed limbs flew past. Most of them were covered in the blood mist that seemed to have thickened suddenly.

On the other side, Pritto and Kaya were already sitting inside the car. Their foreheads were beaded with sweat while they tried to move the car. However, the engine seemed to be against them for some reason, as it refused to start at all!

Meanwhile, Isaros covered Arisa and Vivien's eyes tightly and stuffed rolled up paper into their ears while cradling both of their heads in her bosom.

"Damn! It hasn't started up yet?!" Kaya beat the car window angrily.

The terrified screams in their surroundings had decreased.

The front of their sedan was blocked off by the cars that the Blood Breeds had driven, forcing them to turn the corner to escape. Fortunately, the blood mist had covered them, allowing them to move freely without being countered by anyone else.

"That monster is almost here!! Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!!" Kaya turned around and glanced behind before feeling her soul escaping her body when she noticed that only a few Vampires remained out of the hundreds that had arrived.

"I'm trying my best!!" Pritto was also panicking.

Bang!!

Suddenly, the glass of the car window was instantly smashed. A blood-covered arm grabbed Kaya violently and dragged her outside while large amounts of blood mist drifted inside.

"Save…!!" Kaya could only yell out half of her sentence before she was torn out of the car.

A crashing noise could be heard after Kaya was thrown out of the car by her throat. The tires of the sedan made scratching noises when the car was pulled by his immense strength.

"Save me, save me, you say?! Hahahaha…" Dahm laughed maniacally while clutching Kaya by her throat and suspending her helpless body mid-air.

"I'm the strongest 'Deadly Fist', Dahm Elfman! Anyone who blocks my path must die!! Die!! Hahahaha!!"

He raised his head towards the sky and laughed like a madman.

The ground was a mess of corpses and severed limbs and he was the last man left standing in this pool of blood. The people in the car felt chills run down their spines when they looked at the crazed Dahm and his completely bloodsoaked body. This man seemed like a demon from hell who was neither Blood Breed nor human while fat pigs that were waiting to be slaughtered lay before him.

"Get down from the car and run away from here!!" Pritto spat out those words hurriedly before he rushed out the car as well and charged towards Dahm. He could not just stand here and watch this man murder Kaya. Despite this woman's venomous and harsh words, she chose to remain by her friend's side at the most crucial moments instead of selling him out in times of fear and danger.

Isaros took a deep breath and held both of the young girls while they got out of the car hurriedly before running towards the far end of the area quickly.

They were only a few steps away before they heard Pritto and Kaya's desperate screams behind them. The shrill and painful screams made it impossible for the girls not to shiver in Isaros's arms.

Whoosh!

A blood red silhouette appeared in front of them suddenly.

It was Dahm!!

This terrifying man had apparently gotten rid of Pritto and Kaya in a few moments and had now caught up with them instantly.

His hand stretched outwards as quick as lightning and attempted to seize the two young girls in Isaros's arms.

"Die… Die… Die!!" You want to control me? Die! Hahaha!!" It seemed as if he had lost his mind. His fingernails that were as sharp as daggers were aimed directly at the foreheads of both girls.

Isaros could not move her body at all and could only watch as he attempted to stab the girls in her arms.

Vivien widened her eyes and could see the blood red fingers that were approaching her through the cracks between Isaros's fingers. The heavy shadow of death was covering her quickly.

"Dad… Mom… Big brother…" her body had stiffened and she was shivering from fear while hallucinations appeared before her eyes.

The fingers were getting closer and Vivien could feel their sharp coldness when her forehead was pierced painfully.

"Garen!!!"

Suddenly, Big Sister Isaros's shouts echoed beside her ear and almost sounded as loud as a roar.

The fingertips stiffened suddenly before stopping in mid-air.

"She's Garen's younger sister! You cannot kill her!!" at this moment, Isaros's impulse that nearly pushed her to tears was apparently effective!

She could see a slight similarity between Dahm and Garen's style of punching. However, this was merely a gamble.

She was finally able to stop this monster's killing spree.

"Garen…" Dahm's body shivered when he heard that name. The bloody insanity and rationality were continuously entangled in his eyes while they fought and conflicted with each other.

Slowly, the seemingly endless amounts of blood mist seeped back into his body. His aura was returning to his body quickly, meaning that his rationality was gradually gaining the upper hand as well.

Pfoo…

The shrill whistling noise of moving air echoed from a faraway distance suddenly.

Bang!!

A large cloud of black mist flew over furiously like a bomb and collided against Dahm who stood dazed in place. It sent him flying more than ten meters away.

"Dahm! You wanted to kill Master's sister?" a cold male voice echoed from far away.

Hochman got down from a sedan with silvery-white patterns. His entire body was contoured by terrifying and violent-looking muscles while he was dressed in a black singlet and slender Western-style trousers that covered his wide back and taut waist. A pair of blonde youthful female twins followed behind him closely.

The collision caused Dahm to be sent flying for more than ten meters after he was hit by a basketball-sized rock. Two long black skid marks that resembled ditches were formed when his legs were dragged against the ground. He did not suffer any serious injuries except for the swelling of a few blood vessels on his cheeks.

"Hochman…" he glared fiercely at the man who had just alighted from the car, "Why are you here?!"

"What do you think?" Hochman's handsome face glanced at him coldly, "Look at your embarrassing state. You're neither man nor beast. Frankly, you're a disgrace to my combat club's reputation!"

He glanced at the dirty battlefield that was filled with bloody severed limbs in disgust.

"Let's go. Take these people. Master wants to see you."

Chapter 693: Meet 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Tap… Tap… Tap…

Inside a study in Berlin, Garen's fingers rapped against the desktop rhythmically.

He lowered his head and looked at Dahm who was kneeling on the ground and Hochman who stood by the side respectfully. The atmosphere was somewhat constrained.

"Both of you were my favorite and strongest disciples," said Garen in a slow and emphasized tone.

Neither Dahm nor Hochman spoke. However, Dahm's body began to shiver slightly as if he was afraid of something.

"I taught both of you so that you would enhance my Waterbird Fist." Garen looked at Dahm, "But do you see what you've done? You destroyed transmission radios and made it impossible for me to relay additional orders. You even almost did unforgivable things."

Garen's expression was calm and gentle as if he was merely chatting about potential afternoon leisure activities.

"If I had not gotten Hochman to rush over in time, Dahm…"

"It was my fault!!" Dahm lowered his head quickly, "No matter how you decide to punish me, I will endure it willingly!!"

His voice was quaking.

The Fist Techniques meant everything to him, and the one who controlled them was Garen. Once the source of this control was taken away… Perhaps it would be impossible for him to find a new source for a certain period of time… When he thought of that inhuman pain, all of the bones in his body itched to the core but he was unable to scratch or soothe it at all.

Hochman glanced at him coldly.

"Master, the conflict with the Blood Breeds was hard to avoid. Dahm killed the inheritor of the Holy Techniques from one of the five main Blood Breed clans. Every single Holy Technique inheritor is specially selected and is also the hope of their clan. We must make prior preparations."

"And what is your opinion…?" Garen looked at his sedate disciple who had clearly never been one to openly express his joy or anger. He knew that this guy had obviously interrogated a few Vampires to acquire this information.

"Master, please move to the Holy Fist Palace. We've built a base with defensive facilities that will make it absolutely safe there. The current Blood Breeds are not certain that you are the president of our combat club. In other words, they may also be unaware that the 'Holy Fist' of the combat club refers to you. In order to face the Blood Breed clans, we must proceed with establishing and setting up complete systems. It will be impossible for loose organizations to counter the hoards of Blood Breeds that will gather," explained Hochman quietly.

"You're trying to say that we should unite our forces such as the combat club, Nighthawks, your Boxing Overlord club, Dahm's Deadly Fist club, and the strengths of Quentin and the others?" said Garen when he understood what Hochman meant.

Hochman had a grim look on his face. In comparison to Dahm, he had always been the one who could actually think subtly and deeply.

"With the Holy Fist Palace as the core, we will gather as a large group. I believe that with Master's strength, neither the Blood Breeds nor anyone else will be able to obstruct us," Hochman displayed his wild ambition calmly.

"We'll integrate the combat strength of the entire world to create a system for martial artists that will be used as our core. Therefore, everyone will respect our Holy Fist Palace as the holiest and most supreme place! Doesn't this fulfill the true meaning behind Master's propagation of the enigma of the Holy Fist?" although he was clearly speaking coldly in a low voice, it still sounded as if he was instigating something.

Garen looked at his disciple carefully.

"My Fist Techniques are ancient Fist Techniques that were used for killing. Are you sure you that you understand the meaning of these words?"

Integrating all schools of martial arts and forming a holy land of all the martial arts in this world was equivalent to pioneering a new era. What kinds of exploits and feats were this?!

But it would surely bring unprecedented reigns of terror that would start a war of supremacy.

"This was the best method we could think of," Hochman nodded. It was obvious that this was not the first day that this thought had crossed his mind.

Garen narrowed his eyes. He understood that Hochman's desire for him to integrate all of his forces was based on his own wild ambitions. This disciple knew that he was uninterested to govern these trivial matters and preferred to shove them to other people. Meanwhile, Dahm was not a suitable candidate to take care of such a large organization because he was too cruel. Those who were truly suitable for this position were frankly far and few in between.

"This is something we could do," said Garen slowly while mentioning the keynotes, "From the perspective of you and Dahm, the results of the international combat competition that you organized was good and very successful."

"True," Hochman nodded, "So far, we've received different martial arts sects from 246 countries around the world. We've taken note of certain strong and special sects and registered them already. That includes the areas that they occupy, social positions, personal influence, and economic strength among other things."

He arranged his glasses.

"From this information, I've discovered that even the strongest combat sects cannot be compared to the power of our Waterbird Fist. Most of the Grandmasters of Combat are unable to counter ambushes that use firearms. Moreover, they lack experience in fighting with weapons during actual combat as most of them are merely adept in showy martial arts that are impractical."

Garen nodded assuredly.

"Isn't the competition actually just an opportunity to eliminate these useless and trashy sects?"

"Getting rid of the weeds to keep the flowers. That's an ancient Asian saying," Hochman smiled, "Once we had finally approved and finalized the standards, we decided that there were only three main sects in the world that could truly be called martial arts sects, excluding ourselves."

"Which three?"

"With us as the center, there is the Eastern Fist Technique in the west that includes Wushu-like fighting sequences as their fundamental principles. These have been passed down for many years and are very valuable. They are mainly found in countries like China, India, Mongolia, and Russia among others. The Saudi Fist Technique in the south includes many types of sword moves and leg techniques and focuses on speed. It is mainly spread across Argentina, Chile, Brazil and other countries. The eastern side is more complicated as many main sects have fused and blended with each other. One of the strongest actual combat sects is the Mocksaw Sword Sect, a sword sect established by the master swordsman Mocksaw that focuses on actual combat. However, it has currently evolved into the gun and sword technique, a sword technique that is paired with firearms. It is mainly used in various countries in Europe. The ideas behind this sword technique have influenced the combat of many countries heavily. Therefore, the masters of this technique are always be invited as instructors when the special forces of various countries are undergoing training sessions," Hochman listed all the main points of these notable sects in a familiar manner.

"Eastern Fist, Saudi Fist, and Mocksaw Sword Sect. Meanwhile, our own country has the Waterbird Fist. These are the four main notable and powerful sects in the world," Garen repeated once more, "Have you met the representatives of these sects?"

"Of course, we have already established interactive relations as well," Hochman nodded, "There are actually many other powerful sects, but we've placed them in the second batch because the representatives of their sect were not powerful enough. That's all I have to report right now. In order to establish a Holy Path for our Fist Technique, we need an overwhelming victory that will truly involve the whole world! In this respect, we need large amounts of manpower and financial resources. We will also need stronger safety measures."

At this moment, Dahm who was kneeling beside Hochman finally flared up. The soul primer inside his body, the core of his aura had been stirred up by Garen. The painful itchiness that reached his bone marrow tortured him until his body shivered continuously. Sweat soaked through his entire shirt in a few moments while he remained kneeling on the ground.

The muscles on his body felt as if they were being air-dried. They had started to shrivel up slowly because his skin was getting dehydrated from losing large amounts of water at once. These terrifying effects could be seen by the naked eye because he was losing water too quickly.

Garen glanced at him.

"This is your punishment. After two days, I will relieve you from these disciplinary actions."

Dahm's entire body spasmed before he lowered his head barely.

"Thank you… Master…" he squeezed these few words out with much difficulty before he stopped speaking altogether.

"You will solve the problems that you created on your own. The issues with the inheritor of the Holy Technique will be solved by yourself as well. Since you created the Dead Waterbird Fist because you desired to form your own group, you need to be equipped with the ability to take responsibility as well," said Garen while waving his hand, "You can leave now."

Only then did Dahm raise his head. He stood up with much difficulty and moved like a zombie before walking out of the room. He would need to endure this punishment for another two days. This sensation was easily more painful than frying his whole body in boiling oil. However, he had no strength to fight back as these were the retributions of taking the shortcut. While gaining powerful strength, he would be imprisoned in unbreakable shackles at the same time.

Garen continued to ask Hochman about the other martial arts sects in the world.

This world mainly revolved on an orbit that consisted of Blood Breeds and Witches. They were the conductors who were currently orchestrating the melodies of this world and the ones who would decide the main path that the earth would follow.

Meanwhile, the normal martial artists formed a completely different circle. They had no extraordinary powers at all and were merely walking on the path of becoming stronger purely based on their own hard work and the integration of modern technology. Many disciples who were guilty of manslaughter that had been forced into the circle of mercenaries had naturally received training that involved blood and fire.

Although this circle was not powerful, unifying it would be no simple task.

*****************

At the temporary Nighthawks base on the outskirts of Berlin.

The base was located at the bottom of a valley in the wilderness, where the furthest road was a ten-minute car ride away.

The entire base was once used as a training base for the German army garrison before the Nighthawks had bid for it at an auction. It became a training base for a smaller group of stationed troops after it was modified.

Those who were inside the base performed their garrison duties strictly in an environment that was filled with guards.

Every few steps, there would be at least one or two elite mercenaries carrying firearms while on guard. They were dressed in the exact same black soldier's uniform. Meanwhile, monitor probes and infrared defense lines were placed in every corner of the base.

Small-scale unmanned drones would fly across the sky at certain periods of time to patrol the area. Although no one knew how the various parameter inductors detected the threats, they were still used as additional layers of protection.

The base consisted of unified black buildings that were metallic and glossy. Black houses were built inside a square-shaped area that cars drove past continuously. Occasionally, people who either left from missions or returned after completing them would exit and enter the base.

Within a building that was used for medical services.

Inside the clean white ward, three sickbeds were scattered and distributed there.

"Pritto…" called a weak female voice from one of the sickbeds. "Are you still alright?"

White light cascaded into the room from the outside through the window and shone on the blankets of the white sickbeds. There was a pale young woman with blonde hair under the blanket. Her eyelids were slightly swollen and she seemed lifeless. Currently, her head was turned sideways while she looked at the man on another sickbed.

"Damn them! Don't they know that male and female wards should be separated into two rooms? How dare they just throw us into a room without a single care!"

Some of this woman's vigor and energy seemed to have returned when she opened her mouth and began cursing suddenly.

"Don't be angry… This place is that monster's territory… Only bad things will happen to us if we end up provoking him," the man on the sickbed beside her answered in an exhausted voice.

These two people were Kaya and Pritto who had been personally saved by Hochman from the slaughter. Since both of them were lower-level Blood Breeds, they would not die even if their blood dried out. They would only weaken; as long as their cores were unbroken and their brains remained intact, other things would not be a problem. However, it had been sheer luck that Dahm decided to go after Isaros and the others while he went crazy. This distracted him from finishing them off with a killing blow. Otherwise, neither of them would have lived to see another day.

Chapter 694: Meet 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In Dahm's eyes, the supposed Vampires and Blood Breeds were mere insects with slightly stronger life forces. They were not extremely different from regular humans. Although these Blood Breeds had learned many techniques and combat skills that were suitable for themselves with their enhanced lifespans, Dahm thought that these were useless and tantamount to not learning anything at all.

"We're still alive… How fortunate…" Pritto seemed much weaker than Kaya. He had been stabbed in the chest by Dahm when he'd tried to save Kaya and his core would have been seized if he had not prepared himself to dodge the attack in time. However, Dahm had used his aura to suck all of Pritto's blood out of his body, causing it to spurt outwards until not a single drop was left. This was immensely detrimental to his vitality.

"A hoard of Blood Breeds were actually defeated by a single human, butchered even…" Pritto smiled bitterly, "This world is truly becoming mad…"

Kaya opened her mouth and was about to mention that she was unconcerned about the attitudes of normal humans but was momentarily unable to say anything.

"Wait till my uncle arrives. He will definitely make that fellow pay the price for hurting us!!" she was finally able to squeeze out a few hateful words.

"Your uncle, huh? Look at that bed over there and see if…" Pritto gazed at his good friend with a sympathetic and compassionate look.

The head of a slightly balding middle-aged man stretched out from the last sickbed slowly.

He smiled bitterly and waved at Kaya.

"I'm sorry, Kaya…"

"Uncle!!" Kaya's eyes widened immediately. A look of utter disbelief appeared on her face, "You!! How did you…??!!"

The middle-aged man rubbed his nose bashfully.

"I encountered the man named Hochman halfway through my journey and fell into a coma after he struck me with his fist. When I woke up, I was already here…"

"…"

"…"

The sick ward was filled with awkward silence.

Pritto did not know what to say while Kaya's face was completely flushed. She was extremely resentful and wished that she could find a hole to bury herself.

After some time…

"That's right, Uncle Bally. Did you come here alone?" it was clear that Pritto had a good relationship with this middle-aged Blood Breed as he was able to chat with him casually.

"Yes, I drove here hurriedly from home. I wanted to come to your aid quickly before the secret party Blood Breeds arrived. However, I was unable to find my other friends to help in time," Uncle Bally nodded frankly.

His human identity was based off a rich merchant. He was portly, fair, and plump with a little clump of a beard. No one would be able to guess that he was a heavily embellished, first-rate American boxer. Moreover, he was also a Blood Breed boxer and one of the light party's few lower level Blood Breed representatives.

"But you don't have to worry. Although I've been captured, my friends and brothers from the clan should have discovered that something is amiss by now. They've probably made their moves already as well. We just need to wait and we'll be fine," explained Bally assuredly. He had rushed across a distance of a thousand meters to save his niece but did not expect that he would be dragged into this as well. This made it hard for the older man to hide his emotions while he tried to redeem his reputation quickly.

"That's right, where are Isaros and the rest?"

Kaya had just remembered the three other people who came with them.

"They were taken away by the people here…" Bally replied.

*****************************

On a road on the outskirts of Berlin.

A black limousine with silver vine-like patterns drove past steadily. It clearly did not fit in with the other cars in its surroundings as it was particularly showy.

A car like this resembled an exquisite work of art. Its slender and streamline body seemed like a mirror that could reflect the images of people.

Although the limousine was not traveling quickly, it steadily overtook a few large lorries and normal cars. It attracted the curious gazes of the drivers while some of them even took their phones out to snap pictures.

This was Athena no. 4, a first class luxury manual car manufactured by Poly, one of the four largest car manufacturers in the world. It was also a limited edition vehicle that was worth more than five million Euros.

It was also the Nighthawks' only custom-made vehicle that was specially manufactured for Garen.

The people inside the car couldn't feel that it was moving at all. Instead, they merely felt as if they were sitting on the sofa at home. Even though they could see that the scenery outside was passing by rapidly, they could not tell that they were moving at all.

Regardless if this was due to the performance of the car or the skills of the driver, both of these factors coordinated with each other to produce great results.

Isaros and Arisa guarded little Vivien in the back seat while quietly observing and taking in their entire surroundings.

After they left the site of the killings, they were taken away by a man that was sent by the one named Hochman. Things took a turn for the better after they were flown directly to Germany and finally placed in this luxurious car. Once they had eaten an exquisite and sumptuous dinner in the car, the emotions of all three girls had finally calmed down slowly.

Perhaps the driver was making an effort to slow down after taking into account that they had suffered a terrible fright. The car moved slowly, making it seem as if they were not moving at all.

"Where are we going now?" asked Vivien quietly.

Arisa shook her head but kept holding Vivien's hand tightly while looking at her older sister Isaros.

Isaros nodded to show that she understood before raising her head to ask the driver.

"Ladies, you don't have to ask. We will be reaching Berlin immediately," the driver was a gorgeous woman with an exquisite face. She was dressed in a clean and tidy black outfit that consisted of long pants and a tight sleeveless top that wrapped itself around her body and showed off her ample bosom and beautiful figure clearly.

"I am Quentin. I came over to pick you up according to Master's commands," said the woman while introducing herself, "Therefore, do not worry. Everything has passed and all of you are very safe now."

"The master you are referring to is…?" Isaros furrowed her eyebrows.

"Our President Garen, you mean? How is it possible that none of you know him?" it was obvious that Quentin was slightly shocked.

Isaros felt a chill in her heart.

They had seen a lot of people holding firearms on their way here. Both of the terrifying professional fighters that seemed too strong to be human were apparently the ones who had sternly arranged them in an orderly and disciplined row. It was obvious that an extremely powerful force was controlling and backing the overall situation.

She thought that she had already overestimated Garen's strength. However, she had not anticipated to find out that she had actually underestimated the exact details of that man. What kind of world had that man named Garen actually experienced previously? He was apparently able to gain the backing and support of such strong forces.

No... 'Support' was not the right word. In retrospect, this strength was obviously something that he had nurtured on his own.

The car moved forward slowly while Quentin occasionally answered Isaros's questions on the way.

Gradually, she finally exposed more information about Garen. Vivien had slowly recovered from her shock as well and was now interested in the topic that the other women were speaking about. The Garen that they were talking about was a completely different person from the Garen in her memories.

The Garen that Quentin spoke about was strong, cool, and perfect. He was simply an inhuman existence that would be divinized soon.

Meanwhile, the older brother in her memories was merely a normal guy. Apart from his slightly handsome looks and exceptional grades, nothing else was special about him.

Both of these people were completely unrelated to each other.

The sky slowly darkened.

The car finally arrived at the grounds of a magnificent villa before slowing down behind a black villa.

Whoosh…

The large garage doors opened themselves automatically while being illuminated by tiny glowing red lights.

Quentin drove the car inside slowly and stopped in a parking lot on the extreme left side. The whole garage was unusually spacious while three expensive looking race cars and a limousine were parked inside.

Two men in black suits opened the door for the three women with respectful looks on their faces.

"The commander has already been waiting on the second floor for some time. Please come with me."

One of the gentle-looking blonde men spoke in fluent American English while flashing an enchanting smile at the three women inside the car. He spoke with a slight London accent which made him sound strict but refined.

Isaros got down from the car first and stood in front of the car door to protect the two other girls while they alighted slowly. She was also taking in the sights of her surroundings at the same time.

The garage was illuminated by gentle yellow light. When the light reflected off the surface of the car, countless dots of faint yellow light appeared throughout the garage suddenly.

There was a transparent glass wall on the right side of the garage where they got out of the car. Through the glass, they could see a little reception room that was decorated with a sofa and some flower vases. Maids in black and white uniforms were cleaning the dust off the furniture inside.

The blonde man who led the way walked towards a corner of the glass wall where an automated glass door was placed. A muscular black man with a concealed gun at his waist stood in the doorway and spoke a few sentences to him softly before stepping back and bowing towards the women slightly as a sign of respect.

Isaros returned the sentiment by smiling before taking Arisa and Vivien inside quickly.

Frankly, Arisa and herself were quite used to this. They had once entered the Primary Colors' high-scale laboratory and had seen upper-class living conditions. Only Vivien, however, was somewhat unable to stay calm.

Her eyes scanned the room curiously. The iron nerves and sense of adventurism that were naturally present in the bones of Americans were vividly portrayed in her. Despite almost losing her life earlier, she was apparently able to restore herself in a day.

"Vivien… Are you sure that we're meeting your brother?" Arisa came close to her ear and asked quietly,

"I don't know either…" Vivien shook her head. Frankly, her heart was only filled with curious desire.

All three of them entered the little reception room before the maids that were sweeping earlier lifted their skirts and executed an accurate curtsey in front of them. The trio was at a loss and did not know how to return the sentiment. Fortunately, the man who was leading the way called them over to the small door on the right side of the reception room immediately.

There was a little elevator there with a retina and fingerprint scanner on the side of the silvery-white elevator door. Isaros saw the blonde man align his eye there and press all five of his finger pads against the scanner before the elevator door opened.

She was keen enough to notice that there were hidden cutting laser traps inside the silver elevator as well. If an enemy were to either break into the lift and get inside hastily or enter it without the appropriate approvals, these lasers would unleash their terrifying killing abilities, making it impossible for any enemies to even exist within this tightly-sealed space.

"A minor accident occurred when we were supposed to send you off earlier. The culprit, Marshall Dahm has been punished properly already. Frankly, Marshall Dahm's initial motives were good before he was provoked by those few Blood Breeds who caused his emotions to become insane. We hope that all of you will no longer blame him," said the blonde man sincerely.

Only then did Isaros notice that this man was one of Dahm's four strongest subordinates.

"He nearly killed us," said Isaros coldly.

"Regardless of the kind of compensation you desire, the Marshall will swear to fulfill it. This is his sincerest apology and we hope that you will accept it." The blonde man placed a little object on Isaros's palm gently. It felt like a little box but its contents were unknown.

Chapter 695: Plan 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Isaros pinched the object gently and hesitated momentarily.

However, she was not hesitating about this item. Instead, she was thinking about the fact that Dahm was Garen's subordinate, and the contradicting problems that would arrive if she did not accept Dahm's apology.

"Please don't worry. No matter what, Marshall's apology is truly sincere," replied the blonde man with a smile when he noticed her hesitance.

Isaros nodded faintly and gently stuffed the item into the palm of Vivien who was behind her. The latter was slightly stunned and about to say something but stopped when Isaros shook her head and signaled her to keep her mouth closed.

Ding…

The elevator stopped slowly before the door opened automatically. A young woman in black tights stood guard outside the door.

"Please follow me, all three of you," said the woman respectfully while bowing her head lightly.

Isaros and the other two girls followed the woman out of the elevator and walked towards the right side into a corridor that was covered with a white carpet. There was a study with a faint white light at the end of the corridor. The door to the study was slightly ajar, allowing rays of light to shine outside.

The trio followed the woman and stopped in front of the doorway. She knocked the door three times gently before pushing it open slowly.

The inside of the room was immediately exposed before the eyes of these three people.

Inside the spacious room, nothing was eye-catching except for the magnetic presence who was clearly seated behind the metallic silvery-white desk in the middle of the room. This figure had instantly attracted the gazes and attention of all three people.

A young blonde man sat in the leather chair behind the desk with one hand on the armrest of the chair. His other hand was gently stroking the white jade lion paperweight on his desk. The most eye-catching thing about him was the black metal mask on his face. That mask was unusually hypnotic because it was expressionless but had clusters of little eyes on the forehead area that added mysterious and cold qualities to this man.

"Welcome. I haven't seen you for such a long time, Isaros, Arisa, and my beloved Little Vivien," said the man while sounding as if he was smiling.

"You are… Garen?!" Isaros could feel a sense of familiarity from his voice suddenly.

"Big brother!!" Little Vivien who stood on the side could sense this familiarity even more. She ran over immediately and threw herself into Garen's embrace at once. She had been in a state of anxiety throughout her journey and was finally able to release all of her emotions fully now that she had arrived here.

Once she jumped into Garen's embrace and smelled his familiar scent, Vivien suddenly felt as if she was wrapped in a thick security blanket. She only wished that she could bury herself in her brother's chest and stay there forever.

Garen hugged Vivien. The little sister whom he had grown up with had already become a sixteen or seventeen year old beauty now. She was wearing a pair of denim shorts and a white T-shirt that she had just changed into while her pale thighs were exposed. Moreover, Little Vivien sat directly on his lap and curled herself up like a little kitten that was crying against his chest.

"You're so big already. Alright, alright. Don't cry." Garen held Vivien and attempted to pull her away, but this little fellow rubbed her snot and tear stained face against him instead. She would rather die than let go, forcing him to just let her stay there as she wished.

Both Isaros and Arisa each found a chair to sit on inside the study. Meanwhile, someone else had closed the door behind them.

Once Little Vivien's emotions had calmed down slightly, Garen brushed against an acupuncture spot on her back and Little Vivien began to doze off suddenly before drifting into deep sleep.

Only then did Garen raise his head to look at the two people in front of him.

"I know that both of you definitely have a lot of questions to ask me. However, I will only answer you selectively."

"Big brother Garen, why do you have so many subordinates?!"

Before Isaros could speak, Arisa who stood beside her asked the first question. After experiencing Dahm and Hochman's terrifying powers personally, her initial favorable impression and admiration of Garen were suddenly amplified all at once. Although she was still barely able to maintain her image of a virtuous maiden, for now, the bright and watery gaze that she used to stare at Garen made it seem as if the word 'worship' was written on her face.

"I obviously nurtured them…"

"Then why are you wearing a mask?"

"This was something that I was utterly helpless against. You just need to know that I did not wish to wear it."

"Your mask looks really good. So cool!"

"Thanks…"

"Could I have one too?"

"This mask is not something that can be worn by the average person…"

"Big brother, how did you know that we were in danger?"

"I have my information channels."

"How should we repay you for saving us?"

"Don't worry about that…"

They continued speaking, but after less than ten minutes, Garen looked on impatiently as Arisa buried herself in his embrace as well. This beautiful little girl with shoulder-length red hair used the excuse that she had been scared silly and needed a warm, strong embrace before burrowing herself against his chest.

It was fortunate that he was tall, muscular, and almost two meters tall. The shape of his entire body had become burly after he entered the fifth star, allowing him to envelop both of these little girls in his arms without any problems.

Arisa curled herself up in Garen's chest with a satisfied smile on her face before falling into a deep sleep quickly.

Suddenly, only Isaros and Garen were left in the room.

Isaros glanced at Garen who was sitting behind the desk. There were too many questions in her head that she wanted to ask him. She wanted to ask him about his power, strength, and other things such as his true position and character…

But once the words reached the corners of her mouth, she realized that she was completely unable to open it as there were too many related questions and she did not know where to begin.

"I'm already aware of the incidents between you and the Blood Breeds," Garen spoke first after a few moments of silence, "The Holy Technique of the Scarlet Moon clan was inscribed in the depths of your consciousness. Did they obtain your approval before doing this?"

Isaros nodded faintly after acknowledging what he had said. She was not surprised at all that Garen knew this information already.

Garen looked at the expression on her face and smiled.

"The Secret Party and the Light Party were fighting and it was merely an internal struggle at first. I did not anticipate that they would involve you in this."

"We have been involved in this long ago actually. After we were listed as targets to be hunted by the Secret Party, Pritto decided to inscribe the Holy Technique in the depths of my consciousness. Compared to the Blood Breed's powerful regenerative abilities, the characteristics of normal humans like myself were much weaker. Therefore, the people from the Secret Party would have their misgivings when they hunted us down and discovered our secret, ensuring our safety," said Isaros quietly.

Garen's eyelids drooped downwards.

"With your current strength, it's completely impossible for you to protect Arisa. Do you understand?"

"That's why I have a request," nodded Arisa with a determined look on her face.

"I can't promise anything now." Garen knew what she was about to say. He was certain that she was hoping to put Arisa in his care. However, being by his side was actually more dangerous than if she were to be with Isaros.

"All of you should hurry towards the northern areas because the Lion Mother's territory is there. Moreover, the Light Party's reinforcements are there so it should be much safer. Meanwhile, here with me…" Garen placed both of his hands on the desk. "The period of time that follows after will be extremely dangerous."

"But compared to us, your powers are…" before Isaros could finish speaking, there was a soft knock on the door.

Knock knock knock.

Isaros stopped speaking suddenly and picked up the coffee cup on the little table in front of her and drank from it.

"Commander, Mr. Rod is here," said the woman who had led the way earlier called in a loud voice while standing before the door.

"Ask him to come here," Garen replied.

"I'll leave first then?" Isaros stood up because she was worried that Garen would have things that he needed to discuss.

"Your Blood Breed friends are at the base on the outskirts of the area. If you want to see them, you can just ask anyone to take you there," Garen nodded.

Isaros nodded faintly to show that she understood.

Garen continued by saying: "Arisa can stay here with me for a while. It's still temporarily safe here. When the time is right, I will send her to you."

"Thank you very much."

"You don't have to be so courteous. I've always thought of Arisa as a little sister," Garen smiled.

Once Isaros had left the study, she could hear a set of familiar sounding footsteps approaching and walking up the stairs slowly. Not long after, Rod's face that was completely devoid of any signs of sternness appeared at the doorway suddenly.

This guy had changed into a checkered shirt and white boxer briefs and flinched just as he entered the room.

"Damn, your place is so hot. Don't you ever turn on the air conditioning?" he complained.

"I've never used that toy," said Garen impatiently. The weather had become slightly unpredictable now as hot sunny days would occur in Berlin during its winter period in December. The temperature would only decrease rapidly in the evening, causing differences in temperature of over twenty degrees sometimes.

Rod pulled a chair over in a familiar manner and sat down. He soon noticed the two beautiful young girls who were curled up in Garen's lap behind the desk. One was red-haired while the other was blonde.

Suddenly, this man pointed his thumb at Garen rudely.

"Amazing! Two at one time. I had the same demeanor in my previous years!"

"They're my younger sisters…" Garen was utterly impatient with this man.

"No worries, most of them usually start as younger sisters," laughed Rod.

Garen did not explain any further.

"Any developments over at your place?" he changed the subject.

"The testing grounds have been prepared already. When do you want to test it?" said Rod frankly once his smile had finally disappeared.

The tests that he was talking about were the Rexott Group's experimental areas. They were going to test every aspect of Garen's strength and physical abilities. Moreover, Garen was also eager to compare the limits of his powers with the technology of this world.

"I have some matters to attend to now."

"Understood. Both of them are asleep because of you, huh?" Rod spoke crudely again.

But when he noticed traces of anger on Garen's face, he shut his mouth quickly.

"Alright, alright. I'll stop joking. Looks like they're really just your younger sisters. You can visit the testing grounds anytime you want, but we can't really delay the other thing anymore."

"What?"

"I'm talking about the International Fighting Competition you're organizing. The prize money is too high. Some special class mercenaries may attend, so you must be mentally prepared," Rod seemed to know some insider information.

"Don't worry. I'll take care of it properly." Garen had taken currently taken over the competition that Hochman and Dahm had organized. The prize money had been raised again and was now at ninety million euros. This large sum of money would not be provided by Garen alone as there were many other commercial sponsors who would be present. Since the last competition was a huge success, the current one would be even more influential and dynamic.

"That's right, how much do you understand about Blood Breeds?" Garen pondered for a moment before asking the question.

"Blood Breeds?" Rod's pupils shrunk, "Why? Did you provoke them?"

The Rexott Group was an organization that was determined to develop the potential of humans. Actually, they mainly existed because they were extremely unsatisfied with the Blood Breed's rule and influence over the structure of the world. Therefore, they were trying to find a new path that would strengthen normal humans to achieve their end goal of surpassing the Blood Breeds.

A goal like this would naturally require deep research of the Blood Breeds.

Chapter 696: Plan 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"It was just a small conflict."

Rod muttered to himself.

"Speaking about the Blood Breed, there is one person that we cannot miss out - the last King. It is said that thousands of years ago, our planet had a huge empire named Suva Dynasty. Due to unknown reasons, the entire great dynasty fell into turmoil and was on the brink of collapsing. At that time, the last emperor of the dynasty, who was also the last King of Suva used all kinds of mysterious measures in an attempt to solidify all his strength within himself so that he could restore the dynasty. Unfortunately, he did not succeed. Because his strengths were clustered together, his body fell apart. They exploded into two parts, split between his upper and lower body. However, his brain, and all five sensory features were still attached to his upper body, along with his heart too. That's why it became the first ancestor of Blood Breed. Whereas the lower body had the reproductive organs and both his legs, symbolizing the movement and reproduction of a collective power. Hence, it was turned into the first Witch."

"Is this the source of the myth of Blood Breed and the Witches?" It was the first time Garen of this rumor.

"We selected this out from the various myths and legends that were mostly true. Which also means that there is a possibility that this could be true," Rod nodded and said, "That's why Blood Breed is the strongest; it lies in their effort, five senses, as well as their ability to control the brain. While the for strongest Witch, it lies in their power to bring everyone together, no matter if it's through fear or respect," Rod said in detail, "These were all the untold stories my brother told me. He keeps in contact with the top ranks of the Blood Breed's five-scepter-clan. If you come across any problems that you cannot solve, maybe I can help you make some arrangements, only if it's not a huge issue…"

"Is it a big issue if a Holy Technique Inheritor was killed?"

Rod heard the reply even before he could finish his sentence. Suddenly, he stood up from his chair. His face was stunned.

　　*******************

"Damned for life!"

A clan would not have necessarily produced an inheritor of the Holy Technique even if it took them hundreds of years. This was every clan's most precious future deterrent power - the most potential talent in Blood Breed, or maybe even the future support pillars of the combat power.

Somewhere in the dark space of nothingness, black smoke clouds slowly floated around in traces of plume, as if it were silk.

An oval egg-like shape appeared in the air, and there was no light inside. All they could see was a vague red statue figure. Beside the statue sat three figures with different qualities, but because they were all so dark, it was difficult to make out who they were.

"Our Holy Technique Inheritor, Eeleen was the potential candidate we chose in the recent years. She cannot die in vain," A black figure spoke in a low voice. It was as if thunder reverberated in this space.

"Don't be so radical. We are now in the era of peace, and our clan has already claimed superiority from the action against light party. We would not want to offend any unknown force that might be powerful just because of a potential candidate,' Another person answered lazily, "For someone who can kill Eeleen so easily, it must be the intervention of other Blood Breeds or Witches."

"This issue involves the Wellington family's dignity. If we don't retaliate, our people's confidence in us will be shaken," The last voice rang out. However, the voice could not be distinguished by gender but it carried the same thunder-like echo.

"Only a few lower levels were killed. Why are you so emotional?" The lazy voice said lightly.

The Wellington Clan was one of the Blood Brood's five-sector-clan. Other than the secret party's top Death Apostle leader, the three of them were the strongest ranking elders of Blood Breed. Any decision that had to be made for the entire Wellington, whether big or small, was discussed in this confined illusionary dream space. Who knew how many decisions they have made over this noise that had a huge impact on important issues?

Originally, the Wellington family was a neutral clan. But following the clan of the Death Apostle, it leaned towards the secret party. Then naturally, their perspective shifted too.

"It is now the time for us to stand for ourselves. If we don't fight back after being provoked, it will be extremely detrimental to our clan's ranking in the secret party," The first one who spoke with the radical voice said again, "Moreover, what do you mean by only a few lower levels were killed? Every ranked Blood Breed are a precious part of the clan!"

"What is the name of the provocateur?" The lazy voiced asked.

"Dahm. I think that's the name," The unidentifiable voice replied softly.

"Maybe we can develop our descendants? Such strong humans can be very hard to find…" The lazy voice sounded excited.

"If you can convince him then it is up to you."

For the development of vampire descendants to work, both parties must agree with it so that they would be able to let go of conscious resistance. Only then, the soul could be changed.

"Forget it, it's too troublesome."

"Since the other party had the ability to kill Eeleen who was so closest to the middle rank, then let's assign that to the middle rank judges of the clan," The radical voice said in a low tone.

"Agreed."

"Agreed."

　　************************

Garen put the two girls down lightly onto the bed in the bedchamber. He covered the both of them up with a thin blanket, adjusted the room's temperature, and left.

'It's rare to seeing you so soft-hearted,' Black Sethe, who hated being lonely appeared, 'Don't delay the writings of the Demonic Book.'

"I know," Garen put his hands into his pocket, "Dahm is one of the important chess pieces I have with me right now. For now, I cannot lose her. According to intelligence, the one he killed was Wellington Clan's Holy Technique Inheritor. The other party might be responding really quickly."

'How do you plan to sort it out?'

"To resolve this as quickly as possible, before the next time Nadia attacks."

Garen walked to another study room which was a little more secretive. From the lowest level of the bookshelf, he took out a black shelled notebook. He lightly flipped it open, and impressively, there was a black gel pen in between. On the paper, some words that were written in detail were recorded.

He held up the pen, and took off its cover as he slowly flipped to the last page of the notebook. Then, he started writing.

'I need to know the detailed account of the information on Wellington Clan,' He ended the sentence with a hook-like symbol.

For a moment, the symbol that he swiftly drew suddenly disappeared on the page.

Garen slowly put down the pen, and waited.

Very quickly, within ten minutes, the notebook reacted.

'Wellington Clan from the Blood Breed? They are one of the five scepters, and you do not want to mess with them," the AG promptly replied.

'As an exchange, I will participate in your next operation. How does that sound?' Furthermore, AG helped him destroy White Phoenix Base the last time. Additionally, he provided the detailed report this time, especially since the Blood Breed really offended him. So, Garen did not intend to wait for the other party to make a move.

AG was against Blood Breed; mainly it was those who clans that initially besieged him. However, in fact, there were not only people from secret party among the crowd, but even more of them were from the light party too. Therefore, the objective of his revenge was not between parties. Instead, his goal was the Blood Breed.

This fellow had been scheming and calculating, planning for a shocking conspiracy, always wanting Garen to join.

'Then that's a deal. You joined at the right time, just when we are preparing to stabilize the situation. The secret party is huge, so our target will be Wellington," AS gave a confident reply, 'We have already arranged the detail, and we have enough people with us. The main goal will be killing statues of Wellington's Death Apostle. The other areas, we will rely on your men. Remember, you cannot let any of the Blood Breed's go! The Vampires don't matter, but if they react, all Blood Breed's must die!'

'It looks to me that you have reached the stage of attacking, and it seems like I have come at the right time,' Garen had never thought that it would be such a coincidence.

Before this, he understood that AG did not idle around. He made use of the Blood Breed's wrecked ashes from the large amount of shooting they did, and collected a lot of strange materials. With that, he created an extremely insidious and horrifying magical tool. In between, he visited Berlin once where Garen felt AG's qi becoming stronger and more profound.

Over hundreds of years accumulating in his grave, it would finally explode. He was very close to making changes that would turn the world upside that - Garen had that feeling. This old guy might be breaking through to a new level soon.

What level would a high rank go if he broke through it? There was only one answer - Death Apostle.

'Among the four Death Apostles, Wellington lost to Castine the last time. Since they are far from recovering right now, this is our chance. To be honest, even if you don't show up, we are prepared to attack. This time, we determined the two secret party clans but we could only choose one. But since that you have decided to come, we won't hesitate,' AG replied

After continuing the discussion in further details with AG, Garen closed his notebook. The words he wrote at the top were slowly starting to fade away, so he left it on the study table.

He walked to the study room window, and looked down.

The outskirts of Berlin's night sky was filled with stars of yellow dots. Away from the city, the white beam formed from the bright searchlight swept across the sky; he could vaguely see the reflections of both sides of streets on the Spree River.

This bungalow was situated on a high location, just enough to overlook most of Berlin's night view.

A few moments later, the notebook on the table moved slightly, without a single wind blowing.

Whoosh...

As the subtle page flipping sounded, the notebook suddenly stopped on the last page.

The area that was originally empty was now filled with dense writing.

'Wellington Clan: There are 3 upper level elders, 13 middle levels, and 492 lower levels. The number of vampires was still unknown. As secret party's newly entered clan, Wellington was originally under the light party, but they abandoned most of the clan's peripheral forces. In its top ranking clan, the ones who are able to fight are one of the elders among the upper level, 7 of them in the middle levels, and you can ignore the lower levels. Our aim is to use the time when Wellington himself is resting to snatch the Blood Breed clan's Hallow Blood Statue. Once it is in our hands, we will launch a full-scale attack - Leave this part to me. Your responsibility would be resolving other resistance forces. In between specific patrol alert measures, what you have to pay attention to is to cover up your breath, as well as light sensitivity. We have prepared the latest development of Lightless Cloak so there might be a way to avoid it…"

AG explained the details of the action below the page - The Wellington Clan's defense measure, patrol route, as well as any possible responses that would go against the reaction of the Blood Breed; whatever they needed to do to achieve maximum effect.

From his arrangements, Garen could clearly see that Garen must have another two capable assistants other than himself. At least their strengths were also at the upper level.

Chapter 697: Plan 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He remembered, the last time he parted ways with AG, that fellow was still with that girl whom he was still entangled with. It seemed like she might have been a witch.

In AG's planning, it was clearly demonstrated that he had the strength to destroy one of Blood's five-scepter-clan. He could see it from the way he planned it out.

The statistics and information were passed on for more than ten minutes before it ended. Then, Garen picked up the notebook and read.

At the bottom, the scheduled time, place, as well as the number of people they needed were recorded.

AG seemed a bit more relaxed with his arrangements. The only he needed was for Garen himself to show up. In fact, he already had quite a lot of things to handle here.

Such as training seed scholars; these students would serve as the first official disciples of Holy Fist Place. The speed of a few among them was quite fast, and with the help of the Soul Primer, they had reached the standard level of typical martial artists. Even though most of it was boosted with the help of Garen's Soul Primer, but credits must be given to their efforts and understanding towards the subject.

Training students, observing Nadia's qi under suppression, and search for the new masks. On top of that, he had to make arrangements for his sister, Arisa, and more. He could not allow them to stay here all day, especially for Arisa and her people. Garen felt that Isoras and Arisa were the two key figures influencing the overall situation of the world. To put it in simple terms, being with them, one would never be in a situation without trouble. Just like a certain dead student on Earth, although they had not reached the point where there was a murder everywhere they went, at least it was a typical mess.

Yet the most troublesome one between the three of them was Nadia - he would never allow her position fall. So far, according to Garen's contact with Nadia, she still does not have all her strength. The Army Level of Endor had a lot of strong fighters, and even up to now, they had only used projections to attack again and again for three days. But her projections only had the strength to project less than half her body. However, the terrifying thing was that this strength was only counted as her first life performance. With the true core of her Nine-Headed Dragon talent, her ability of eighty-one lives did not even activate once. Every time she dies, her strength should double up, according to the most basic body strength as a standard measurement. Once her eighty-one lives had come to its final form, all energy of her eighty-one final form would then be compiled, which would be equivalent to Nadia now but with eighty-one times of the strength.

That was her true strength, and it was what worried Garen the most.

He went to the secret room, took out the Demonic Book that was in a dark divider, and returned to the study room to sit down.

Without the lights, his vision was clear enough for him to read the words on the Demonic Book under the dim moonlight, just as if it was daytime.

He picked up the pen again. So far, there were already records of the countless Secret Techniques he had remembered from the Book of Demonic Secret Techniques. He even wrote down some of the proper secret techniques. In the end, he was enchanted by the Demonic Book which had become a powerful Demonic Secret Technique.

Until this moment, he had already covered 89 percent of the essence of Secret Technique in this book - all the Secret Techniques he had seen, practiced, and fought before. Everything was recorded at the top of the book.

The remaining ten percent of the content was for the toughest areas.

That was the Living Secret Technique.

No matter if it was Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, the Hellfrost Peacock Technique he was currently practicing, or even the other types of Demonic Living Secret Techniques such as Flame and Metal that were kept in his memories, he still could not figure them out.

Hence, he could only note down, step by step, his own understanding, and truth to it.

The Demonic Books increased as its content increased. It had been constantly changing since the black ink in the beginning, and to the faint glowing dark gold luster now.

Garen lifted his pen, and slowly wrote down a new Secret Technique at the bottom of the page: Han Jade Technique. But before that, he rearranged some Secret Techniques that were not the best. A lot of them were the ones he had practiced before, such as Red Jade Palm and Mammoth Secret Technique.

Regarding Black Water True Technique, he had recorded it down earlier.

During the recording process, The other Demonic Book in Garen's head was slowly changing as the surface glowed with a touch of dark gold luster.

This book had completely turned into Demonic Book. The rare technique method on the top could allow anyone who had it the power to change their own fate. The Demonic Book itself seemed to have produced a Soul Seed qi; for anyone who practiced the Secret Technique noted at the top, they would be able to achieve that Secret Technique very quickly under the influence of the Demonic Book if they had it for a long period of time. This, along with Garen's soul qi as a primer could be implanted to scholars as a reason.

'Soon… The Demonic Book would be completed soon. Then, you will be able to condense the second Soul Seed. By that time, maybe you would be able to reach a new level, and enhance your basic soul limit,' Black Sethe said with a hint of admiration. He admired Garen's spirit of constant growth, whereas he had lost this possibility.

"I can't seem to understand the Living Secret Technique seed, and the Demonic Book cannot be completely done without it," Garen shook his head slightly, feeling a bit disappointed.

'But this type of rearranging would be very helpful for your martial arts.'

"That is true too."

Without saying more, Garen devoted himself to continue writing.

　　***********************

After a couple of days.

The sound of delicate utensils hitting the plates rang continuously.

The white morning rays shot in through the window, and onto the table in the first floor of the villa.

Garen and his sister, Vivien, Arisa, and Isaros, along with Rob were eating their breakfast quietly.

The menu was oxtail stew with red wine, black ink cuttlefish, and Garen's favorite tomato cooked snails. Even though the dishes were simple, but the taste was authentic. This was also one of the main reason why Garen chose this mute maid, Marquilli in the first place.

"After resting for a few days, you should have recovered well? Garen radiantly looked at little Vivien. He knew that this girl had been enjoying these few days under the care of his people. Her face small face blushed red, and her mood was good.

"Brother, you didn't accompany us," Vivien pouted, and said unsatisfyingly, "What do you mean recovered well? My petite body has been hurt seriously. Without compensation, it will never heal…" This girl had thick nerves; she had quickly accepted the reality that her brother was a rich and powerful diamond bachelor. Furthermore, their family was not poor, and they lived under great conditions here. Hence naturally, she had gotten used to the life here.

These few days, she had been obsessed with the smart swimming pool that could add hot water. At the side, there was also a 3D projector cinema. Once some of the special features were switched on, there was still an additional feature of a massage and silver light flashes. Looking down from the second floor, it was like a mercury pool, glowing with countless silver spotlights. It was very beautiful - Rob made it just for little Vivien.

That guy loved to fool around. After a few trips here, he and little Vivien had been very happily fooling around together. He himself was about twenty-years-old. The age gap between them wasn't huge. Since he was young, he had been fooling around under the protection of his brother. When two people who loved to fool around were suddenly brought together, they hit off well; having such chemistry was rare.

"Where would you like to go today?" Garen lightly split the oxtail on his plate into pieces.

"To my private garden. I have a few jaguars there, as well as white pythons. Vivien wants to adopt a small leopard," Rob answered honestly. He doesn't know why, but since he and Vivien got together, he felt more and more guilty facing Garen - a kind of feeling as if he was facing his own brother.

"Beware of your safety, the Blood Breed might be making a move soon. Although the there is no possibility of you attacking first, it is better to take extra precautions," Garen advised.

"Brother, would you have some spare time later? Can you come with me?" Vivien pulled and blinked her narrow eyes at Arisa who was beside her. The latter's cheeks suddenly blushed.

Arisa was sitting smartly at the side, with her dark red curls falling down her shoulders. She looked exceptionally quiet with her dainty face as she bit her bottom lip. For a moment, she swept a glance at Garen. Under this situation where she was sitting opposite from him, this type of peeking could not be called a peek anymore but instead, she used a rather obvious and bold hint to show her attitude - she liked Garen.

Even Rob could not take this burning 'peak', but Garen still kept a calm and composed look. Suddenly, a sense of admiration arose.

"All of you can go ahead. I still have some things to sort out," Garen answered without lifting his head up.

However, he did not see the hint of disappointment flashed across Arisa's face.

When a bunch of them had finished their meal, and as they were about to leave the dining room, they came across a Nighthawk subordinate - a delicate and mature woman with black curly hair.

This woman was tall, but the strange thing was the silver mask she wore that covered half her face. It was only covering the lower part of her face, below her nose - people were able to see her gem-like, yet magnificently colorful eyes. Those pair of eyes gave people an incomparable sense of danger, like standing unprepared in front of a crocodile or rhinoceros that might snap anytime.

Regardless if it was Rob, Isaros, Arisa, or Vivien, they could all feel a deep chill in their hearts.

This woman… Was very powerful!

Unconsciously, Isaros put on her best attack posture; all the muscles in her body started to tense up.

As if the woman felt something, she swept a cold glance towards them. A scornful arc appeared at the edge of her mouth.

She lifted her head high, and proudly walked into the dining area. Then, she closed the door with her backhand. It was followed by the sound of the chair pulling outwards on the floor.

"Nasira, this is your Colson Fort," Garen's voice vaguely echoed.

Then, it seemed like the woman said something but no one could hear clearly. However, it seemed like the both of them opposed each other.

"Who are these friends of your brother's!" Rob now realized that he had completely put Garen into the position of his brother. He was starting to realize more as his understanding of Garen further developed. This Nighthawk King really possessed the power of terror. This was not just power, but his own strength. This quality of this terror was absolutely powerful, giving out a sense of overbearing respect.

His every world could involuntarily convince people; his body's aura and chi could easily coerce people around him that consciously made them listen to his orders.

Chapter 698: Plan 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I am not very sure too. My brother has been very secretive since he was young. Even my parents did not know what he was doing the whole day. He got better and better anyway, but this part never changed," Vivien was not very concerned about these things. She treated her brother just like Arisa, carrying a sense of blind worship towards him. Especially this time where she was brought back from life, she unconsciously depended greatly on Garen.

Rob nodded his head. To be honest, the information on Garen was simple. But just because it was simple, that was why it became very mysterious. Anybody who looked him up knew his development history. However, nobody understood how he acquired those terrifying killing skills.

"Enough of that, let's not think too much. Anyway, my value has been pushed to this side, let big brother deal with these things," Rob laughed.

"Who did you call big brother?"

Boom!

Vivien fiercely slapped Rob's lower abdomen, and said with a cruel face.

"I was wrong… I was wrong…" Rob quickly apologized, covered his stomach and left.

　　************

Inside the dining room.

Garen and Nasira sat opposite of each other. The table was already cleaned. On top, there was two piping hot milk coffee.

The rich coffee smell mixed with the smell of milk spread across the room, diluting the food smell that still hasn't left the room.

"As the Witch Leader of Dark Colors, why are you here if there is nothing happening?" Garen looked around the dining room's floor. He was not sure when a circle of thin black traces was spread all over the floor, forming a perfect circle that surrounded the both of their positions. He felt as if there was an inexplicable film of energy protection layer wrapping this place up, isolating the sound from the outside.

The relationship between Nasira and Garen had not always been great. If it AG did not hold them back in time the first time they met, the two of them would have beaten each other up. Only after another two meetings did their tension gradually eased a little, but their relationship still did not improve.

As AG's ex-lover, a natural absorbent, and an orthodox Witch against the opposition organization, Narisa was Darker Color's Witch Leader. Even though she had been suppressed by the forces of Lion Mother, her strength and power were still there. Moreover, her absorbent body type had an indescribable suppression towards unnatural powers.

"If AG didn't arrange for me to come because we are temporarily lacking in men power, do you think I would have wanted to come here?" Narisa said impatiently. She immediately threw him a black medal that she took out from her chest, "This is a token to enter the magical tool's enveloped area. Don't lose it, or else even if you become a Death Apostle, you could only hold on to your life for another two more hours."

Garen caught the medal, held it up and took a look at it. In the middle of the black triangle medal was a dark purple beetle; it looked like it was alive. Even when he plucked its leg, the beetle moved, proving that this medal was made from a real beetle.

"When we formed the Lightless Alliance, this medal was a symbol of the highest status. Now, only three of us wear this medal to represent that we are a military alliance. When there is trouble, we would send support to help each other. Is that a problem?" Nasira explained her eyebrows raised.

"Of course that isn't a problem," Garen nodded. His voice dropped as a faint sound came from the medal. The moving leg of the beetle's child suddenly stopped moving.

"Contract sealed."

Garen did not mind at all. No matter how much stronger he gets, he was on his own. Moreover, AG had helped him for a couple of times, and the sincerity he demonstrated was definitely not fake. This exchange was normal since he disliked the Blood Breed anyway.

Talking about that, the two worlds he was in before this were the same. He did not deny the power of an alliance to expand his own efforts. Suddenly, Garen had a thought that perhaps this was the purpose. Using whatever method regardless of the means, it did not matter if it was his own growing strength or the consequent of others' joint alliance. If he delayed his own growth timing, then he could not refuse.

What if this method changed? This was what my heart had decided, and among that, it would also reveal my habits and personality.

Garen's thought fleeted for a moment.

"Are you listening to what I'm saying?!" Nasira's frustrating voice was in his ears.

"Of course," Garen came back to reality.

"Operation time would take place one month after. The Wellington Household would also need some time to readjust their strengths. A few of them in the Middle level judging panel is on a mission to execute enemies, or either on a holiday. If we want them to come back without a reason, in terms of the inefficiency of these Blood Breed Household, we will definitely get some benefit out of this," When Nasira talked about efficiency, her mouth showed a trace of contempt.

She was proud and had a poisonous mouth, as if she could never see eye to eye with those whom she does not approve of.

In fact, other than the Death Apostle rank, there were only a few people in this world who could capture her attention. Among them were AG and Garen.

"We want all of them to be there. Otherwise, isn't it too troublesome searching for them one by one?" Nasira said casually.

"What about the operation details?"

"We will attack two Upper levels, and twenty of them from the Middle level. The others are up to you. However, your main aim would be destroying the Wellington Household's Silver Demonic Statue. That is Wellington's personal set up of a reality barrier. You can only break it with purely physical power," Nasira explained.

"Then pass it over to me," Garen nodded.

However, he knew one part of AG's terrorizing plan. This guy AG made the whole Blood Breed his revenge targets. He was nurturing a type of genetically horrifying monster that would go against the Blood Breed with his hundreds of years of knowledge. Most of the Blood Breed feasted on flash and ashes as food. Hence, this monster had been nurtured to a primary phase. For it, close to three hundred Vampires, and over ten of the flesh and ashes of the Lower level Blood Breed had been sacrificed.

AG named this monster as 'Sacrifice'.

"That is the whole situation. AG will let you know the further details, but I'll remind you of one thing: the Blood Breed Household has been around for over a thousand years. The accumulation looks very optimistic. However, if there isn't enough manpower when the time comes, don't say that I didn't remind you," Nasira said coldly as she stood up and stridden out.

The strange thing was that when she was at the confined door, she disappeared slowly and then she was gone like she shuttled over the door.

Garen kept his sight, and played the beetle medal in his hand.

　　**********************

The Wellington Household in a certain location, beside a certain pool.

"We received some news that the Witch from Dark Colors will be having her eyes on us."

A seductive girl with red-firey hair that fell to her waist, said. She was wearing a loose black silk pajamas, vaguely showing her naked body under it. She was lying lazily on a white oriental cane chair.

"Dark Color's Witch's Guild? What does this have to do with her? Those bunch of bastards is notorious. They would do anything for power, under any circumstances," A fool sat beside the blue-water pool, with a handsome yet beautiful face. She gave out a blue-haired silhouette that neither seemed male or female. Her voice was crisp and neutral; there was a slight bump on her chest, but there was Adam's apple on her throat.

"Who knows? Anyway, I got this news through the channel. I have no idea why those bunch of crazy people is keeping their eyes on us," The red-haired girl straightened one of her legs while one of her hands reached towards the small table for a cigarette that had a detailed black tobacco rod. She then proceeded to fill in the tobacco. With one single-handed brush, suddenly a flash of fire sparked and lighted the tobacco up, wisps of white smoke rose continuously.

The girl took a deep breath and slowly spit out a mouthful of smoke. The white smoke changed its shape in the air. In a second, it became a small and thin snake, circling around the girl, and slowly disappeared.

"This kind of life is really comfortable…" The girl moaned, seemingly lazier, "At first, I did not agree on jumping from partisan to partisan because it was just too troublesome. What is the difference between light party and secret party? They were the same anyway."

"You can't say it this way," The Blue haired person in the water said, "Even though Lord Castine is strong enough, but he is too softhearted. He is not a suitable candidate to lead my Blood Breed towards a great cause."

"That means, once your fight ends and after the light party is killed, what else is there to prepare for?" The red-haired girl asked.

"Of course it is for us to gain power," The blue-haired person replied.

"What about after you have gained power?"

"Then the best is if we could have a life!" The blue-haired person speechlessly rolled her eyes at her.

"Then isn't your life now good enough?" The red-haired girl yawned, "Nobody cares. You do whatever you like - you eat well, play well, drink well. What haven't you experienced? I think our life now is great…"

The blue-haired person was speechless, as if this girl had set it all up.

"Hence, why do all of you even fight so desperately to survive? You guys are real fools," The red-haired girl waved her hand and said, while she continued smoking her tobacco.

"You and I can't see eye to eye, Tu Lan," The blue-haired person said frustratingly.

"It is me who can't see eye to eye with you," The red-haired girl, Tu Lan replied lazily, "We are already at the Upper level. We still have thousands of lives or even more, so what else can't you enjoy? That's enough, let's not talk about this. But you should still think carefully on how to handle the Dark Colors Witch's Guild over this period of time. I have a feeling this will not be pleasant."

"What you're saying is that they might attack? That's not possible. We're Lord Wellington's personal commanders."

"Who knows what those crazy people would do?" Tu Lan's eyes narrowed, prepared for sleep.

To be honest, as an Upper level Blood Breed who had seen too many rises and falls; she had been alive for almost four thousand years. She had witnessed the rise and falls of the dynasty, the rapid development and sudden rise of modern civilization. She had seen the first and second world war, as well as participated in the history's famous Normandy landings. When Germany announced the war, she was a delegation of the alliance of victorious countries.

Success and failures - what is the meaning of it all? Even a stronger winner could not hold onto the loss time. Yet, Blood Breed had been standing at the victory point right from the start. On this basis, they still wanted to fight their own war. Weren't they just idiots?

Even if all the Wellington Household's Blood Breed would die in front of her, she could just continue living elsewhere and enjoy her life. The things that could excite her became less and less. As the third most horrifying existence in the Upper level Blood Breed, even with the Dead Apostles, she would rank seventh in the world.

However, no one knew. She could now feel that there would be a breakthrough sign soon.

She had already succeeded the pinnacle of Upper level for thousands of years, but once the breakthrough happened, maybe she would become the latest Death Apostle. Seeing those fellow Upper levels who were struggling to break through the border and still could not improve, she would occasionally imagine. Maybe it was that radical, yet full with desire mentality of hers had blocked them from moving forward.

"Haih… That's very lame"

Chapter 699: Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

One month after…

Hoot...

A faint horn sound could be heard floating in the night sky as if spirits were howling. But it also sounded like a low hum of a certain animal.

Clang...

A man with tall and strong figure opened up the grass bushes in front of him. He looked left and right as he immediately tightened the black gun in his hand and walked forwards.

This man was wearing a black body-hugging leather suit. He was also carrying a leather bag - his whole body was covered with a layer of protection. On both sides of his waist, he carried two matte black holsters.

The moonlight shone down from the sky and fell onto the man's back. It light appeared in a faint, pale white color.

After realizing that there was nothing wrong, the man continued to walk forwards. However, there were countless men and women with robust physique walking behind him. They each carried a single-sided headset that blinked red, and they each wore reddish glasses that on their face. On the glasses, you could vaguely see the moving data on the lens.

These people carried long sickels in their hands and swiftly cut down the surrounding grass. It opened up a piece of empty land that would allow the group behind him to move forwards conveniently.

"Nothing found. Everything seems normal."

"Nothing found. Everything seems normal."

Voices reporting the situation rang out continuously. In the dark forest, there were many flashing red light spots. Every one of these light spots represented a person. With such dense light points in this forest, it meant that there were at least over a hundred of them.

A single miniature car was driving slowly in the woods. The car was black, with a blood-red flying bird pattern on the surface.

Impressively, a bald John was sitting in the car. His figure was two feet taller than the rest, with a body full of muscles. He wore a brown tight strap; from his shoulders to his waist, his strap was packed with dark spiked daggers. And surprisingly, these daggers did not have a handguard.

In the forest, the trees here and the ones in other places were different. Each tree stood tall and straight. However, only one person surrounded was as thick and tall. The gap in the middle was exceptionally big.

John held a cigarette between his mouth as he annoyingly looked towards his left and then his right.

"Lord Hunting General, we will be approaching the destination soon. So do we still want to continue moving forward?"

A sound came from beside John. It was a young girl with gold hair who was wearing the exact same red glasses. She greeted him with a firm salute before she spoke.

John laughed.

"Continue of course. Why not? We are the front line soldiers. What else is there for us to take care of? Since we are here, they must have already known that we've arrived."

"But do we need to wait for the large forces waiting behind us?" The girl said with embarrassment.

"Wait for them? Wait for them to grab the first power?" John jumped down from the car with a loud boom, he even dug a small hole in the floor with his heels. His weight was so heavy, it was frightening. It was as if his whole body was made out of steel. With his weight pressured on his feet, he would dig out a deep hole underneath every step he took.

He waved his hand.

"Let the explosives team prepare!"

He quickly walked towards the front and separated the crowd who was blocking the road. Using the moonlight, John walked to the edge of a slope and looked down.

Outside the forest, down below the slope, a humongous silver oval estate was clearly printed into his eyes.

There were four large silver statues around the estate. Every statue was at least ten meters tall, like they were four small buildings. There was a connection of walls between the statues that was in a shape of a circle. Below, there were groups and groups of people patrolling the place.

"This is the destination. We would want to break through the door at the side of the mermaid statue," John smiled, "Immediately report this to the authorities. Say that the enemies are personally attacking us and that we have to attack back! Let the explosives team go first to give them a huge dazzle. Hahaha!!"

"But, the team behind us are still not here…"

"Didn't you hear what I just said?!" John turned his head over. In his eyes, there were faintly smoke traces of red.

"Yes!" The girl could only follow his orders obediently.

John could faintly hear a horn sound from the air.

His face revealed a nasty yet horrifying smile. Since he had been with Marshall Dahm, this was the first task that involved in such huge operations. Moreover, he was allowed to vent freely and was given the permission to do what he was initially prohibited to do. This made him very excited. As a gangster who killed and tortured by nature, this operation was very tempting, like a hungry wolf walking into a pig's pen.

Peng! Peng peng peng!

Within seconds, the periphery of the estate below lit up with a bunch of fake flame and fireball. It looked like a bunch of orange-red balloons that expanded and shrank. It ignited the land that surrounded the estate.

Suddenly, faint noises of people escaping and screaming could be heard from the estate. If they had people with amazing vision here, they would be able to see clearly. In the midst of screaming and shouting, suddenly a black shadow was seen flashing across the estate. It then floated towards the direction of the hills where John was at as if it was effortless.

"Kill!! Hahaha!!" John fiercely held up his hand, and was the first to rush down the hill. To one's surprise, it was like the ancient times where they charged forwards without carrying any guns or machines.

After a few of their own rockets shot out from behind him, the faint light from the cave reflected the blood on his face.

　　****************

On a hill that was far away from the estate, three white helicopters were parked on a wide field beside the forest.

The surrounding was thinly spread with people masked with white scarfs who were holding guns. These people had in their hands some assault rifle, and waist grenades. Each one of their bodies let out a smell of fresh blood.

Immediately, beside the helicopter stood three silhouettes of different aura.

Garen wore a white open-chested white coat, showing off muscles on his chest. His golden hair fell onto his shoulders, and he wore a black mask on his face. Both his hands were held in front of his chest as he stared quietly at the two other people who were beside him.

"My men have already reached the periphery. Are your side of the arrangements ready?"

A cold laugh rang out.

"Of course they're there. But since your men can't wait and they have already rushed forwards to start the fight, whoever that is killed or hurt will not be my responsibility anymore."

The one talking was a skinny old man who had a gold scarf wrapped around his head, and supported himself with a walking stick. On both sides of his legs, two bloody-eyed male lions lied on the ground. However, he was donned in a white robe. From afar, he looked much weaker than before.

"AG, how did you end up with such a face that looked like you are neither a ghost or human?" The one who spoke was Nasira. This girl was also wearing a white dress, though she was impatiently wearing her own matching earrings. This time, she already wore the left side of her earing; it was a dark gold Eiffel Tower that was only the size of her fingernail, but it reflected a dim gold light under the moonlight.

"It's just a small breakthrough," AG answered plainly. However, his normal voice seemed to carry a hint of sharp laughter. It gave people chills when they heard it.

Garen leaned onto the helicopter, and looked at his watch.

"In ten minutes, my commander-in-chief will arrive at the battlefield."

"My shadow army are done with their set up," Nasira satisfyingly pressed her pendant as she spoke.

"I am also done preparing. My men are now on the north side fighting alongside Nasira's men. I estimate that they can hold on for another ten more minutes. The silver statue is your responsibility now, Garen," AG looked at Garen with a straight face. But even with his serious tone, he gave people a feeling as if he was showing a strange grin.

Seeing as Garen nodded his head, AG raised one hand into the air.

Suddenly, a ripple appeared. In front of the three of them, a dark red map lit up. The name that appeared on the top took Wellington's estate as the center.

The estate was a huge red origin. Whereas the surrounding was filled densely with large amounts of green light dots. These green light dots were split into three parts that surrounded the estate.

"What is this witchcraft?" Nasira asked.

"This is not witchcraft, this is the new research tool. The whole system is projected with virtual imaging," AG answered smoothly.

He pointed at the estate's red dot.

"Wellington must be done with his preparation, to prevent our attack but they would not have expected us to have enough manpower. According to intelligence, the strongest of the Wellington Household, Tu Lan has already retreated to their secret underground cave. Only the old and weak ones are holding up the fort in this estate. There are still some of them with more potential. The newly recruited team of the Middle level judging panel are all in there now, and there are two old Upper levels who have yet died."

"We have thirty minutes to sort out this entire Blood Breed. If not, the secret party will send everything they have to help when they receive the news," AG said in a low voice, "Thirty minutes is all my magical tool can take to defend the Death Apostles. I would have to rely on you and my two babies for the rest."

Boom!

In a distance, red lights burst from the direction of the estate, and then towards the side of the sky.

"It has started," AG smiled, "Let's go and try it out."

The three of them each boarded one of the three helicopters. The propeller started turning at high speed, and slowly lifted off the ground, flying towards that direction.

While Garen sat on the plane, he looked down at the view.

"Where is Dahm at now?"

"He is already fighting with the Wellington Household. Among his Four Hunting Generals in the front-line army, three has already started the attack. But they only have with them the lower grade cannons so the losses are a little…"

Nighthawk's computer genius, Angel was sitting on the plane. This woman had a thick foundation and eyeshadow on her face as her fingers quickly knocked onto the keyboard. The computer screen flashed by so quickly that it was hard to see what it was.

"Having losses are normal. Our opponents are not human. The losses are still in an acceptable range."

Garen nodded. This time, he had brought his own men. Most of them were from the mercenary's periphery, which meant they were Nighthawk's periphery. They had no problem using high technology and advanced combat weapons but with those vampires that were piling up, they were not afraid of dying. Only then, it was obvious that they did not have enough manpower. That's why his true subordinates were only three people: Dahm, Xander, and Quentin.

All three of their Waterbird Fist had reached level three and above. Moreover, this time would be Dahm's chance to redeem himself from his crimes - all process command would go through him. This bastard had commanded many wars of annihilation. His talent in fighting was very strong, and he was an expert in this field.

"The opponent is very strong. According to the information that Lord AG shared with us, the opponent has put in at least a hundred Vampires, and dozens of Lower level Blood Breed," Angel's voice was slightly shaking. This was the Vampires that were told in legends. If they could fight with a living thing in a legend, nothing could be compared to this battle, no matter what."

Garen nodded.

In fact, Dahm's strength had already reached a horrifying stage in the Upper level. As Garen got an upgrade, so did he. Because of the ancient Soul Primer qi, Garen's upgrade affected Dahm's and Nasira's own strength, giving their strength a boost with a stronger Accumulation.

As a matter of fact, the most horrifying thing of Garen was also the most horrifying thing of the Living Secret Technique. Those subordinates who were contaminated by his soul would be able to enhance their strengths along with his and strengthen themselves.

If Garen's attribute quality becomes stronger, his soul subordinates would also become stronger along with him.

Black Sethe had mentioned this a lot of times - an indicator of an Army Level…

The so-called Army Level was named as army meant that one person had the ability to influence the whole army, not just himself who had the strength to defeat an army.

This was the indicator of an Army Level, but actually, Garen was still miles away from achieving this Realm. He had only ever practiced the Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, and because of the enhancement of this evil technique soul seed, these signs started to slowly show in him.

As a result, the enhancing part completely relied on the strengthening magnitude of the evil technique seeds.

Looking down at the huge groups of men, it was as if an army was surrounding such huge grounds.

"Dahm wouldn't have mobilized the local troops directly, would he?" Garen frowned.

"More or less," Angel nodded her head, "Marshall Dahm used the bandits as an excuse, and have secretly dispatched the cheetah of this mountain division. However, he was mainly responsible for artillery training; our men are still at the front of the palace. But Commander, no matter how well our men train, they are still a normal human. I'm afraid that attacking from the front would cause us too many losses.

"It doesn't matter. Just keep an eye out of the distance between us and the Blood Breed Household."

Garen slowly said, "If we do not experience the storm, this fight would still happen sooner or later anyway."

Garen attentively sensed the soul seeds that he sprinkled down individually, with an addition of the first batch of them from the combat club, as well as the second batch of scholars. Altogether, there were more than thirty of them. All these people had either a high status, rich background, or had shocking potential.

Along with the enhancing of the soul seed, it was as if they had gone through a small change. Their strength had a certain degree of amplification.

Chapter 700: Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

‘The indicator of an Army Level is when a core Warlock has enhanced a level of strength. The commanding army, in the case where they are not superior compared to him, could share the same increase of strength with the same increase in strength level. This was the indicator,’ Black Sethe explained, ‘A true Army Level does not only have a tough individual strength, but also a strong subordinate support, just like Nadia. Her Nine-Headed Dragon Army had demonstrated strong strength in many battles. Furthermore, they shared some of her own strength. However, they still lost badly in battles and in the end, they perished.’

“This is the true Army Level?” Garen suddenly realized. No wonder the Warlocks are so tough. With this strong core army under them, and as the core expanded, then they could form countless powerful and incomparable terrorist armies. It would be a matter of course that this kind of army would definitely conquer a lot of territories.

However, you felt that his own strength had increased from an average of two or three points to an average quality of seven points. His strength increasing span was very powerful. After all, he mainly relied on the Slaughtering Hand during all the fights before, and now, all he relied on was his own strength.

With this kind of enhancement, not only would it double up, but instead, it would simply improve by multiple times.

However, it seemed that Dahm’s and others’ enhancement barely even increased by a level. Originally, their Aura strength could only reach the Middle level. Though this time they achieved the ranking of an Upper level, it’s still not stable.

Then, he found that those subordinates who had achieved the Upper level were only Dahm and Hochman. The rest who at the top of the Middle level were Quentin and Xander. Those in the normal Middle level also included that Asian girl, Cece who just recently returned to the combat club. Unexpectedly, this Cece was an Asian Battle Vein Inheritor who had practiced swordsmanship. No wonder, in the beginning, she did not show any panic in combat club. Garen was the one to give her some help behind her back. Hence, she officially joined combat club’s deep operation recently.

After that, there were the Lower levels, and they were few and far between. There were only a few of them – Nighthawk’s Baldy, Angel, as well as few of Dahm’s and Hochman’s strongest subordinates.

Baldy and others were mainly because they lacked Shooting Shadow Secret Skill. Although it was made up after that, they still could not compare themselves to the top Princes and Princesses, who had large amounts of resources to help them. But compared to them, they had very rich battle experiences.

That was why, as a Lower level, they were able to fight face to face with the Blood Breed, which could be comparable to the top levels in the Mercenary.

But with such strength to confront the entire Wellington Family, only higher level strength would be able to see through them. It would be too appalling for the lower levels.

“This battle against the Wellington Family; on one hand, it’ll be a symbol for us, Holy Fist Palace to demonstrate our strength, and on the other, this is to end our last conflict,” Garen said simply, “AG and the Dark Colors Witches are unwilling to stand behind the scenes. If that is the case, then we should take advantage of it too. The Witches are on their guards while watching the Blood Breed’s civil war from the side. This is our chance to grow.”

“I understand,” Angel nodded.

In the North side of the estate, the mist in the forest was heavy. In the darkness, it was as if a ton of knights, riding on their black war horses were slowly moving forwards.

From time to time, the black war horses would spurt its snort, but there was no trace of white and hot air.

Looking down from the trees, the whole forest was dense that one would not be able to realize that there were hundreds black Knights.

“Mystical Mist Knight, the Dark Colors Witches really did set off the trump card… This Wellington is in trouble now.”

Somewhere on a tree branch that was hundreds of meters away from this forest, there were two looming silhouette above the ground. One of them had an ant-like voice, which seemed to be a girl.

“Looks like this Lightless Party can’t restrain themselves, taking the advantage of rising when this is chaos. But this is our chance. The more chaotic it is, the better,” The other man said in a low voice, “If one of the three Secret Party Household is wiped out tonight, then that really would be a big issue that would reverberate the entire Blood Breed.”

“Impossible. This estate of Wellington’s was only a bait. Moreover, the other two Households will not watch them as they get wiped out. The show has just started,” The girl laughed lightly.

“Barney’s two Household has been detained by the Light Party, but support can still be sent over. Bloodshed and white machete will come over. Only then, it is time for a show.”

“You were the one who reminded them?” With one listen, the man knew it was the girl’s writing.

“Of course. Lord Scarlet Moon was killed, and Lord Ashen is trapped. They ruined our Light Party; we suffered a heavy loss. The Secret Party should pay the price too,” The girl’s tone carried a hint of bitterness and determination.

“Be careful, an expert is coming!” The man violently pressed the girl’s head down. Suddenly, the both of them vanished into the darkness. They were completely invisible.

Below the branches, two black horses were walking down slowly.

There were two Knights speaking softly on top the horses. Both of their black armors were different than the other knights. They seemed to be the only ones in the group that made noise.

The one on the left had a figure of a black heavy armor, but two points of blue lights could be seen vaguely under the black helmet.

The other was a young girl who was carrying a machete on her waist; one of her arms was broken. Only an empty sleeve was floating in the air.

The girl’s brows shot upwards with her sharp eyes, giving people an aura of a cruel and cold wolf. Her long black hair was tied into ten small braids, like an ethnic style.

“Manasi, I can’t believe that you came here yourself. I thought you were still repressed in Morchon Underground Palace.”

The girl’s voice was like the wind, carrying a hint of whistle in the air.

“Even yourself is here. What am I supposed to do in the Underground Palace?” The black knight who was called Manasi answered. His voice was like putting countless electronics into one. It was very weird.

“The attack timing is three minutes after. Estimate it yourselves. Maybe other Households will come to assist. I need you to defend the outsiders,” The girl said directly.

“What about your men?”

“My men will attack from the east. Those humans are coming in from the front of the south side. But I suspect that they will not be able to break through the gate,” The girl laughed coldly, “We cannot fail our master’s goal. I will personally coordinate this.”

“Leader gave me half an hour. So after half an hour, I will not let my sisters sacrifice themselves without a cause. Don’t blame us if we leave you guys aside.”

“That is fine.”

The two of them continued forward, and very quickly, they had disappeared from the forest.

The two lurking silhouette in the branches reappeared.

Both their faces did not look happy.

“That was close… We almost got exposed! It was the black knight Manasi, and that Thousand-Legged Serpent who had surprisingly increased in two Upper level ranks… I did not think that they would come over. More so, they are now related to the Dark Colors Witch!”

“We must report this to our Lords.”

**

East side.

The silhouettes in black cloaks each carried firearms. They surged into the estate and fought into one with the red-shirt Vampires.

A pool of blood constantly exploded in the ground, forming marks on the floor.

The black cloaks and vampires were like two groups of black and red ants that gushed out crazily, and tangled onto one another. As the firearms were shot in close proximity, bullets were not shot out. Instead, black water arrows were shot out. Once these water arrows fell onto the Vampires’ bodies, it would quickly corrode into a big hole, dripping out large amounts of white fluid. Whereas the men in black cloaks were continuously tackled by the Vampires, then biting into them as food and ripping their veins out.

In the center of the battlefield, two silhouettes – one black and the other red – were fighting with such quick speed. Occasionally, half a black card was spurted outwards that stuck out fiercely into the ground. Then suddenly, one after the other, holes with white fluids exploded. But at certain times, red blood was spurted outwards too; this black-shirt man was also injured.

“Kill!” The black-shirt man shouted so fiercely that the wolf’s fangs necklace he wore suddenly lit up a white halo.

With a sneer and taking him as the center, a white halo was suddenly spread out into a circle that expanded rapidly along the ground. The surrounding Vampires that touched the ring of halo became stiff. Their bodies quickly turned white. Very quickly, they were turned into white fluids and collapsed onto the floor.

The red silhouette was also hit violently by the halo. To one’s surprise, as if it was hit by certain substance, it immediately flew outwards, letting out a sharp cry.

“Aioria!”

In a split second, red shadows sprang out from the side, joining the battle circle to attack the black-shirt men.

Again, three were fought into one. It seemed like the black-shirt man could abuse the use of his halo as it required a lot of energy. The red shadow was heavily injured by that attack just now. The war was now at a deadlock

****

Chi!

Chi!

Chi!

Dahm’s face twisted into a huge smile. He flew forwards with great speed. With every step he took and as he brushed his hands outwards, fresh blood would spurt out onto his body.

Every Vampire that passes him would explode all of a sudden as if there were mini bombs placed in their body. With a thump, they all would turn into a cloud of blood mist.

Under half a minute, only a few dozens of Vampires were left from the hundreds of them on the battlefield.

A burst of fanatical cheer rang out from the entire battlefield.

“Dahm! Dahm! Dahm! Dahm!”

The Mercenary army shouted as they fearfully, yet respectfully raised up their weapons. Some who were abnormal lifted, tossed and shot the Vampires that only had half a body left and were still alive.

Hahaha!

Everywhere was filled with the smell of blood and crazy laughter.

Dahm rejoiced by opening both his arms wide, enjoying this wonderful and sweet smell.

“I am Dahm! Dahm Galahad! Come! Enjoy all these deaths. Death is the start of everything!” He chanted out loud.

Whoosh!

At this moment, a group of huge black shadows was heading over from the front with a dramatically empty sound.

When everyone could clearly see the group of black shadow, they couldn’t help but gasp.

Surprisingly, that turned out to be a huge iron ball with a few meters in diameter. The black iron surface was contaminated with tons of bloody stuff. It had already killed a lot of people.

“Giant rock Aruda…” Dahm opened his mouth, and revealed a merciless smile.

“You are right. You have come to provide support indeed…”

In a moment, he jumped out fiercely, but his body was stuck to the ground. As a lightning swept below the iron ball, the red air around his body suddenly diffused outwards. Then, he headed towards the mysterious shadow behind the iron ball.

“Die!”

Countless spirits, as if they were a bunch of dark red snakes, let out a hissing of a breath and strange sound, biting at each other.

“Hehehe…” The same cruel people laughed in a low voice. In the dark, only his pulling eyebrows could be seen, as he opened a red and bloody eye.

Chapter 701: Battle 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Clank!!!

Arudo wielded two short daggers in his hands. He braced the daggers in front of him, blocking Dahm’s unstable aura.

The red aura and the daggers clashed with each other as the harsh scraping of metal against metal rang out.

A few parts of aura was sliced off, which promptly vanished.

Arudo wasn’t a member of the Wellington Household but an elder of one of the secret household. He’d once ruled the whole Europe for hundreds of years and no one could overthrow him. He’d gone silent at the end, so no one would have expected him to appear here.

This man was in a black shirt with two white leather strap forming an X in front of his chest. After blocking the aura’s attack, he rolled as he was pushed back by at least ten meters.

The giant metal ball automatically moved with the chains as he pulled on them. It flew back to him and landed just beside his body, forming a crater.

“Dead Waterbird Fist – Nightfang!”

A red figure instantaneously passed above his head. Just like a bird flying in the middle of the night, the red wings fluttered as the figure let out a gentle and crisp chirp.

Chirp!

Two hidden and soundless streams of aura impaled Arudo’s shoulders through his armpits. At the same time, Dahm flew up, made a turn mid-air, tumbled around as he glided and landed at least ten meters away.

As he landed on the ground, hundreds of streams of densely packed aura seeped out of Dahm’s body like poisonous snakes and slithered towards Arudo.

“I’ve heard that there are a few elites from the humans. I didn’t expect them to be at this level. How disappointing…” Arudo smiled, revealing his white teeth.

As he faced off against the countless aura streams, he kicked up his right leg and sent the giant metal ball flying up, which collided with hundreds of streams of aura. With one hit, most of the aura streams were dispersed, leaving behind only a few streams that had managed to slither past the metal ball’s landing site.

He pulled out two fingers and moved lithely at lightning speed. The remaining aura streams were then detonated mid-air.

As an upper-level Blood Breed, Arudo possessed an overwhelmingly powerful physical attribute. He had pushed his Blood Breed body to its extreme limits, and his speed, strength and regenerative power were off the charts. Only his hypnotic skill wasn’t as powerful.

The difference between an Upper-Level Blood Breed and the other Blood Breed was that they could pull other beings into their illusions and their prey wouldn’t be able to escape from it. Although Arudo was weak in this aspect, in return, he had a strong immunity against illusions.

A few streams of aura hit the tree trunk at the side and holes were pierced into the bark as if a bullet had shot through them. Arudo’s power was alarmingly high.

Dahm’s expression finally looked more serious.

He reached out his fingers and licked at his nails. His nails were stained with red and some of them had even turned purple. One would wonder just how much Blood Breed’s blood had stained his hands.

Those that had died in his hands were not comprised solely of vampires. There also were tens of Blood Breeds that had attempted to ambush him. There were lower-level and even middle-level ones. If not for his cruelty, Arudo wouldn’t have come out in person.

“Is this the true strength of an upper-level blood breed? …” he inhaled deeply and smirked as blood flowed out from the side of his lips. Then, a strange thing occurred. His hair started to turn blood red as if his hair was being coated with a layer of blood.

He had created a Secret Technique that suited him most based on the highest level of Two-Faced Waterbird Fist. The Death Waterbird Fist had started to show its real strength.

“Waterbird’s Profound – Bloody Flower Outline!”

As he shouted, Dahm instantaneously shot forward by tens of meters. As he lunged forward at great speed, a clear red line formed behind him. He placed his hands in front of his body and afterimages of them started to form. These afterimages formed into tens of petal-like red shadows which resembled a strange bloody lotus. As he got closer to Arudo at great speed, the lotus in front of him started to blossom.

A strong and evil energy started to leak out from the bloody flower.

Arudo laughed crazily as he threw the metal ball at him. However, as he was very agile with his skill activated, evading it didn’t pose much difficulty.

Arudo wasn’t surprised. He started to leap forward, planning to face him head on!

He opened up his hands as he tried to grab his opponent. At the same time, his right knee was slightly pulled up as he aimed for Dahm’s pelvic area. His actions were so smooth that it seemed like a natural reflex. Surprisingly, Arudo was a top-tier wrestler.

He unleashed his true strength in this instance as the wind gusted while he tried to capture his opponent with his hands. The muscles of his body moved about like mice. He, who was nearly two meters tall, literally looked down on Dahm, who was almost a head shorter.

Both of them, one black and the other red collided against each other once more, forming a bloody aura mist.

Hochman had a coat draped over his shoulders. He was in a black suit and was slowly moving two alloy metal balls in his hands, which produced high-pitched clanging noises.

With a pair of gold spectacles on him and an invisible earbud in his right ear, he raised his head and stood straight in front of the big sculpture at the entrance of the Wellington Manor, admiring it. Behind him, there were at least ten of his most elite subordinates.

Some were strong and muscular while some were small yet beautiful and golden-haired. There even were a few dwarves smirking as they gently stroked the guns in their hands.

The white sculpture was a giant knight from the mythical Centaur clan. It was holding a huge weapon which resembled a shovel. It had no shirt on, revealing its strong muscles. The sculpture was at least ten meters tall, rivaling a small building. It stood proudly in front of everyone.

Hochman analyzed the sculpture and realized that there was a void area in the horse’s abdomen that people were able to enter.

There even was a small black door for accessing the void. However, the door was already opened and blood was oozing from it and could be clearly seen on the white stone floor.

“Looks like someone else had arrived before us,” Hochman observed calmly. He had taken the opportunity to come here while Dahm and the Upper-Level Blood Breed Arudo were battling against each other. It had been a timely opportunity to bring his elite team to ambush while the Blood Breeds were paying attention to the three-way battle. However, he didn’t expect other people would’ve had the same idea as him and arrived before him.

“Let’s go.”

He led the way to the tiny door.

Following tightly behind were three of his strongest subordinates. Similar to Dahm, he had also found three elites among the elites as his subordinates to fight against Dahm’s Four Hunting Generals.

They were the Three Sharp Crosses, his strongest subordinates. It consisted of one very strong and muscular gigantic man and two golden-haired beautiful twins.

The three of them had been personally trained by him. Although they did not possess as much combat experience and talent as the Four Hunting Generals, they were very agile in fighting and killing and were also able to use Hochman’s Extinction Waterbird Fist. This made them overwhelmingly powerful as they could increase their strength and speed in a very short amount of time.

As they approach the door, Hochman immediately stopped moving as a gun was fired at the door frame right in front of him, sparking it in the process.

He’d immediately sensed it when the bullet was fired and avoided it by a centimeter.

“Kill him,” the dwarf behind Hochman smirked as he held a knife in his mouth and entered into the shadows with more knives on hand.

Soon, a few cries and moans could be heard from within the darkness. Then, gunshots and laughter could be heard.

“Let’s go. The dwarf will handle everything,” Hochman seemed rather confident in this dwarf.

The group of people didn’t seem to be worried at all as they entered through the small door.

As the Holy Fist Palace’s main army, they were responsible for the missions related to fighting and obtaining the Blood Breed’s Treasures. They had the responsibility to not allow the other two parties to obtain it first.

After they entered the tiny door, they arrived at a narrow corridor. The invisible glass skylight had been shattered into countless shards. There were a few black piles of ashes by the corner and it was obvious that these were the ashes of Blood Breeds or Vampires.

One of the golden-haired twins walked towards the ashes, picked up some of it and sniffed it.

“Lower-Level Blood Breed. Looks like some strong ones have entered before us.”

Her memory astonished everyone as she had already memorized and could easily differentiate the scents of Vampire, Lower-Level and Middle-Level Blood Breed’s ashes in such a short amount of time.

“We’ll pick up the pace,” Hochman nodded.

There were a total of six people in their team, namely Hochman, the twins, the strong man, one of the two dwarves in black guava hats and the other one who had been left behind. The dwarves seemed to be brothers.

The remaining five continued pushing forward. As they passed through the corridor, they arrived at a blood-stained white jade fountain square. It was oval in shape and wasn’t really big. However, blood stains and ragged clothes could be seen everywhere. The air was filled with the stench of gunpowder and blood.

“The smell of the blood is right in front of us.”

One of the twins whispered.

Hochman raised his head and looked at the other side of the fountain, where the streetlights were blinking as if they were about to go out at any moment. There were three slender ashen men were standing underneath them.

The trio was all in dressed in the same ancient black formal attire and each had a silver flower pinned on their lapels as decoration.

The leader had his hair pulled all the way back, hair oil had been applied to enhanced its reflectiveness and hair gel had also been used to keep it in its desired form.

What made everyone wary was that he was holding onto a twitching corpse with his right hand.

Slam.

He threw the corpse directly onto the ground in front of him.

“Welcome to the Garden of Blood.”

Silently, a huge swarm of black smoke slowly spread out behind him and clouded the surrounding air like ink in water. It spread out in such a way that it appeared to be alive and sentient.

Hochman squinted through his spectacles as he released a rather threatening aura.

“Weidi? What a surprise, it’s another fellow not from the Wellington Household…”

In this world, there were less than a hundred Upper-Level Blood Breeds and they weren’t found just anywhere. In addition, among these Blood Breeds, only ten to twenty of them were able to maintain their true strength at all times. To be able to encounter so many Upper-Level Blood Breeds here could only mean that the Secret Party had decided to focus their strength here. It was obvious that there was a spy who had leaked this news to the Secret Party beforehand. Since they couldn’t ambush them, they could only resort to attacking them.

Chapter 702: Battle 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Hochman stopped playing with the ringing steel balls in his hand and lightly tossed them to the subordinates behind him. What was strange was that his palms had the same brilliance as the steel balls, and making them look rather inhuman.

“We have been waiting for you for a long time,” Weidi stomped on the corpse in front of him, “This guy is the so-called elite from the Lightless Alliance and I can’t believe he stealthily came here to gain some advantages. What a stupid man.”

Before he could finish his sentence, Hochman slammed hard with his hand.

Bam!!

The black shadows surrounding him were abruptly shoved away from him. He then grabbed one with his hand and smashed it into the ground.

Boom!!

Fresh blood erupted everywhere.

The black shadows stopped moving and started to turn into black dust.

Hochman stood up casually as if he did something meaningless.

“Invisibility? Interesting.”

His action in that instant made Weidi so stunned that his pupils had contracted. The black mist around him had stopped spreading and was only covering half of the area. Furthermore, it was the smaller half too as the area had been occupied by an invisible force field.

His pupils started turning green.

“Who exactly are you? Why do you have such power!”

Hochman’s expression didn’t change as he slowly walked towards Weidi. As he moved forward, with each step he took, two green lights would flash mid-air near where he walked. What would then appeared were black-shirted human figures that were originally invisible. These human figures were frozen stiff as they floated in the middle of the air and each of them was maintaining a strange pose as if they were unable to move out of it.

Boom.

In an instant, the first black-shirted human figure exploded and turned into black ash that drifted to the ground. Then the next boom could be heard; it was the second body. Then the third, the fourth…

Wherever Hochman had been, the hidden invisible Blood Breeds near him were revealed and frozen mid-air, unable to move. They then exploded into ashes one after another.

An inexplicable and vicious shadow slowly changed its shape behind Hochman. The shadow behind him was no longer in human shape and what replaced it was a horrifying giant beast with sharp horns. The shape closely resembled the dragons from the folklores of the west.

A calm yet powerful oppression spread from his body. With his every step, the shadow’s occupied space cast by Weidi and his members was further reduced.

Perhaps even Garen couldn’t foresee that Hochman would be able to break through the middle-tier upper level and get close to the peak of the upper level when Garen had increased his strength. Even his soul was faintly similar to that of Garen’s, which meant that his soul possessed the overwhelming aura of the incomparably powerful Nine-Headed Dragon.

Ahh!!!

Weidi shouted with all his might and two white sharp fangs suddenly appeared in his mouth. His body bent and he instantly teleported behind Hochman as he attempted to tear into his neck.

Hochman reacted by giving off a green light from his body as if he was covered with a layer of greenish, glowing fluid.

Suddenly two white scimitars stealthily ambushed Hochman from both sides, as if there were two other Blood Breeds as strong as Weidi attacking him at once.

One had to realize that Hochman wouldn’t even allow an ambush to come this close from a typical Blood Breed of Lower-Level and Middle-Level.

However, these two scimitars made it. They came out of nowhere and seemed to draw very close to Hochman’s skin.

“Waterbird’s Profound!” Hochman’s eyes instantly lit up and a shapeless whirlwind appeared around him.

“Dual Blade!!”

In that instant, the area was filled with white sparks that could blind someone temporarily.

Blood was trickling down his arms and dripping down onto the black dirt in a green field. The blood was immediately absorbed into the dirt, leaving nothing behind but soil that was slightly red.

Dahm opened his mouth wide as he panted while staring at Arudo.

His situation was dire; his right arm had been destroyed and a big chunk of his left arm had been torn so badly that blood was flowing out profusely.

On the other hand, Arudo who was before him had half of his brain blown out. However, defying logic, it was recovering at a normal pace. What was inside his skull wasn’t something that resembled a brain but similar to his other parts of the body. It was filled with red thick matter which moved around.

The newly recovered Arudo looked equally battered. His shirt was covered in holes from when he was hit by Dahm’s Waterbird Fist and had exploded innumerable times.

The metal ball on his body had broken into multiple pieces nearby onto the ground, while both of his swords had also broken into multiple pieces as it stuck onto the dirt. So many cracks scarred the blades’ surfaces that they could no longer be used or they would immediately shatter.

His body was equally bad. The vertical eye in the middle of his forehead was an indication of his strength. It would reflect his current strength like a thermometer. When he was at his peak, his vertical eye would be red in color. However currently, it could hardly open it and it looked very sick and pale.

“My Blood Breed talent is unlimited regeneration. Dahm right? Let’s see how much longer you can last!” Arudo managed to laugh as he mocked his enemy. Although he had obtained the information of his enemy beforehand and knew that the opponent was no normal human, he only realized how truly powerful this human Dahm was! Unexpectedly, he was able to fight on equal ground with an Upper-Level Blood Breed who had lived for thousands of years. He was simply incredible!

Eventually, a strange anxiousness started to dwell within him.

The Blood Breeds who were busy with their civil wars weren’t that interested in the Holy Fist Palace that was gaining momentum in strength in the human world. They thought that no matter how strong humans could be, they would always be weaker and could pose no threat to a Lower-Level Blood Breed. Now that he had witnessed their strength…

“How long I will last?” Dahm laughed loudly as he heard what he said, “Look around you.”

Arudo was slightly surprised as the Four Hunting Generals had started to spread out and weren’t even worried about their battle. There were only a few subordinates left who stood far away as they set up an instrument with unknown purposes.

Suddenly, he could hear the churning of a helicopter’s propellers approaching from afar.

“Could it be…!!??” His pupil instantly contracted as he thought of a possibility.

Underneath the manor in a certain dark room.

Three black figures were gathered together at the center where a pillar resembling a trophy was placed. The pillar was only half a person tall and had a basin filled with blood on top.

The blood was slowly rotating and the reflection on the surface was as good as a mirror as it displayed the situation outside.

“The other two households’ people have all arrived. I didn’t expect the Lightless Alliance to be so powerful. Luckily we left a few men in case of any unexpected event,” a neutral tone sounded.

The other two was staring at the situation flashing within the bloody basin and didn’t utter a single word. The atmosphere was rather intense.

“It’s that old man AG… I knew it was him!” a hoarse voice came from a black figure.

What flashed across the basin was AG’s pale and wrinkly face. Two of his golden lions had transformed into lion head humanoids and were fighting against some Middle-Level Blood Breeds. Meanwhile, he was strolling towards the manor with his cane in hand, under the cover of numerous greenish-black bats. No Blood Breed could halt his advance.

However, what was strange was that once he had reached a certain area, green smoke started to appear underneath his feet. It seemed like there was something blocking his path and he couldn’t proceed further.

“He’s here for revenge,” the last black figure said lazily, “I’ve told you guys not to participate in this earlier on and you guys ignored me. Now we have to face this troublesome man.”

The other two didn’t respond at all. Although they sound very confident, each Blood Breed’s sacrifice, be it a Lower-Level Blood Breed or Middle-Level Blood Breed, greatly pained them. It hurt them so much so that the pain could be described as stabbing their heart again and again with a knife.

“What’s the current loss?” one of them asked lazily.

“Thirteen Lower-Level teams and we have five remaining…” the hoarse voice responded softly, “We sent out ten Middle-Level Blood Breeds and only one has returned. However, we do not have to worry about this and the issue isn’t our household’s alone but the collective decision of the entire Secret Party. The leader has promised us to compensate for our losses. As long as we have enough Blood Essence, we can produce more Middle-Levels and Lower-Levels and recover our losses. As of now, the leader is very interested in the humans named Dahm and Hochman. He has requested us to capture them at all cost. The leader is very interested in the root of their strength. This root, this so-called Secret Technique has piqued the leader’s interest.”

“Indeed. This Secret Technique has enabled Hochman and Dahm to achieve the strength of an Upper-Level within just a few years. If we were to spread this to the mass…” the neutral voice said softly. Suddenly, the lazy black figure jolted and couldn’t hide his shock.

“A few years? Are you sure they only spend a few years of their time? Instead of a certain Witch’s branched cult?!!” the lazy tone had started to wake up.

Then, the blood in the basin started to boil as if there was a fire underneath it. The Blood started to boil rapidly to the point white vapor started to form. Even the situation inside the blood was no longer visible.

“It’s time,” the hoarse voice sounded rather excited. Although Blood Breeds’ emotions were neutral most of the time, it didn’t feel good watching their Household’s strength decreasing over time.

“Let’s begin.”

The three black figures each reached out one of their hands and pressed down on the protruded corners of the bloody basin.

A strange mosquito-like buzzing started to sound. It wasn’t coming from the three of them but from within the bloody basin.

The boiling in the basin stopped and the blood started rotating once more just like before. However, the vortex was slightly different as the eye of the vortex was deepening and its speed had increased. It kept going down to the point where even a black light could be seen glowing slightly.

At the same time, from the bird’s eye view at the top of the manor.

With Wellington’s manor at the epicenter, the surrounding area of hundreds of meters started to tremble as layers of invisible walls started to emerge from the ground. These walls created by the members instantly separated the attackers, forming a huge invisible labyrinth.

As the horse neighed, while the Mystical Mist Knight was battling against the powerful Blood Breeds who had blue battleaxes in their hands, they were separated by the invisible wall. Immediately, the Blood Breeds took the opportunity to knock at least ten knights off their horses.

AG, who was standing on the field, slowly looked up at the moon in the sky. It was strange as the moon was as red as blood through the invisible wall.

“So this is… the Holy Labyrinth?”

Chapter 703: Gruesome Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Holy Labyrinth…

What a farfetched item.

At the North, Nasira was wearing only one pristine white leather glove. She actively moved her five fingers as she tried to get used to the comfort of the glove.

Occasionally, people in black cloaks with guns in their hands would appear beside her and rush towards the manor like killing machines without fear. They then would fight against the remaining Blood Breeds present.

“The rumored Holy Weapon of the Blood Breed: ‘The Labyrinth’ had completely disappeared from the previous Blood Breed’s civil war and hasn’t appeared in many years. I didn’t expect it to see it here…” Nasira looked up at the blood moon in the sky. She didn’t seem to be worried about a holy weapon being activated.

The activation of the Holy Labyrinth had excited all of the Blood Breeds; their bodies had turned black and some of their eyes had even turned red. Their fangs and claws had lengthened and their strength and speed both increased by at least threefold.

In an instant, the stalemate was broken and the Lightless Alliance started to lose ground on all three sides.

Nasira’s side was especially bad, as a huge group of soldiers and horses had been separated from the main force by the Labyrinth and were unable to continue their attacks. The Mystical Mist Knights could pass through physical matter temporarily, which meant that they could attack if they pervaded through the walls. However, they weren’t able to permeate through this invisible labyrinth and could only be trapped hopelessly within a channel that didn’t even span 1 meter wide.

With the manor as the epicenter, cries could be heard in all directions.

Nasira gently tugged on her glove. Seeing that she had lost a considerable amount of her Mystical Mist Knights, she finally walked forward slowly. She raised her gloved hand and touched the first layer of the Labyrinth’s wall.

Sizzle…

The invisible labyrinth’s wall started to melt as if it had come in contact with an extremely corrosive substance. The wall immediately degenerated and a huge hole was quickly formed. Nasira then strode through the hole.

At this point in time, both the Lightless Alliance and Blood Breed had suffered greatly. Two hundred of the Mystical Mist Knights that Nasira had brought along were trapped within the Labyrinth and couldn’t escape. In addition to the previous losses, there were only about ten of them left struggling while being surrounded by the ever-increasing amount of vampires.

However, Nasira acted as if she didn’t see the situation; she fought off the underlings, corroded the invisible walls and walked further in without any hint of concern.

“Leader!!” the remaining knights panted. They were surrounded by the vampires whenever they weren’t careful, and some of them had fallen off their horses. The leading young witch wiped off the blood on her face and attempted to escape on her horse.

A thud could be heard as she collided with the labyrinth’s invisible wall and fell from her horse. The vampires which had surrounded her started swarming over her. These vampires had been ordered by the Upper-Level Blood Breeds and had long lost their minds, and all that was left of them was their husk and feasting ability. They had already turned into the rumored devouring vampire corpse.

After a few cracking sounds that sent chills up everyone’s spines, what was left behind at the spot where the female knight fell were a few tattered rags. Even her bones had been devoured.

Nasira did nothing but sigh.

“This is a necessary sacrifice. My sisters, the Mystical Mist Knights, please rest in peace.”

“With such a huge sacrifice, what if the plan still fails…?” a voice came from behind. It was a tall man in a full heavy body armor. Two blue flames were glowing under the helmet and his face couldn’t be clearly seen.

“Manasi, have you cleared your side?”

Nasira asked softly.

The two of them then went further in.

“I’ve temporarily bound them with the Top Formation. This is so troublesome. I believe a few major households from the Blood Breed’s Secret Party are here. The situation is slightly worse than what we have expected,” Manasi whispered.

“However it’s still within the plan, no?” Nasira replied softly.

The two of them soon disappeared into the night as they walked into the manor.

The helicopter descended slowly.

Garen frowned as he jumped out of the cabin. As his black leather boot landed on the ground, his shoes sank into the bloody field below. The field was completely covered in fresh blood.

A few elites from the Nighthawks jumped down from the airplane. They stood together with him as they looked at the huge battlefield at least ten meters away from them.

It seemed like there was a huge invisible cover that had restricted the battlefield to a dome. The battle had entered its final stage and the winner was evident, considering the number of ash piles present on the field.

The people Garen had brought along had either escaped or killed by the vampires. What was left was just a huge amount of vampires piling together in a circle as if they were attacking someone.

“This settles it. Mortals with firearms are no match for the vampires,” Garen crouched down as he dug up some dirt and sniffed at it. Most of it was the blood of the humans and it carried just a faint hint of the Blood Breeds’ scent.

“This is something that cannot be changed,” Angel whispered from behind, “The natural talent of the Blood Breed is too great and it is not something that we can hope to catch up to in such a short amount of time.”

“Where’s Dahm and Hochman?” Garen asked softly.

Angel adjusted her spectacles as she read the data.

“Lord Dahm is currently in front of the forest to the right and he seems to be fighting against a Blood Breed as of now. Lord Hochman has already gone deep inside and seems to be surrounded by a huge amount of Blood Breeds. However, judging from the probability of him being alive, he shouldn’t be in grave danger.”

“This is the first cleansing,” Garen said calmly, “Those who manage to survive are worthy of bearing the name of the Holy Fist Palace,” he glanced coldly at the elites around him.

“That goes the same for you guys.”

“Yes!”

The Nighthawk members immediately replied with their heads down.

Angel adjusted her spectacles as she read out the data.

“According to the overall intel, there are a total of six higher ranking members who have gone out to fight and that have been held off by us. There should be only a few Middle-Level and Lower-Level non-combatants inside and we should need about…. Wait!” Angel’s expression changed for the worse, “There seems to be a new gathering point appearing. It’s from the underground!”

“Impossible! Wellington and the surrounding Blood Breed elites are all here. There shouldn’t be any other elites appearing!” a Nighthawk elite was in disbelief.

“The instrument doesn’t lie,” Angel’s face turned pale, “Captain, there’s a new unknown force gathering together in front of us. There’s something interrupting my scanning so I don’t know what it is.”

“What’s their power level?”

“Undetermined.”

“How about the overall size?”

“Indeterminable as well. The enemy has the latest jamming device,” sweat started to appear on Angel’s head.

“Isn’t this interesting?” Garen smirked and didn’t seem to be worried at all, “If everything is determined from the getgo, I don’t even need to be here.”

He then slowly walked towards the huge Holy Labyrinth.

Everything was a test for Garen. He was using the Blood Breed to test the Holy Fist Palace’s strength.

AG had set up a huge witchcraft nearby and was currently sapping a huge amount of fresh blood and life forces. A strange black gas started to appear from the air and ground.

Garen reached out his hand in an attempt to grab hold of the black gas but the black gas evaded him as if it was alive and hastily swam far away like a fish.

“Looks like it’s a success,” He smiled, “Next up, we will have to see whose trump card is more superior.”

The battle between the Lightless Alliance and Blood Breed had reached its final stage.

With the activation of the Holy Labyrinth, it meant that the battle was nearing its conclusion.

Dahm was struggling with the endless amount of vampires that tried to kill him. Explosions would happen each time he pushed off the surrounding vampires. However, the ashes didn’t give up and kept going after him like starving wolves.

On the other hand, Arudo had already hidden in the forest at the side and could no longer be seen. He was like a venomous snake, hidden inside the dark corner waiting to strike a lethal blow.

This gave Dahm a huge amount of pressure.

This was the first time.

This was the first time he felt anxious fighting against someone who was not Garen.

Furthermore, the loss of blood made him annoyed. It was as if his annoyance had been incensed by the idea of him losing too much blood.

Black figures kept revolving around him as a huge group of vampires was killed by him, and they kept producing a strange sound. Their eyes were red and it was obvious that they had long been hypnotized by the Upper-Level Blood Breeds and the only order they had was to kill their enemy even if it killed them.

“Blood Breeds… These damn bastards!!” Dahm looked very barbaric while drenched in his own blood. His makeup and attire were not as glamorous as before. His vision had started to turn muddy and he had spent most of his aura as he fought with Arudo. Now, he could only struggle with his basic skills.

“You can’t escape,” Arudo’s voice came from the forest, “As a Blood Breed, I commend your strength but unfortunately, a human will always be a human. You’ll always be flawed and this is the reason why you lose.”

“Shut up!” Dahm scolded. Then, a scream could be heard nearby. It was one of the Four Hunting Generals. His eyes twitched at every loss from among the Four Hunting Generals; it pained his heart greatly as they were his loyal subordinates!

“Look around, your subordinates have been surrounded again. The holy weapon shines upon us and we’re back to full power. You guys, on the other hand, will slowly feel pressured physically and mentally,” Arudo said coldly as his voice kept reverberating in the empty field.

Pew!

As Dahm wasn’t careful enough, a black shadow from the vampire swift passed his hand and a huge chunk of meat was bitten off.

He screamed as he held onto his hands. Now that both of his hands were severely injured, he could no longer exert any force from it and blood had seemed to stop flowing out as well. He had already lost close to thirty percent of his blood. If not for being a Martial Adept who could shrink his muscles to drastically reduce the amount of blood loss, he would have fainted from excessive blood loss ages ago and be shredded into pieces.

As Dahm finally lost his means to defend himself, Arudo came out with a perfect third eye from the forest.

The Bloody Arudo! He who represented the Upper-Level Blood Breed. One of the rare few that could fight a good war. He looked at the surrounded Dahm while thinking of a way to develop his descendants. Even though this would make him lose some of his blood and reduce his overall strength, this person right in front of him was still rather valuable.

Chapter 704: Gruesome Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“If you wish to live, I can convert you into my descendant. How about it? You’ll be immortal and possess incredible physical characteristics such as speed, strength, and regeneration. Time will no longer be a threat to you…”

“Shut up!” Dahm shouted as he started to laugh while being surrounded by vampires.

“Idiot! You don’t even know how terrifying Teacher is. If you kill me, the Holy Fist Palace will definitely avenge me! Your friend, your household will be completely destroyed!”

Arudo’s face turned foul and his body turned into a black line as he went past all the vampires and appeared right in front of Dahm.

Thud!!

Arudo punched Dahm directly in his chest. The thud resembled someone hitting against rubber and Dahm was sent flying.

“Kill? Destroy? You’re going to die soon and your teacher, the guy from whatever Holy Palace didn’t even come to your rescue. How dare you threaten me when you’re on the verge of death?!” Arudo was furious. The surrounding vampires had been ordered by him to stop attacking. Arudo was the only one attacking now.

“The is the inner region of the Holy Labyrinth. The more powerful a non Blood Breed is, the more restrictions he will face. Are you still hoping that Garen to come and save you? This is the first time I’ve met someone that’s this dumb,” Arudo rushed towards him and gave Dahm a firm kick in the abdomen and he was sent flying once more.

Cough cough cough….

It took Dahm some time to push himself up. His face was covered in blood and dirt but he had an evil smile on his face. He didn’t seem like he had given up at all.

“As long as I’m alive. Eventually… Eventually…!!” he stared at Arudo very sharply.

About seventy percent of Dahm’s bones were broken and he would need to force himself to even twitch.

Ever since he practiced the Waterbird Fist, he had obtained respect and strength he’d never had before. People who had a taste of power, wealth, strength and excitement would never become someone’s servant and beg again!

Dahm’s eyes turned red as he teetered on the verge of losing his mind.

Boom!!

Hochman defended himself with his hands as he blocked a punch from the stone statue in front of him.

He groaned as the pavement underneath his leg sunk in, forming two deep holes.

The stone statue’s hand was three meters wide and had no effect on Hochman’s hand when it attacked him. It was as if it had attacked a very solid wall and was blocked.

Half of Weidi’s body had been torn apart and he was holding himself up against the wall, watching the humanoid stone statue summoned by the Holy Labyrinth attack Hochman.

“This is a very small portion of the holy weapon’s true strength. You can’t win against it.”

Inside the square, Hochman’s party had only four people left as the two dwarves had been turned into bloodied meat piles. The twins’ legs had given way and they had fainted as they fell to the ground. Lastly, the giant with scars all over his face was barely holding himself up as he was attacked by the stone statue.

There were at least ten stone statues in the area and all of them had appeared out of the blue from the dark areas of the manor. These white stone statues were dressed in heavy armor and were about seven to eight meters tall. They looked like the giants of the legends.

Hochman’s suit had been torn apart, revealing his upper body filled with muscles. His skin was as black as obsidian, with a metallic sheen.

He glanced at his surroundings and started smirking.

“Although I don’t know what you’re planning, it no longer matters.”

In an instant, he retreated as fast as lightning by at least ten meters and was approaching the manor’s main gate.

“Don’t you dare escape from me!!” Weidi was stunned and immediately shouted, “Block him!!”

As soon as he shouted, Hochman’s body stopped moving as if it defied physics. His body halted at the side of the door and he could no longer move backward and out of it.

Suddenly, a strange bloodied humanoid figure appeared between the entrance and his body.

The humanoid seemed to be made entirely of fresh blood. It had no face and hair but maintained the shape of a human.

The exit behind Hochman was completely blocked by it.

As this humanoid appeared, Weidi and the other Blood Breed gave sighs of relief.

“The Fresh Blood Statue!! It has finally appeared!!”

The bloody humanoid reached out its hand. Although it looked very slow, in reality, its speed was terrifyingly fast as it pressed onto Hochman’s back.

Boom!!

Hochman flew away as if he was hit by a train. The muscles underneath his singlet sunk in as he was sent flying like a cannonball to the ground by the square, forming a crater which was half a meter deep.

At this point in time, the whole square was filled with craters and it no longer resembled what it originally looked like.

Ugh!

Hochman could no longer hold it in and vomited a mouthful of blood.

“We should stop moving forward for now,” AG stood just in front of Garen as he stared at the manor which had become quiet, “The Blood Breeds have activated the Fresh Blood Holy Weapon, the Labyrinth, and the statues. Our witchcraft has been affected by it and we need time to adjust it.”

Garen started frowning.

AG looked at him.

“There’re only ten minutes left before our plan is completed and two of the Holy Weapons are currently in their prime time. When the witchcraft is activated, their potency will reduce drastically and they will be unable to deactivate them as well. As long as we are able to obtain the two major Holy Weapons from the Blood Breeds…” greed started to flash across his eyes, “They will definitely know that we have been aiming for the Holy Weapons from the beginning.”

“The Silver Light Demon Statue will soon appear and will enter its weak period after ten minutes. It’s all on you after that,” AG said in a serious manner.

Garen ignored him as he turned his head and looked at Angel who was behind him, “What’s the current situation inside?”

Angel and a few people were busy tuning a sophisticated black instrument. It looked like a mini satellite receiver and would beep as turned while it was being tuned.

Sweat was dripping profusely from her forehead and she didn’t even have the time to wipe them off as she kept staring at the huge amount of data through her spectacles.

“Dahm is in serious trouble! Lord Hochman is in a slightly better situation than him but he has been placed in a difficult position. Something really strong seems to have appeared inside!” she immediately replied.

Boom!!!

Suddenly, the ground started to raise up in the center of the manor, between the buildings. It was as if the ground suddenly erupted halfway, forming a strange protrusion.

Kaboom!!

There was another explosion and the protrusion finally exploded.

Countless amounts of dirt rained down, plopping down all over the manor and surrounding districts.

“The Silver Light Demon Statue has finally appeared,” AG said with a nostalgic tone as he looked at the explosion in the center, “The Wellington Household’s strongest weapon, nicknamed the Realistic Apostle. It would require three peak-tier Upper-Level Blood Breeds to be able to barely summon this overwhelmingly powerful weapon of warfare.”

“How long more until I will be able to enter?” Garen asked.

“Eight minutes more,” AG responded immediately.

The manor started to clear up from the explosion as the dirt spread away, revealing the core object that had caused the explosion.

It was a silver humanoid statue which stood five meters tall.

The statue was completely silver in color and seemed to be made out of a silver liquid. It had a pair of angelic wings, but instead of having normal human hands, it had a pair of sharp claws just like the vampires.

As soon as the statue was formed, it immediately looked in AG’s direction and started to move its wings. Then a sharp chirp could be heard as the statue instantly disappeared.

Boom!!

When it reappeared, it was in front of AG and Garen, only about ten meters away from them!

However, it was this distance that restricted the Silver Statue’s attack. The ground was lit up by countless blood-red textures. At the same time, a strong force gathered and landed on the Silver Statue’s surface, oppressing it and causing its movement to slow down.

“How much longer?” Garen asked once more.

“Five minutes. Soon.” AG started to frown as well.

“Lord Dahm is in critical danger!” Angel shouted out of nowhere, “His heartbeat is dropping drastically! It’s no good! Same goes for Lord Hochman as well!! His spleen is broken and his head is severely injured!!”

Garen was suddenly in a bad mood and started to walk towards the Silver Statue.

“Garen what are you doing! We still have another five minute before the Silver Light Demon Statue is at its weakest! If we go for it now our plan would be destroyed and the Blood Breed may even retract their Holy Weapon!!” AG was stunned and immediately blocked his path.

“Move away!”

Garen’s body slowly expanded and his muscles on his body started to buzz as he kept expanding.

“It’s only two subordinates! If the plan is successful I will give you as many subordinates as you desire! I want you to calm down! Right this instance!” AG shouted.

Buzz…

Garen replied by inhaling deeply.

Just like a huge whale swallowing the sea, Garen’s chest sunk in deeply and he let out a deafening shout.

The fine buzzing sound spread all over his body once more, and it turned black from head to toe, giving off a metallic sheen.

His big yet solid muscles looked as though stones had been embedded in his body.

“My disciple can only die by my hands!”

Garen’s voice seemed to have changed as it now contained a thick and horrifying tone. It was similar to one shouting into a valley, that produced multiple echoes.

Boom!!

A solid raging aura spread powerfully with him at its epicenter. The wind blew so hard that Angel and the others couldn’t stand straight, and even AG had to take a few steps back from his tremendous aura.

“Calm down!!” AG shouted.

“Waterbird’s Profound.” Garen’s voice rang through the night and into the distance and echoed deep into the inner region of the Holy Labyrinth.

“Soar!!!”

As Garen roared, a sharp chirping sound could be heard.

Chapter 705: Awe 1

The sky darkened as the ground trembled.

Chirps were mixed into Garen’s intense roar and it resounded even in the deepest parts of the Holy Labyrinth.

Garen then pulled his right hand back, and a vortex started to form as the air swirled on the ground while he aimed at the Holy Labyrinth in front of the manor.

He then released the attack.

From afar, Garen’s body looked like he was inside the abdomen of an invisible giant bird. The moment he threw his punch, the giant bird moved.

It spanned its wings and flew forth.

AG reacted swiftly in an attempt to block Garen’s attack. A golden hoop which looked like some sort of a wristband flew from his hand and stopped right in front of the giant bird’s beak.

A clear explosion could be heard, but the golden hoop was as weak as an egg. The golden hoop didn’t even last for a second before it was shattered into gold pieces as it was touched by the giant bird’s beak. The golden pieces flew about, interrupting AG’s next action.

A gully of a few meters deep had been formed in front of Garen, piling up an immense amount of black dirt which formed into a giant circular pillar. It was then sent towards the Holy Labyrinth.

Clang!!!

A deep ringing sound resembling a giant bell ringing could be heard, and a white supersonic soundwave spread about.

Garen’s fist landed firmly on the Labyrinth while his fist was filled with a unique high frequency that only a Secret Technique possessed.

Crack!

A small crack instantly appeared on the Holy Labyrinth, which started to multiply in every direction.

The cracks instantly propagated tens of meters up into the sky. It was as if the walls of the holy weapon had spread towards that region.

Boom!!

In just a moment, a hole had been created through the gigantic Holy Labyrinth.

Garen’s fist turned into a black soil column which looked like a black thorn. It pierced through everything as it stabbed towards the deepest region of the Labyrinth.

What accompanied the black pillar’s piercing was an overwhelmingly powerful shockwave.

Layers of Labyrinth broke into huge pieces as if they were made out of glass.

“The Labyrinth!!!… It’s broken….!!!” AG stopped moving his hand and unconsciously, his mouth opened wider as each second passed.

Dahm slowly closed his eyes as Arudo’s steel fist shot towards his head like a cannon.

“Die!!!” his rage-filled shout reverberated in his ears.

He could feel an immense pain in his head. It was the sense of crisis before the opponent’s fist would come in contact with his head. However, he had no more energy to move about.

Then, the strange roar appeared right beside his ear as if it’d leaped through space and time itself.

“Flight!!! …”

Yes… It was just like a water bird which gently touched the surface of the water before flying up into the sky.

“It’s teacher…” Dahm was unsure why, but he became very calm as he watched the fist getting closer to him. The slightly black skin, the solid fist, and five sharp Blood Breed nails clenched together.

“Have you given up?” a voice wondered deep within him.

Give up? Why would he!

He was a person that was going to surpass everyone!!

Dahm, struggling with all his might, used his last ounce of strength to open his mouth as he attempted to bite at Arudo’s fist with his teeth. However, he then realized that Arudo suddenly stopped moving as if a tape recorder had stopped rolling. He stood quietly as his fist was only a few centimeters away from his face. However, it felt like it would take forever for him to go across this distance.

Buzz… A slight wind blew past.

Arudo’s body started to collapse as his body started to turn into fine ashes that were blown away by the wind.

A familiar yet horrifying figure appeared behind Arudo out of nowhere. What was strange was that the figure was slowly disappearing, as if it was just an afterimage.

“The final profound of the Waterbird Fist… Flight…” Dahm seemed to have understood a lot of things. His eyes twitched and he fell to the ground on his rear.

As his laugh trembled, the vampires which had surrounded him started to turn into ashes while maintaining their posture.

Hasty footsteps could be heard from the darkness a distance away as Nighthawks uniforms and the lights of the signal swiftly approached.

Hochman was barely able to stand firmly. He stared at the Fresh Blood Statue with blood all over its face standing a short distance away. That statue’s body was made out of constantly flowing viscous fresh blood, but it could move around freely as if it was a living human being. It had no face and no hair. It did, however, possess simple maneuvers that could kill off anything.

The enemy didn’t seem to plan to kill him but wanted to severely injure him so that he wouldn’t have the strength to defend himself.

“The Fresh Blood Statue, a killing machine that is automatically created near the Silver Light Demon Statue. Although its strength can’t be compared with the Silver Light Demon Statue, it does possess regeneration and defense that is superior to the Blood Breeds. It’s the perfect counter to you humans who possess incredible strength with very little regeneration ability.”

Weidi, whom Hochman had been beaten as though he was a dog, had completely recovered. Furthermore, he was even blessed by the Holy Labyrinth as he kept recovering the spiritual energy and Blood Essence that he’d previously spent.

Without changing his expression, Hochman pressed onto his wound at the side of his abdomen. His spleen was broken and had a serious hemorrhage. However, he’d noticed them and pressed onto an acupoint to delay his injury. Currently, his most critical issue was not his severely injured body but his brain.

In Hochman’s vision, it seemed that a few additional Fresh Blood Statues had appeared. His vision was muddy and dark. This was either due to the excessive loss of blood or the attack from the Fresh Blood Statue possessing some sort of poison.

He shook his head as he attempted to clear his vision. Unfortunately, his vision had become even muddier.

Suddenly, a group of Fresh Blood Statues appeared and had encircled him. All of them reached out their sharp claws at the same time as they aimed for his chest.

Hochman at the time was in a daze. He was motionless as he stood while raising his chin as if he was looking at the night sky above.

“Do you hear it?” he muttered, “That’s the sound of the waterbird…”

The Fresh Blood Statue’s sharp claws pierced into his chest and drilled in between the lukewarm muscle and bone.

Then…. It just stopped moving.

The statue that did not possess any face, too, started looking up into the night sky.

“What… What is that!!?” Weidi raised his head as he looked above the manor. His face was filled with disbelief and terror.

Up above the manor, there was a huge bird that was as big as, or even bigger, than the Silver Statue flying towards it. It spanned both of its wings as it pecked at the Silver Statue’s chest.

The huge bird was half transparent. Its inner parts were filled with countless white airflows and a huge amount of black dirt. These two ingredients had merged together and made the huge bird very realistic.

The huge bird’s wings were as wide as the legendary supernatural Phoenix’s as it dragged its long tail.

Hochman knew of the shockwave of this move. He had seen Garen using this simple high frequency trembling technique but he’d never seen its true potential.

The Two-Faced Waterbird Fist Technique’s Final Profoundity — Flight.

Its full name was the Flight of the Evil Phoenix!

It was a horrifying fist technique derived from the West Phoenix Fist. It was also one of the strongest profoundities of the Two-Faced Water Bird Fist Technique ultimate technique.

Perhaps other people were unable to hear anything strange, but those who had practiced Secret Technique could hear the sharp chirp of the Phoenix.

It was the howl of the wind and it was the sound produced by the strongest technique of the Waterbird Fist!

The Blood Breed’s holy weapon, together with the Wellington Household’s strongest warfare weapon — the Silver Light Demon Statue versus against the Holy Fist Palace’s Two-Faced Waterbird Fist Technique’s Final Profoundity — Flight of the Evil Phoenix.

In an instant, a gold light so bright that it blinded anyone appeared as these two bodies collided with each other.

Hochman was unable to open his eyes after he’d automatically closed his eyes. However, his vision was still filled with bright gold light. The gold light was so bright that it could pass his eyelids and glare into his eye receptors. It was the strongest excitement he’d ever felt.

The sound frequency was so high that his ears could no longer pick it up. All he could see was a circle of solid grey shockwaves bursting from the golden explosion as the core spread about hundreds of meters around the region.

Hochman was on the verge of collapsing as his ears and eyes were bleeding profusely. The blood flowed down from his cheeks, leaving four trails of red blood.

Weidi, on the other hand, was on all fours on the ground as he grabbed tightly onto the edge of the crater. However, it was all futile as his body was pushed back by the shockwave, leaving a trail of marks on the ground.

The Fresh Blood Statue seemed to melt away slowly like a candle. It turned into a huge amount of blood and started to vaporized into a bloody mist before disappearing into thin air as the ground trembled while the golden light bathed onto it.

After some time.

Hochman slowly woke up from unconsciousness. Every inch of his body was in pain and he could no longer move.

His vision was muddy and could only see very little.

Amidst the confusion, he tried to open his eyes wide as he attempted to look at his surrounding.

He then started to hear clear and rhythmic footsteps. From his muddy vision, he saw a strong and horrifying figure walking towards him.

“Teacher…” he moaned.

That figure was ferocious and huge as black smoke kept surrounding his body. That black smoke was the aura that he recognized as it moved about like a living being. It spread about in the area, forming into shadows of dragon heads which looked greedy and cruel.

He then felt that he was being lifted up.

“Bring him back and treat his wounds,” that man finally spoke and Hochman was finally at ease. He could no longer bear it and passed out.

Chapter 706: Awe 2

Garen stepped on the ruins of the countless estates and when he looked around, he could see that large pieces of silver statue fragments were scattered everywhere. They were silver in color but were more likely to be made out of a high-tech alloy than the precious metal. Occasionally, the remnants of some sophisticated circuit appliances could also be seen.

Wisps of black and white smoke were floating around the estate, and some areas were even on fire.

Garen was bare from the waist up, and the horrifying muscles of his body were like black metal armor that twitched with every slight movement while encasing his entire body.

It looked like the armor of a human machine, one that could morph constantly. He did not look human at all.

The final form of the Waterbird Fist was the improved version of the West Phoenix Fist —— the Flight of the Evil Phoenix. The reason why it was called Evil Phoenix was due to its terrifying lethality; this level could no longer be considered as a proper technique but an evil technique. It was why Garen had made it the Waterbird Fist’s final form, included it as a secret technique, and written it down as the final version in the demonic book. The Flight of the Evil Phoenix that was written in the demonic book would be a benchmark for the power of the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist.

He glanced at the miserable estate once again.

All the walls had collapsed, and the remains of the building were not over a meter in height, and he could no longer tell the artifacts apart from each other; everything had become piles of different colored dust.

With the exception of Hochman, Dahm and all of the beings who have trained the Waterbird fist, including the few magic mist knights of the dark witches, they had all turned into piles of different colored dust when the moisture in their body had been completely evaporated.

This was the true horror of the Flight of the Evil Phoenix.

It destroyed the water particles in all living things under the high-frequency oscillation, and rapidly evaporated and dried to the point where it would turn anything into dust. Only secret users who have practiced the Waterbird Fist would be able to reduce its terrifying damage depending on the level of their skill.

Just by gently touching the edge of a broken wall.

Crash!

The wall collapsed and released a huge cloud of dust. With the moisture absorption, high-frequency oscillation, as well as the violent impact of the air current, only the most rigid materials could survive after the being hit by the combined assault.

The Nighthawks and the people from the Holy Fist Palace worked together to quickly carry Hochman and Dahm away. Each one of them who met Garen treated him as though he was a God-like being, with traces of respect and fanaticism.

That kind of fist technique was like a mythological fist technique! It was beyond their logic and understanding. That was not a field that ordinary humans could stand upon, it was an extraordinary field that belonged to the blood breeds and wizards.

While Angel was commanding her men to clean up the battlefield and help the wounded, she glanced at Garen from behind with passion and adoration.

AG slowly caught up with Garen from the ruins, while Nasira, who had a complicated look on her face, was standing beside him along with two helpers: Manasi and a high ranked witch.

“You’ve become stronger…” AG sighed lightly.

“You just never understood how strong I am,” Garen turned around and replied softly.

In fact, after he’d reached this level, he was no longer interested in this world’s blood breeds.

If it wasn’t for the pressure from Nadia regarding the void creatures, he would not have disputed over such trifling matters with the blood breed and witches. He would’ve made a move and established his superiority immediately. By doing so, the matter would not have been delayed until now.

“What are you planning to do next? I’m done with my part,” Garen casually asked.

According to the divided tasks, all he had to do was deal with the silver magic golem, then AG and Nasira would deal with the rest.

“Both parties are equal now,” AG casually answered, “About the Upper-Level blood breeds, we have finished off the entire secret party, and now the three of us and their three elders are the last remaining forces,” there was a mysterious smile on his aging face.

Without needing instructions, Nasira, who was standing at the side, looked at the Thousand-Legged Serpent beside her, nodded slightly, and withdrew a silver snake-shaped pendant. She walked to a part of the estate ruins and dropped it on the ground lightly.

The silver snake pendant freely fell towards the ground and made a clang when it hit a pile of black dust, which was the sound made when gold collided with iron.

In that instant, a circle of black ripples started spreading from the ground, and the affected areas were blackened, forming a huge seven to eight meters wide black hole.

Shadows started forming on both sides of the hole and two hound-like strange creature statues were formed. There was a stair extending downwards in the middle of the hole.

“I’ve opened it, the actual core residence of the Wellington family, the family’s underground palace,” Nasira quickly returned to her previous stance, “This part of them is similar to the vampires in the movie, they like to live underground and absorb the earth’s yin essence.”

“The Garden of the Immortals, it is their reliance and they claimed that it is an absolutely forbidden zone that can never be broken into,” there was a mocking smile on AG’s face, “It seems like tonight, it will be completely destroyed.”

He strode into the underground palace with his cane and soon disappeared into the darkness.

He was followed by Nasira and the two upper-class witches. The rest of the witches were trying to clean up the battlefield. One by one, they walked in in a well-ordered manner; they were very experienced and not even a wince was observed. Only when they saw Garen did they reveal a respectful look, but other than that they were not nervous at all. It was obvious that they were very experienced in fighting wars, or they’d planned this for a long time.

Garen squinted.

Things had gotten completely ugly with the blood breeds. Previously, because Raffaele and the other witches had been protecting their hometown, they protected his parents and sister too, so he only needed to add a few more bodyguards and it was enough. Moreover, the people that they used to provoke were just ordinary forces and none of them were highly ranked, so he was able to cope with it. But now, he really had to deal with it immediately.

As for the safety of his parents, Garen had already sent people to get them. Even before he made a move, he had already expected it, that if things were to get ugly, a place like Grana would not be able to withstand their revenge, and the people that he sent should almost be at the headquarters by now.

The headquarters was also no longer the old one in Berlin, but a new place, a remodeled palace at the summit of the American mountain which had been bought by Hochman and Dahm to be made the Holy Fist’s headquarters.

However, Garen believed that the best defense was to attack and destroy the enemy, as there would naturally be no more danger.

The reasons he’d come was to test the strength of his men as well as make use of the blood breeds’ power to toughen the future core members of the Holy Palace.

The last was to test the strength of blood breeds and at the same time, repay AG’s favor. The previous attack on his sister had been just a lead.

“Captain, are we following?” Angel whispered to him.

“AG is about to break through, it seems like getting the two holy objects was his core objective of this mission,” Garen said calmly, “I also wanted to have a look at the real immortal beings, and how powerful they are.”

He glanced at Angel.

“You do not have to go, I will go by myself. Be careful of surprise attacks by the blood breeds, and have Quentin back you up.”

“Understood.”

Although now all the experts of the Secret Party present were either severely wounded or killed, it was not everyone from the Secret Party, and there were still two more major secret clans which could gather experts to reinforce this heavily damaged party.

After arranging the situation properly, he jumped into the hole and glided downwards in silence like a bat.

Berlin

The group of moving vehicles was the same as normal vehicles. Everyone was busy as the commanding officer barked out orders while he managing the transportation of all sorts of items.

Several Nighthawk members dressed in plain clothing with bulging bellies glanced around the area vigilantly.

In the evening, the carrier workers were busily working on the lower floor of the mansion; they had not even gotten to the second floor.

Through the darkness of the second floor, blurry shadows were slowly yet steadily moving towards the secretive, hidden room on the second floor. It was as though they were the shadows of the curtains, and no one noticed their presence.

The two groups of shadows were communicating in voices so low that ordinary people would be unable to hear.

“He definitely left, it’s our chance.”

“The source of the weirdness must be the room on the second floor.”

“Pay attention to avoid traps.”

“Understood.”

In a suburban district forest that was less than ten kilometers away from the two groups of shadows.

A group of people dressed in black was commanding in a nervous yet ordered manner.

Medis and Kabb from the Bailey Group were smiling as they stared at the huge projection screen in front of them.

“That man has finally left, it has been confirmed that he left Berlin completely and will not return anytime soon, otherwise he won’t have people moving his stuff,” Medis whispered, “According to my investigation, and the news I heard from the Primary Colors group, there must be some important secret of Garen’s combat club.”

“What is the progress of the research?” Kabb whispered his question.

“Very good, the secret technique we got out of the dying Nighthawk, after putting it into the test, the effect after deriving it in the computer is astonishing! Thirty out of a hundred people who participated in the training reached a remarkable level, they were almost comparable to the world’s top mercenaries’ levels! Even though they themselves are strong candidates, it’s undeniable that the secret technique has greatly enhanced their strength.”

“Even such a simple technique is so useful? Then will the core secret techniques not be that applicable?” Kabb was surprised.

“It is very useful, they are all extremely horrifying killing techniques.” Medis squinted his eye and revealed a foxlike smile. In that instance, something more eye-catching appeared on the projection screen.

A few sturdy and sharp looking elite Nighthawk members were carefully carrying a box covered in black cloth out of the mansion and heading towards the car. In the void that could not be seen, the box was surrounded by some kind of oppressing yet horrifying distortion feeling, it was similar to the airflow that looked distorted above flames.

“That is….” Medis muttered. “The secret in the secret room, it must be in that box!”

“Get ready to make a move.” Kabb giggled as he slowly took out a weird looking black mask. The forehead of the mask was covered with dense eye-like holes, and it was the same mask as Garen, the Sleepless Faces mask!

Chapter 707: Underground Palace 1

Inside the mansion, the two groups of black shadows quietly floated out and moved within the shadows of the stone armrest, so that no one would notice their movements.

Somewhere not too far away from the truck, several sturdy Nighthawks members were carrying boxes towards the truck. They gently and very carefully walked along the slanted steel plate and placed the box covered in black cloth on one of the large containers they prepared in advance.

The container was filled with a large amount of white, ice-like substance that was constantly exuding white cold mist; it was something like dry ice. As soon as the box was put into it, it was constrained, as though the box was not an object but a living thing.

The few sturdy men quickly sealed the container with the lid and covered it with seven to eight locks.

“Take good care of it, it’s something that the commander specified to handle with caution.” A leader-like Nighthawk member whispered to the men carrying the boxes.

“Understood, don’t worry, we will take turns to look after it.” A man laughed and said in a low voice.

The leader nodded, lowered the offloading boot of the vehicle and went to delegate the workers to move other stuff. There was a total of three carrier trucks, and he needed to verify all three of them one by one.

The two groups of black shadows stopped under the shadow of the armrest and appeared to be waiting for something.

Soon, everything in the villa was being moved into the trucks, they started up the trucks and it seemed like they were ready to leave.

Some Nighthawk members jumped into the car and closed the door.

The two men who were guarding the box both lit a cigarette, puffing on it from time to time, and exhaled rings of smoke. They were having a pleasant conversation and laughed occasionally.

The two groups of black shadows started moving slowly. They took advantage of the moment when the car had started moving forward slightly to quickly float behind the truck carrying the box and get into the vehicle.

Where the light shone on the shadows, two groups of transparent human shaped outlines could be vaguely seen.

“Get in position.”

“It has already started.” Both shadows were exchanging information with each other.

Amidst the darkness, dots of red lights started flashing in a corner where the two guardsmen were not able to see.

Chi-chi!!

Along with two light noises, the two guardsmen fell. They clutched at their necks with their eyes rolled back, and fell to the ground twitching.

“We got it, notify someone to pick us up.”

One of the dark shadows suddenly walked out of the shade and the air vaguely twisted for a moment before suddenly, a small thin figure appeared. It looked like a lovely little girl.

She walked before the container with an unknown tool in her hand, and lightly pressed it along the edges of the container and clapped her hands.

Bap!

Along with a crisp sound, all the locks on the container was fully opened. After the lid of the container was removed, the box covered in black cloth that was exuding a white mist was seen in the middle of the container.

The girl raised her left wrist and gently tapped on the screen of her watch. The screen started flashing and transformed into a black display, upon which a smiling old man’s face appeared on the screen.

“How was it? You got it?” the old man was the Kabb of the Bailey group, and he was smiling while he slowly enjoyed his coffee.

“We have arrived at the targeted area, but the targeted object is too large, so we can’t easily move it.” the woman replied in a low voice.

“Can you split it?” Kabb asked.

“It’s difficult.” the woman glanced at the box’s material under the black cloth, “It is made out of the latest alloy manufacturing technique.”

“Then drill it. Destroy the entire box quickly, you do not have much time,” Kabb ordered.

“Yes.”

The woman switched off the screen on her watch, and a small black knife popped out of her left hand, one that looked like a fruit knife. She placed the knife on top of the surface of the box under the black cloth.

Hiss!!

Suddenly, there were two saw-like crisscrossed razor blades at the tip of the sharp knife which was moving in a cutting motion alternatively, and also a needle-like drill in the center which was rotating constantly, causing sparks to appear on the surface of the black box.

Toot!!!!

Suddenly, the box made an extremely piercing alarming sound.

“Warning!!!” the Nighthawk members started yelling outside.

At that moment, along with a ‘thump’ sound, a big hole was being made on the box beneath the black cloth.The edge of the metal bent upwards and formed a few sharp bulges. The size of the hole was sufficient for a hand to reach in.

The girl kept her watch and drill without hesitation then stretched her hands into the hole.

All of a sudden, she shuddered and her body felt stiff.

“Hurry up!” the other black shadow urged urgently.

Strangely, the woman did not respond and she remained stunned. Her hand was left motionless in the box and she was frozen still. Her forehead had started dripping with a large amount of sweat, and her eyes were wide open. It seemed like she was enduring some kind of terrifying torture.

Thump!!!

Suddenly, an enormous force slammed into the girl mercilessly, directly throwing her out and hit the hidden black shadow behind. The both of them moaned in pain and rolled off the moving truck.

Before they even landed on the ground, rounds of firing gunshots were heard, and the only things left on the ground were two heavily shot bodies.

At that moment, the hole in the box started emitting traces of invisible distortion and that small area where it was distorted vaguely looked as though it was a ferocious dragon head.

“What happened?! They found out about it?” Kabb looked at the static monitor screen in front of him.

“I’m afraid so.” Said Medis while frowning, “The sisters rarely fail, this time they should have got into trouble. It seems like the reason why Garen left something so important here is that he’s well prepared.”

“Let’s start our first backup plan, doing it the hard way seems to be the only option.” Kabb thought for a moment and said with a low voice.

“I’ll go get ready.” Medis understood what her boss meant.

Kabb’s face got slightly gloomy.

He had to get the masks as he’d heard from the Primary Colors that Garen had several masks with him. Moreover, it was part of Garen’s secret, which was also something that he’d wanted to uncover for a long time.

At that time, the campsite was getting busier as Medis seemed to have arranged something, and the members of the Bailey Group started moving around urgently.

“Do you need me to help?” suddenly, a new image popped out on his watch screen. It was a sinister looking hook-nosed man, who had his chin slightly lifted while he stared at Kabb on the other side of the screen with a hint of arrogance.

“Mr. Gremlin.” Kabb remained calm, “You’re pretty well-informed.”

“Garen ruined my dream, so how can I not pay attention to his actions?” Gremlin responded coldly, “Don’t tell me that you can’t even deal with what Garen left here? If so, then I’m disappointed in your capabilities.”

“You do not have to worry about these, I will deal with it.” Kabb said with a false smile on his face, “How is your White Phoenix Base doing?”

Upon mentioning that, Gremlin’s face twitched. Since Lesothy had put a lot of pressure on the Primary Colors, it had led to a huge setback on the reconstruction of the White Phoenix base. After all, the White Phoenix base was just one of the Primary Color Group’s branches. To them, a Violent Organization branch was not something that important. There were many other factions within the group that were happy to see his branch being suppressed.

“It seems like you do not need my help.”

Kabb smiled, stopped talking and directly ended the contact. For now, Gremlin was worth nothing to him; he was of no importance, his branch was gradually being abandoned by the Primary Colors, and his forces had been greatly damaged by Garen. Without the deterrence of the special-class mercenaries, nevermind Garen, even to Kabb, he was just someone of no significance.

Wellington family’s underground palace.

Garen slowly walked down the underground passages. Inside the passageway, there were circular arch-type stone doors, and every few meters, there would be a greyish-yellow stone door, all of them were open.

Garen looked forward and could not see an end to this stone tunnel.

Garen could only vaguely see the torch of Nasira and the rest of them somewhere in front.

He himself did not need any illumination, as his extremely strong senses were enough for him to get through any environment without any hindrance.

The structure of the underground palace was very peculiar; both sides of the passageway were filled with yellow, nails-like steel points, and looked like the nail boards of the ancient criminal law. On top of the tunnel, there was a round dome of cloud patterned arcs. He did not know what the patterns were about, but they were bending all over the place.

Not knowing why Garen felt that there was something wrong as he moved forward, it was as though every time he went through a door, he entered into a new environment. Through the layers of stone doors, the feeling that he felt now was completely different from when he’d entered.

Also, he could no longer see Nasira and the rest in front of him.

He did not know what AG had planned, but they were not the kind to rush forward and leave him behind.

He took his phone out but there was no signal.

To avoid destroying the valuable information in it, Garen had not brought along the notebook that enabled him to contact AG, and he figured that AG would not have brought it either.

Garen took a few steps forward and he could sense that his surroundings were being filled with a faint dusk-like yellow light, though he did not know how the yellow light was appearing in the underground palace.

The nail boards on both sides of the wall were filled with spikes, and there was a stone door in front which he could not see an end to the passage, which kept going downwards as though there was no end to it.

At that point, the entire tunnel had brightened up, the yellow lighted up the entire tunnel, but the surroundings were dead silent, and he could not hear Nasira or AG at all.

Garen looked back and forth, the door which he entered initially had completely disappeared, and all he could see was an endless amount of stone doors. All the opened stone doors were quiet yet they oddly connected to form a straight tunnel. The faint yellow light illuminated the whole tunnel.

“It’s not the same as when I first came in.” Garen frowned, “I only went through five stone doors when I came in. Is this an illusion or a maze?”

‘It should be a maze.’ Black Sethe whispered, ‘There’s something weird about this place, please be alert.’

“I know.” Garen nodded and continued walking forward.

Chapter 708: Underground Palace 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A dark corner in the underground palace.

AG was holding up his burning flame staff while he walked forward with a calm face. There was no one around him, as Nasira and the rest of them seemed to have been separated from him, and he was left alone.

“This place… it feels weird…” he murmured to himself. “I’ve been separated by some sort of dimension force…. It seems like…”

He looked at his surroundings with vigilance and speculation.

The fiery flare caused his face to look slightly reddish.

He reached his unoccupied hand into his pocket and touched something, then he instantly calmed down.

“I will succeed this time, just one last step… one last step…”

There was a determined look on his face once again as he strode forward.

Another dark corner in the underground palace.

Manasi, who wore a full set of armor, and the thousand-legged serpent witch were following behind Nasira who was holding a torch. The both of them observed their surroundings with vigilance from time to time.

“I can feel an extremely evil force here.” the thousand-legged serpent’s tail slightly swayed, as if it was a slightly distorted living thing.

The three of them walked through the passage. Before and behind them was endless darkness, and the torch could only illuminate an area within a few meters. The areas where the flame was not able to illuminate occasionally looked like statues of the skulls of beasts.

“Every death apostle’s immortal garden is not the same, so you need to be careful. All we need to do is to restrain the force of the underground palace and we would have completed our mission. As long as the AG can successfully fulfill his goal, he can completely destroy this garden.” Nasira whispered.

The blue flame in Manasi’s eyes flickered a few times.

“It seems like this is Wellington’s final card. I’ve prepared some special weapons, they will come in handy.”

The three of them were alerted and sped up towards the depths of the underground palace.

After an unknown period of time had passed, the underground passage appeared to have become more spacious, and some deep scratches began to show up on the ground. There were also tiny writings appearing on the wall.

“It seems like there are words on the wall.”

The thousand-legged serpent walked over and gently stroked the wall.

“Wellington… Pearson… Dovich…” as she touched the writings, she said softly.

“Pearson Dovich?” Nasira frowned, the name gave her a bad feeling as if she heard it somewhere.

“There are more words behind.” the thousand-legged serpent continued to reach towards the back. As her fingers touched it, she read it out softly. “Anil’s Gardens.”

Anil’s Gardens?!

Nasira’s expression changed.

“It’s a trap!! Anil’s Gardens! How could it be…!!” Even someone of her status could not help but feel a chill.

There were many unsolved mysteries in this world, and Anil’s Garden was one of it. Rumors said that it was an underground garden someone named Anil built, but in fact, it was an underground cemetery, an underground mausoleum.

No one knew who Anil was, and no one has found any records of the mausoleum in the history, but somewhere in the underground of a lost ruin, people unintentionally discovered the existence of Anil’s garden.

It was known as one of the most well-known taboos in the supernatural world and was infamous because there was no way out of it.

“Shouldn’t Anil’s Garden be in Australia? How could it appear here!!” Nasira felt her heart pounding violently, as the feeling of her plan going out of control overwhelmed her.

“We probably have not gone too far, it’s not too late to retreat!” on the other hand, Manasi was not very nervous. Since he was a half-wizard cyborg, he has never heard of how scary Anil’s Garden was.

Nasira shook her head slightly.

“It’s too late, if this is Anil’s Garden, then space has already been twisted, we will definitely not find a way out. Even the time here is distorted, the both of you need to be careful.”

She took out a small wooden bird, gently tossed it, and the bird started flying backward.

“Look.”

Manasi and thousand-legged serpent looked and were instantly stunned.

They saw the wooden bird flapping its wings as it flew backward, after flying for just a short distance, suddenly, it was flying on the spot without moving forward before it disappeared from their sight.

“This space will only allow you to move forward and not backward, I used to study the three secret lands and this was no exception, the only way is to move forward,” Nasira said solemnly.

The other two were also upper-level witches and they naturally had pride and confidence in themselves, so they quickly calmed down.

“As we move forward, we might find clues that will get us out of here,” Nasira said in a low voice.

The three of them continued to move towards the depths of the underground palace.

The Wellington family within a certain dark space

“They finally went in.” An elderly black shadow said with a low voice. He took his hand out of the blood pool and there was a trace of exhaustion in his voice.

“Is that Anil’s Garden? The legendary underground cemetery in Australia which could move around like a living creature?” a woman asked with a lazy voice as she finally got a little interested.

“To be exact, that’s the biggest secret of our family, everyone knew that Anil’s Garden is in Australia, but no one knew that there is a pathway in our family’s underground palace that connects to a second Anil’s Garden.” a third black shadow explained with a neutral tone.

“The second one? How are you clear about it, you went there before?” The slothful girl asked curiously.

“No. Not even the landlord has not been in it, the landlord used to warn me to not try to enter the garden, or it would be very troublesome.”

“Even the landlord has not been in it?” both of them were surprised.

“To be precise, no one has ever been in it. The entrance of the tunnel has been there since forever, but I do not know what is inside. Even the landlord was warned by his ancestors to never enter the garden. No one knows the reason why, but it was being passed down from generation to generation.” the shadow with a neutral voice explained, “Which is why I do not know what’s inside, and you both should stop asking me.”

The blood pool was constantly replaying the scene when AG and the few of them entered the underground palace.

Strangely enough, the entrance to the underground palace that they enter was not the usual entrance of the family. The blood pool showed that entrance of the family was still hidden underground, but the hole that they opened, where did it come from?

Then, they saw AG and the rest of them jumping into the unknown underground palace entrance, and quickly disappeared.

Just after they have all entered the hole, the entrance rapidly warped from an ancient looking appearance into a whole new appearance. The mottled and destroyed old brick stone surface of both sides of the walls suddenly morphed into a whole new wall, and even the hound-like statues on both sides of the door looked brand new. It suddenly changed from a shabby entrance into the actual underground entrance of the Wellington Family.

“I get goosebumps all over my body every time!” the girl with a slothful voice finally revealed a dignified look on her face. “Where exactly did this entrance come from?”

“I don’t know.” The black shadow with the neutral voice replied, “The only thing I know is that the landlord activated something, then he told me about this plan.”

“They probably won’t be able to get out, let’s think about something else, one of the elders of the other two families is in our hands, and it might get very troublesome!”

The elderly black shadow murmured, “How much do we need to pay to satisfy them?”

“Prior to this, we have already extracted most of the Bloodline Core. As long as we get enough essence, their resurrection will not be a problem, but since it will take time to recover, we might take a massive hit,” the girl with the lazy voice answered.

“Tu Lan, this should be your turn to negotiate with them, it was us for the previous two times,” the elderly shadow suggested.

“I know, it’s so annoying.”

“There’re more words here,” Manasi said with a low voice while she stroked the wall.

“What is it?” Nasira got up from the ground somewhat irritably.

“All those who enter the underground palace…. will become the prey of the Grim Reaper. It is a curse that no one can escape.” Manasi whispered and recited the writings on the wall.

“You’re making things up!” Nasira flicked the ash off her fingers; previously when she crouched down to check the indentations on the ground, she did not find anything.

“Let’s move forward,” she ordered coldly and seemed to have calmed down. “We better find AG and Garen as soon as possible, the sudden appearance of this strange underground palace is way beyond what we expected.”

The trio continued moving forward along the passage. The flame seemed to be moving through the endless darkness, and after a while, the passage gradually grew wider and formed an inclining downwards slope.

Soon, the three of them could hear a subtle sound of water coming from the bottom of the slope.

“It’s a river.” The thousand-legged serpent said in a low voice, held his torch and walked towards it. From afar, they could see something sparkling under the slope and a violent underground river at the very bottom. The river was four to five meters wide and it stretched across before the three of them.

If they wanted to move on, they must cross the river.

They looked towards the left and right side, but both sides were being blocked by walls, and at the bottom of both walls, there was a big hole, which was where the river water flowed in.

A small river appearing suddenly inside the tunnel was suspicious, so Nasira took the initiative to use a special energy-absorbing physique she had that was able to make all supernatural beings useless. She quickly walked to the edge of the river under the slope and gently scooped up some water with her hands.

The water looked blackish, there was even a faint rotting smell, and after Nasira sniffed at it, she immediately threw it away.

“There is poison in the water, be careful,” she stood up and looked at the rapidly flowing river in front of her.

The entire river was blocking the tunnel, it was roughly about seven to eight meters long.

Nasira smoothly took a step back and then jumped over it. Her light body flew forward and in just a snap of a finger, she was on the other side of the river.

The other two jumped in and steadily got to the opposite shore.

The passage on both sides of the river were different; the ground of this side was rough and rocky without any man-made facilities.

Chapter 709: Attack 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There was some gray moss growing on the ground and walls, while the air seemed to be heavy with moisture, forming a faint white fog.

Nasira looked around cautiously but did not find anything unusual.

“Be careful, if this is really Anil’s Garden, it will definitely be a troublesome place.”

“Let me do it,” Manasi the magic knight walked forward and his full body of armor started making sounds. He knelt down on one knee and rested his arms on the ground.

“Fire of Clarity.”

A purple circular pattern lit up around his arms, and the purple snake-like pattern drilled into the ground.

Shoom…

A cluster of yellow flame ignited spontaneously on the ground and turned into a fiery snake, moving around as though it was a living thing.

“Keep up with it, it will bring us to the deepest core of this area,” Manasi warned and got up.

The rest of them did not say much, but followed behind the snake tightly and moved forward rapidly. Soon, they entered a crude tunnel, and as the distance they traveled increased, the white fog around them got thicker and the air became moister.

The bright fire snake that was leading the way started to gradually become dim, as though it was being restricted.

Manasi had to take out a few weird looking things like a snake’s gallbladder and throw it into the flame to barely sustain the flame of the fire snake.

Hooo…

“What’s that sound?” Nasira suddenly stopped, “Did you both hear that?”

At that time, the three of them were already deep into the crude looking tunnel, and they were surrounded by cold, hard rock walls.

“Sound? What sound?” the thousand-legged serpent frowned and looked around.

Hooo!

Suddenly, a group of distortions passed by behind him, and two of them exclaimed and instantly attacked.

Bang bang!!

Two groups of black fog hit the stone wall behind the thousand-legged serpent, the impact causing quite a number of black stones to fall off the wall.

The thousand-legged serpent reacted to it by growing a large amount of hair all over his skin, of which the texture was that of a living creature. His hair started popping out in all directions frenziedly, like needles popping out under high pressure, and most of the spiked hair hit the stone wall and made a crisp clinking sounds.

“Watch out, above you!” Nasira shouted.

The thousand-legged serpent hurriedly looked up, just in time to see a group of transparent distortions lunging towards his head.

******************

Boom!!

Garen punched the walls of the stone wall tunnel. A large number of rocks were smashed into powered form, scattering onto the ground and creating a deep rumble.

A several meters deep large pit appeared on the stone wall, and numerous dense cracks spreading around it.

“Ah?” He unclenched his fist and looked at the stone wall.

‘This should be an independent underground passage, so there won’t be any connected tunnels around, you should just give up.’ Black Sethe said briefly.

“This is indeed a little troublesome,” Garen nodded. “If only I could fly, just like in the previous world, I could just fly straight up, and not even this place could trap me.”

‘If I’m not wrong, even if you could fly, if you don’t figure out the tricks and methods to leaving, you will probably not be able to leave.’ Black Sethe said in a low voice, ‘There seems to be some sort of spatial distortion here. No matter where you go, space will eventually be twisted and you will be directed into a downwards direction. Moreover, if you go downwards, unless you break through this entire planet, you will never be able to leave.’

“Can you find a way?” Garen continued to move forward. The surroundings of the passage changed from a bright yellow tunnel into a rough stone wall tunnel.

‘I need time, how can I think of something all of a sudden? Just keep moving forward, so I can get to know more of the spatial rules here.’

“Ok then.”

Garen speeded up and continued walking deeper into the tunnel.

*****************

“Ah!!” the thousand-legged serpent shouted. Her whole body lit up in a purplish-red glow and a purple flame started burning in her eyes. She opened her tiny mouth wide and shot out a shivering, distorted purple light, which looked like a transparent twisted tip of a knife.

However, a strange phenomenon appeared, the purple laser went straight through the distortion and did not have any effect on it.

Poof!!

The thousand-legged serpent froze with a shocked expression before she was directly covered by that group of distortions. She was being wrapped in it and it looked as though she was being stuck in a huge lump of sticky glue.

She struggled for breath, but she could not get out of the distorted slime.

Nasira and the Manasi tried various methods to cut open the group of transparent distortions, but they were all futile. All they could do was watch as the thousand-legged serpent got smaller and smaller inside the distortion.

Her body began to melt like a candle.

Her face began to decay and melted into lumps of dripping light yellow fluid. Her eyes were the first one start melting, as well as her breasts, nose, and other protruded parts. Before the melted fluid could slide down any further, it would rapidly merge into the group of transparent distortion.

“Damn it!!” Nasira attempted to use her hands to rip open the distorted slime, but it was to no avail. Her energy-absorbing physique did not work, and all she could do was watch the thousand-legged serpent struggle inside the distortion.

Sweat started dripping down her forehead.

“Damn it! What the hell is going on in this place?” Nasira felt pain in her hands, so she immediately took her hands out, and when she glanced at her palms, they were already a little corroded.

“Let’s go!!” Manasi grabbed her from behind and started running backward, and after a few steps, they notice that they were just running on the spot, then they turned around and continued running forward.

Both of them were still in shock, and the thousand-legged serpent’s twisted and hopeless face gradually disappeared behind them, consumed by the darkness. They continued moving forward by following the Fire of Clarity, and soon they put everything behind.

“The thousand-legged serpent is an upper ranked person! Don’t worry, she will not die that easily….” Manasi comforted. However, the both of them were aware that the thousand-legged serpent was AG’s subordinate instead of a member of the Witch’s Association, and as they were not that close, it was unlikely for them to pay a huge price to save her.

Being an upper-level person did not only represent their strength, it represented life and vitality. It also represented the same for upper-class blood breeds.

The upper blood breeds could isolate part of their core and preserve it while their main body could still maintain its peak state, just that their endurance would be weaker. By doing so, when they need to execute an extremely dangerous mission and they were sacrificed during the process, they could extract the essence from the preserved core and quickly create a new body. Of course, reviving would cause that person to be weak for a long time, at least a year or two, but it would be better than dying directly in a fight.

Similarly, the upper-level witches had similar tricks; they could make use a large number of secret techniques to strengthen their own body, and also the Broken Lizard Tail method, which sacrifices a part of their body when they are in a life-threatening danger. The most common way was to use their alliance.

The alliance was the witches’ supernatural companions that belonged only to them. The alliance itself did not have high intelligence, but they were an incomprehensible illusory being that only witches could summon.

Ah!!!!

Suddenly, they heard a piercing scream coming from behind.

Is was the thousand-legged serpent!

She sounded like she was in extreme pain, the instant that they heard her piercing screams, Nasira and Manasi felt chills all over their body and they involuntarily speeded up.

“Quick!”

Nasira was almost sprinting.

Before they got too far, she suddenly stopped, stood still in the tunnel and dared not move forward. Manasi who was behind her almost knocked into her.

“What happened?”

Nasira slightly took a step back and stared at the dark passage in front of them alertly. She did not speak and all she did was point in that direction.

Manasi looked towards where she was pointing and saw a bald man dressed in black standing in front of the channel, blocking their way.

The most prominent feature of that man was his shiny bald head, but strangely, there were various sized eyes covering the top of his bald head. Those were all human eyes with a sharp contrast between black and white, the eyes kept blinking, and it looked oddly creepy.

The man stood with his back facing them, though there were dozens of eyes at the back of his head, and he was motionless. It seemed like he was not a living person, but a sculpture.

Both Manasi and Nasira felt an inexplicable wariness of the man.

“Let’s do it!!”

Nasira suddenly rushed forward and made a sideway kick. Along with a terrifying roar, she took out a few transparent air bombs and threw them directly at the man.

The air bombs were comet-shaped, and they lined out in a straight line on the back of the bald man.

Boom!

The air bombs exploded but the bald man was undamaged.

Hooo!!

Right at that moment, a huge force rushed out violently behind Nasira and hit her from behind.

Bang!

Nasira staggered forward, seemed to have tripped on something, lost her balance and fell forwardly onto the floor. But she immediately felt something entangling around her waist.

She caught a glimpse of a number of black tentacles behind her, each as thick as a water bucket. The moment the tentacles entangled around her waist, they became transparent and started secreting a large amount of transparent fluid.

Heee!!

She immediately made a weird shrieking sound. Then, her left arm broke off and her whole body became blurry. As though she’d teleported, she disappeared on the spot and appeared in front of the tunnel, which was more than ten meters away.

It seemed like Manasi used the Broken Lizard Tail method, and they ran into a forked road which suddenly appeared in front of them.

“We’ll go separate ways!” Nasira shouted and ran straight ahead without turning back. The tentacles were so powerful that they were much stronger than an upper-level blood breed. Each tentacle was extremely sticky, and it was impossible to break free from it.

At this moment, she felt the burning pain on her waist; even the Broken Lizard Tail could not even get rid of the fluid, and while this thought made her gasp in shock, she involuntarily increased her pace.

Along the way, she dropped a few dark red disks, which automatically set off a cracking sound once they were thrown, and drilled into the ground like a tiny octopus.

They were strengthened time bombs that she’d made specially. They were attached to extremely powerful alliance forces, in other words, the power of witches.

Chapter 710: Attack 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Witches made alliances through illusion and reality, then used the alliance as a stepping stone to utilize the magical powers of nature. They could also use their dreamland as a way to train, so they would have this terrifying ability to be much more powerful when they returned to reality.

Even in reality, when they encounter an inevitable crisis, witches could make use of their alliances’ power to enter into their dreamland and avoid any danger. It was something similar to avoiding death through teleportation, which was the principle of the Broken Lizard Tail method that Nasira used previously.

However, that monster’s fluid was still sticking onto Nasira, and even after she entered her dreamland, she was not able to completely get rid of it. It was horrifying because this meant that the tentacle monster’s fluid had a certain degree of spiritual energy polluting toxicity.

She quickly ran into a tunnel, sat down at the side of the passage while gasping for air and quickly took out all sorts of things from her pocket. She placed all of them on the ground and sculpted an eye-like figure.

“Move.” She whispered.

The eye-like figure suddenly moved on its own and disappeared into the ground.

Thump!!

The tunnel started shaking violently, but Nasira was not surprised; she knew that it was the bombs that she planted previously. Even though bombs infused with the power of witches were much more powerful than the usual bombs, she did not expect it to be able to stop that monster.

She stood up and got ready to continue running forward, but before she could, a thick tentacle appeared out of nowhere, popped up behind her, and it fiercely smashed onto her back through the darkness.

Bang! Poof!

Nasira spat a mouthful of blood, ran forward quickly and disappeared around the corner.

***************

Berlin

“What is that thing?” Kabb had a dignified look on his face despite the sweat dripping down his temple.

He was standing at the center of the campsite and looking at the crowd surrounding him with vigilance, while Medis stood by his side with an equally tense look.

In just less than ten minutes, there was suddenly a man lying unconscious in the campsite, which wouldn’t have been a big deal except that man’s entire body had started decaying like rotten meat while he was unconscious. The surface of his skin was like a tattered cloth, upon which traces of dried out wounds could be seen. Through the wounds, the shriveled muscles underneath the skin could be seen, without even a tiny bit of blood oozing. A total of four to five people have collapsed without reason.

It was why Kabb and the rest of them were on high alert.

They immediately found that there seemed to be a black string-like thing that was wandering around the campsite, and when it found an opportunity, it would drill into a person’s skin.

A few of them had to shoot frenziedly in order to cut it into a few parts.

“Take it to the laboratory to study it,” Kabb ordered after nothing weird happened again, only then did he take out a handkerchief to wipe off his sweat.

“How do we get the secret of Garen’s combat club?” Medis calmed down and asked with a low voice.

“The preparation continues.”

Ahh!!!

Suddenly, a scream was heard coming from the direction of the guards patrolling in the forest.

“Who’s that!?” Bang Bang bang!! a burst of gunshots was fired, accompanied by a few grenade explosions.

All they could see in the forest were a few black shadows and the patrolling guards of the Bailey Group being entangled together.

“They are the people from Nighthawk! Retreat!!” the patrolling captain shouted.

Instantly, Kabb was surrounded by a large group of people who were trying to protect him. His eyelids were twitching intensely, and when he looked at his surroundings carefully, all he could see was his patrolling officers falling to the ground one by one.

That few black shadows were running in his direction at great speed.

The lights in the campsite shone onto one of the black shadows who was standing in front, which exposed his appearance, he was a young looking ordinary man. However, he was dressed in black from head to toe, along with a decisive and ruthless temperament.

“How dare you spy on the combat club’s transport team… Berlin Group, how dare you!” the men were wearing black metal gloves with sharp metal thorns at the knuckle, making it look ferociously abnormal and there were even blood stains on top of it.

“Retreat!” Kabb immediately gave this command after he recognized this man.

Xander, the first batch of members of the club’s elite team, who once killed a number of armed forces and then disappeared. Now it seemed like he’d become even more cruel and stronger.

Kabb squatted down, secretly walked away from the crowd and went into a camouflaged car under the cover of Medis. Once the doors and windows of the car were tightly shut, he was relieved.

“They had such a strong alertness!” he wiped off his sweat, and the car started moving silently towards a faraway direction before speeding up to escape. As for the rest of them, as long as they died off, they would be unable to chase after him. Moreover, in no time, reinforcements would arrive, and since now the combat club was lacking in manpower, Xander alone would not be able to do much.

“The harder they try to protect it, the more important it is to them!” Kabb’s eyes flickered, “Just in time for us to test the group of people that we have just trained.”

Medis had just wiped her sweat off with a tissue, thrown it into a rubbish bin and loosened her bow tie.

“I’ll inform them now.”

“If the information we got from the Primary Colors is accurate, then Xander will be the only one there, as the rest of them have been sent off to do other stuff. This will be our best chance to snatch the box,” Kabb whispered. “Inform Gremlin from the Primary Colors and tell him that we can do it together, and we can split what we got in half.”

It was proven that with just a little secret technique, they were able to get so much stronger, hence if he were to get even more records of the secret technique related information, it would enhance their strength in a terrifying way….

“Gather everyone who’s available, I’m sure that I will be able to get it!” he clenched his teeth and a glimpse of determination flashed through his eyes.

“Then should I move them here too?” Medis asked tentatively. Ever since the previous attack on the Nighthawks, their mercenary troop had suffered a heavy loss. Subsequently, the Nighthawks and the combat club have been taking revenge against them, and if they were to gather all their manpower now, they might just be completely annihilated.

“Just do it! As long as we get it, I will reward them with 20 million euros! I don’t believe they won’t want it!” Kabb clenched his teeth.

“We might not have enough time.”

“It doesn’t matter, they will not be back anytime soon, as long as that thing is still on the road, we can always stop it!”

The both of them did not notice that when their car left the forest, a black shadow was standing there quietly, that person had bloody eyes and was wearing a black round cap, and he quietly watched as their car left.

“What’s the matter? Did you find anything new?” the shadow heard a woman’s voice coming from behind.

“I found something interesting, there’s a truck that seems to be carrying the more important belongings of the combat club and this guy found out about it, so he intends to rob it,” the black shadow spoke with an authentic Berliner accent.

“This human’s organization is very secretive…” the woman muttered,”Their leader Garen is busy with Wellington now, and I was told that this man is terrifyingly powerful and we need to immediately retreat the moment we run into him.”

“Oh?” The black shadow suddenly showed some interest. “I didn’t mishear you right… We are the upper-level blood breeds, but we need to retreat?”

“Weidi and Yelu almost died.” the woman answered quietly.

The black shadow seemed to be stunned; he did not know how to react to that.

“Are you joking?” he asked. “Yaludo is much stronger than me, but he almost died?”

“That’s what I heard, but I do not know the details. Isn’t it obvious, since the leader sent us here to investigate it?” the woman said solemnly.

“That’s surprising….” The black shadow shook his head. “If that’s true, then I’m interested in what are they shipping in the truck.”

“It is.”

The black shadow sneered, gradually became more transparent and slowly disappeared.

********************

“Anyone who enters the garden will not be able to escape death…” AG gently stroked on the writings on the wall. They had been written in ancient German letters and had been carved into the walls ages ago.

He continued touching downwards and used the torch to light up his sight.

“No one can escape the grim reaper’s curse, so repent, sinners!” AG read the words out one by one with a straight face. He seemed to be thinking about something.

“Anil’s Garden?” he used to study this mysterious place. It was a confined infinite space loop, and if he could not find a way out, he would never be able to leave.

AHH!!!

Suddenly, he heard a scream coming from the tunnel in front. It sounded like the thousand-legged serpent!

AG had a nervous look on his face. He put his hands down and his body floated about ten meters forward. After moving through dozens of meters through that method, he soon approached the source of the sound.

“According to the distance of the sound, this is indeed the source of the sound…”

AG stopped and looked at the empty black tunnel. There was a forked road in front of him, on top of the stone walls of the forked road, there was a three-headed human-shaped statue with six arms and three eyes. The statue looked neither like a male or a female, though it was at the center of the forked road and it was staring downwards furiously. All six hands were holding something respectively, there was a water bottle, a circular ring, an ax, a ribbon, a short dagger, and a long stick.

Just when he was not paying attention to what was behind him, a group of transparent distortions rose up from the ground soundlessly. The group of distortions was gradually getting bigger before it opened up like a wide-open mouth and approached him slowly.

While AG was still looking at that statue, he seemed to have thought of something important.

***************

“I’m back at the starting point,” Garen frowned as he looked at the hole that he made on the wall.

‘This place is an infinite space loop, without a higher dimensional skill, you will never be able to get out of here,’ Black Sethe explained. ‘Unfortunately, these skills do not exist in my memory, only a few traces of it, which should be due to the incomplete memory. ‘

“A higher dimension? Something like Klein’s bottle?” Garen stood still.

‘Klein’s bottle? What is that? ‘

Garen suddenly remembered that it was the physical conception of the Earth.

“Nothing.”

Both ways were endless dark passages, so he tried punching the walls on his sides, and the ground was now littered with small piles of crushed rock pieces.

“We might find a solution if we find the others.” Garen felt like he was not able to solve this issue alone.

‘Then continue to move forward, try to smash the passage on your sides and see if you can get into other passages,’ Black Sethe suggested. ‘Since there’s no other way, destroying this place might be useful.’

“It’s the only way.”

Chapter 711: Attack 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Moving forward, a dark river gradually appeared in front of Garen. There was something moving up and down inside the river but it was blurry and he could not make out what it was.

Garen walked to the river.

“This was not here before.”

‘It seems to have some effect.’

“En.”

Garen carefully checked around the river. In addition to his footprints, there were footprints of other people. Obviously, he was not the only one who’d come here.

He leaped effortlessly and landed on the other side of the river. Looking back at the passage behind, strangely, the passage was not there. There was only darkness and nothing else.

The passage on this side of the river was made up of rough stones, which was quite different from the passage that was made up of neatly arranged stones on the other side.

Garen looked down at the ground. Sure enough, two clear lines of footprints continued into the rough stones passage.

He silently followed the footprints while maintaining his alertness towards his surroundings.

********************

Nasira had a pale complexion. After taking some medicine, she staggered onward for more than ten minutes before she managed to shake off the tentacles in pursuit and entered a bright and spacious hall made of black stones.

The walls were made of egg-shaped black stones with a smooth and shiny surface.

There was green moss on the surrounding walls of the stone hall, illuminating the entire hall with green shimmers of light.

Nasira stood in front of an entrance on the wall of the stone hall and looked down. In the dim green light, she could see that the bottom of the hall was full of white bones. She did not know how high a pile the bones made, but the sight in front of her was undeniably a sea of bones. Sometimes, there was some movement among the bones.

Suddenly, Nasira’s expression changed. She moved her body close to the wall and stuck to it as close as possible without moving.

Swish!

A shadow flashed in front of her, drilling into the stone hall made of egg-shaped stones. It was a tentacle as thick as a barrel!

After the tentacle drilled into the egg-shaped stone hall, it opened up like a blooming flower, revealing rows upon rows of sharp teeth, and spat.

Pu.

A rotten corpse in the shape of a human body was spat out into the hall. After some time, the sound of the corpse falling onto the sea of bones echoed.

The tentacle spat out some more things before it retracted rapidly and disappeared into the darkness.

Nasira looked at this scene with glittering eyes.

“This creature is capable of moving freely in this place?” She said with a trace of hope in her heart.

She waited until the tentacle was retracted before moving back to the side of the entrance and cautiously took a look inside.

She saw that the walls of the stone hall were filled with holes like a beehive. Sometimes, tentacles would drill out of these holes and spit things out as though they were vomiting. A large number of things such as corpses were spat out into this egg-like stone hall.

These tentacles acted like sewage pipes. Nasira looked towards a distant hole and saw Manasi.

Most of Manasi’s armor had been melted. He was lying at the edge of the hole, looking very weak. His right arm and right leg were both missing.

Boom!!!

At this moment, Nasira heard a loud roar behind her. Afterward came a sound as though something had collided with great force.

Abruptly, a figure was ejected from a passage on her right. It was a white-haired man, whose body was covered in blood and scars and he was spraying blood when he shot out of the passage. Then, he fell straight down into the sea of bones without any sound.

Nasira narrowed her eyes. Then, she saw three suspicious masked men rushing out from that same passage. They shot out a hook from each of their bodies on to the stone wall across them, deftly evaded the tentacle behind and swung down to the bottom.

The three of them quickly reached the bottom of the stone hall and stowed their hook. After walking around the sea of bones, they entered an inconspicuous small entrance.

Only then Nasira did notice that there was a small door at the bottom. It seemed to be a man-made white stone door. The three people entered the door and disappeared.

She looked at the other side and saw Manasi nodding at her. Both of them planned on following the trio.

“Follow them,” suddenly, AG’s voice came from behind Nasira.

“You finally came!” Nasira said while turning around. She saw AG walking to her slowly with his crutch, looking very calm, though there was a black stain on the hem of his clothes.

“Are you sure? We don’t even know what those people are,” Nasira frowned.

“You’re hurt,” AG did not answer her question and only tossed a small glass bottle of green ointment to her before he headed straight for the stone hall.

Walking to the edge of the hole, his crutch slightly moved and a black gas came out beneath his feet, forming the upper body of a man. The man opened his arms and AG sat on his shoulder to fly down.

Nasira gritted her teeth and immediately jumped over. She landed on the man together with AG.

AG took a look at her. There was a trace of excitement in his eyes.

“We’ll go down and follow them first. If I’m not wrong, those three should be hunters that entered from another place for that thing.”

“Hunter?”

“That’s right. Anil’s Garden has the Scavenger, Gatekeeper and Gardener, these three horrifying existences, but since it is a garden, naturally it would have extremely rare and precious flowers and plants. If I’m not mistaken… There is an extinct plant here that I need…” AG was in a good mood.

“It helps… in that thing of yours?” Nasira asked while standing on the black gas man’s arms and looking down at the sea of bones. The closer she looked, the more shocking it was.

“If I got it in my hands…” AG said while licking his lips.

On the other side, Manasi followed them by sliding down on the stone walls. He fell down with a loud thump while scattering bone powder everywhere.

The three of them landed outside the small door at the bottom and grouped up. Apart from AG who looked normal, the other two looked extremely unkempt.

Standing in front of the white stone door.

“Do we wait for Garen?” Nasira asked.

“Wait for ten minutes, if he does not come, we’ll go in first,” AG said decisively.

******************

Xander crouched down in the middle of the camp and gently wiped the grass on the ground and smelt it.

“At least thirty people stayed here for a few hours,” he reported in a low voice. The moonlight glowed on his face and his pale face shone.

Surrounding him were more than ten elites from Nighthawk and the Combat Club.

When a few great forces integrated into the Holy Fist Palace, a whole new powerful force began to form.

A subordinate stood out and said.

“Our main force went to the Wellington Manor, I think we prioritize protecting the goods.”

“You’re right Keith,” Xander was someone who liked to listen to other people’s opinions. He stood up and scanned the people around him. “A lot of people are spying around for the secret behind our Combat Club’s Secret Techniques. Now that the President is away, this is the best time for them to act. We have to be even more vigilant.”

He waved his hand.

“Let’s go back to our trucks!”

The group evacuated the forest camp quickly and disappeared into the night.

************

The trucks drove along the road in the middle of the night like a yellow snake. This place was close to the airport where cargos were transported. Occasionally, there were street lamps that were malfunctioned but their trucks’ lights illuminated the whole place.

There was wilderness on both sides. Sometimes, tall square billboards were set up, but the rest were either hills or sparse woods.

The sound of the engines was endless and a few guards were seen on top of the vehicles.

“Damn, tonight is such a weird night. Hente and Patiya were knocked unconscious and couldn’t even see who knocked them out. I thought the goods were lost but nothing happened? Weird!”

On a truck at the end of the line, a masculine Nighthawk complained while smoking.

“People will get neurotic when dealing with these bizarre opponents all day long,” tanned woman with a black butterfly tattoo on her right arm muttered while driving with a cigarette in her mouth.

“How much you want to get is determined by how much sacrifices you are prepared to make,” the woman talked like an old-timer despite her age being only twenty-something.

“True, didn’t we chose to join the Nighthawks in order to acquire the legendary secret techniques? During the selection, so many people fought to join in. Good welfare, good treatment and it was also a large organization where we can learn the most powerful combat secret techniques. Making an effort in any organization is still making effort, but the conditions here were too good,” the masculine guy sighed, took out the cigarette in his mouth and puffed out a circle of smoke.

In fact, both of them understood that the Nighthawk Combat Club did not give out big tasks easily, and once the big tasks came, they were definitely the troublesome kind. However, to have kept them for so long, was it not their turn to repay their kindness?

Boom!!

Suddenly, a bright red light appeared at the front of the line, accompanied by a great shockwave.

One by one, the trucks made an emergency stop. The people in the trucks came out with their guns. Some looked over at the flames to the front and some people were paying attention to both sides while wearing night vision goggles.

One by one, several teams of masked people in black outfits took advantage of the night to sneak in from all sides for an attack.

Once both sides made contact, they started firing their weaponry at each other.

Xander jumped down from the car with a glint in his eyes. Except for him, the whole team was composed of only ordinary Nighthawk members who have acquired a small portion of secret techniques.

He put on a pair of special glasses and green dots and red dots surrounding the trucks were immediately revealed. The green dots were allies and the red dots were the enemies attacking them.

The green dots were decreasing non-stop. Although the red dots were also decreasing at the same time, their numbers were far greater than the green dots.

Chapter 712: Attack 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“The situation is not good…” Xander muttered while hiding behind the truck door. The special heavy truck’s doors were strong enough to block the normal bullets flying around.

In this situation, not even he dared to charge in and start a killing spree. He could sense it if there were people aiming at him but if it was a stray bullet, he could not sense it whatsoever. In that case, he would not even know how he died.

Without anyone noticing, two black shadows flashed by and quickly dived into the back of a truck in the middle of the line.

Inside the dark truck was two slender figures.

“Is it here?”

“There is no mistake. Let’s see what kind of secret the Combat Club is protecting that these people would chase after them so tirelessly,” a man chuckled and reached his hand out to touch the box with a hole.

At the instance when he touched the box.

Boom!!!!!

A horrifying presence burst out from the box.

No! It was like an eruption had occurred, as if a volcano had spontaneously erupted at his touch. It was as though there was a being that could not wait to squeeze out this box.

“Take off the mask….I will give you an unimaginable power and wealth…” a voice in the man’s mind crooned to him.

“Take off…take off…take off…” the voice kept echoing inside the man’s mind.

“Mudin!”

A woman’s shout sounded beside his ear but the voice seemed as though it came from a place very far away.

His whole body trembled as his fingertips touched a thin and somewhat coarse mask. The mask seemed to be full of little holes.

The voice tempting him echoed in his mind and brought him a sense of pleasure.

“Mudin! What happened to you?!” a woman’s voice sounded anxiously beside his ear.

The man was tugged from behind and his hand broke its contact with the box.

He came back to his senses.

“I…I was nearly controlled!!!”

This…What was this thing!!??

He took a few steps back with his eyes full of fear while staring at the box.

A pair of blood-shot giant red eyes slowly emerged from the dark within the truck. The eyes were incomparably tempting and dream-like. It did not have pupils that a human would have and had slightly golden vertical pupils instead.

“Come… Cute little fellow… Take off the mask and I shall bestow upon you power beyond anything that you can imagine…” a voice crossed over the space and echoed directly inside the minds of two Blood Breeds.

At this time, even the female Blood Breed had gone pale, and her body trembled unconsciously while she tried to break free from the terrifying power that controlled them. They did not know how, but the blood inside their bodies was boiling and out of their control.

“Go!!!”

A circle of blood lines spread out beside the woman and sent both of them flying away. They slammed into the side of the truck’s door and crashed on to the dark road before they took off.

“No!!! Come back!! Come back here!!!”

Only the two Blood Breeds could hear the ferocious roar. They could feel the huge temptation behind them as if it was their fate and destiny.

“Don’t look back!! Damn it! What the hell is that!!?” the male Blood Breed’s eyes and nose were bleeding. He did not dare to turn back and madly dashed away with the female Blood Breed, leaving afterimages behind.

****************

Inside the underground palace in the distant.

Garen narrowed his eyes.

“Someone touched the mask…”

‘Never mind that, that thing is getting more and more troublesome. Even if the mask is suppressing it, as long as someone approached it rashly, they would be contaminated by the curses of the Void Creatures that you hunted down. Once the curse activated, a number of people must die before it stops. Taking away the mask is just asking for trouble,’ Black Sethe sounded as though he couldn’t care less.

Garen nodded slightly and continued to walk.

Somehow, there was a strange presence moving in front and the smell of blood drifted in the rough passage.

“Looks like I have to hurry up and leave this place. I need to collect all the masks and handle the problems here as soon as possible,” Garen said.

‘That sounds about right.’

Garen sped up his pace. Although the speed of his pace seemed slow, each of his steps crossed a distance of more than ten meters. His speed was comparable to a speeding sports car. There was no sign of him crashing into the passage despite his lightning speed.

*******************

Inside a hall full of magma-filled cracks.

In an inconspicuous stone passage, AG walked in slowly with his cane and scanned the hall with a passionate and feverish gaze.

When he saw the huge round garden in the middle of the hall, the light in his eyes became brighter and his throat trembled visibly a few times.

Behind him, Nasira and Manasi walked out. Both of them seemed much better after temporarily stabilizing their injuries through some means.

“Where are those people from just now?” Nasira asked in a low voice.

“Right here, beside the garden,” AG whispered, “They should be trapped in here too. They can’t get out but if they can avoid the danger effectively, they can depend on the food in the garden to survive. Seems like they used this method to survive.”

Following AG’s line of sight, Manasi pointed in the air with one of his hands. A red light spread out into a triangular mirror, revealing the situation of the three people beside the garden.

Those three covered their faces but the black clothes on their body were ragged and their white hair was exposed. Apparently, they were not young people. However, at this time, their eyes were closed and they were murmuring as though they were praying for something while facing the garden.

The garden was just like a normal garden, with red and blue flowers and green leaves. The only weird part was that the sizes of the garden’s plants were much too big to be normal.

A common blue flower in there spanned a few meters in diameter. Slightly larger ones were seven or eight meters in diameter, big enough to shelter more than ten people.

Other than that, the greenery of the whole garden seemed out of place on the dense, magma-filled cracks on the ground, as though it was not affected by the horrifyingly high temperature and the poisonous fumes.

Boom!!

Suddenly, AG leaped forward, avoiding a black tentacle that was as thick as a barrel.

The tentacle was full of mouth-like suckers that were constantly sucking, giving off a horrifying feeling.

The tentacle swept to the side and mercilessly smashed into Manasi, who did not manage to evade in time.

Manasi had only managed to take out a short knife and block in front of his body, but the knife was broken by the tentacle without it suffering the smallest scratch. With a huge force, the tentacle smashed against his body.

The huge force slammed him directly into the stone wall and formed a crater.

Manasi’s forte was his strength and defense but at this moment, it was useless when facing the tentacle. He was just like a toy that had been sent flying.

AG’s eyes revealed a sharp glint. He was nearly attacked by this thing previously from the back and hurt his body. Now, this tentacle came after him again.

His cane moved slightly.

“Slow!”

A twisted transparent force fell on the tentacle, making its speed slow down until Nasira could catch up with it.

“Burn!”

AG shouted again.

In an instant, the surface of the tentacle was covered in dark bloody blisters, as though it had been burnt.

AG lifted his cane again.

“Corrosion!!” Veins stood out on his face as he shouted; he was using all of his strength to cast so many skills.

The top of the cane shone with black light and immediately dissipated.

On the other side, as his voice fell, the tentacle began to rot and melt like a candle, dripping black liquid on the ground.

The tentacle immediately released Manasi and intended to shrink back but to no avail. Nasira at the side took the opportunity to chop down and directly split the tentacle into two. The first half of the tentacle melted completely into black liquid and flowed down into the cracks on the ground before evaporating into black smoke and disappeared.

Both of them finally heaved a sigh of relief.

AG held his cane expressionlessly and ordered: “You guys go to the side of the garden and help me search for a flower with sharp petals. The flower has a layer of red and a layer of blue. If you guys find it, notify me immediately…”

Before he finished speaking, two shadows rushed out from the hole behind them with a speed that the naked eye could not follow and appeared instantly behind AG.

With the red light from the magma, both Nasira and Manasi could clearly see that it was two more tentacles that were darker than the previous one.

The snake-like tentacles bound AG viciously and tightened.

Kacha!

The sound of broken bones came from inside AG’s body, as he opened his mouth and screamed. Black light shone again on top of the cane, spreading a huge shockwave outwards and causing the two tentacles to become loose. He took the opportunity to escape but there was blood leaking from his eyes, ears, nose, and mouth.

“Go!!” He shouted. Black light shone all over his body and covered both Nasira and Manasi and then the trio morphed into a black light arrow speeding towards the garden.

When the light arrow was mid-flight, another tentacle caught up and mercilessly crashed into the tail of the arrow.

The light arrow came crashing down to the ground at the side of the garden and turned back into AG, Nasira, and Manasi. Just as he stood up, AG threw up a mouthful of blood.

“So strong!! If not for the ability to turn into light, we’ll be in big trouble this time!” he frowned. His old face became older and more wrinkled.

“Be careful, the garden is not totally safe. I’ve done some research on this place. Anil’s Garden should have three terrifying existences, the Scavenger, Gatekeeper, and Gardener. The ones we met should be the Scavengers but as long as we don’t go too deep, we should not encounter the other two monsters. If my judgment is correct, this place should be our opportunity to get out of here.”

“Opportunity?” Nasira’s mouth twitched while looking at AG throwing up mouthful after mouthful of blood. She was afraid that AG might actually die from throwing up so much blood. “You… Are you okay?”

“I won’t die…” AG said while nodding, “We can’t wait for Garen anymore. We’ll start right away and find that flower. That’s the key to getting out of here.”

Chapter 713: Monster 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“There, seemed to be some lingering scent of them here…” Garen said while sniffing. He seemed to have smelled the scent of Nasira’s perfume.

He crouched down in the passage and touched the rough rocky ground. There seemed to be a lot of holes on the ground as though a hammer had hit a lot of places here and there, making the ground uneven. There were also some pieces of crushed stones that fell from the wall.

Hu!!

Suddenly, a thick black tentacle shot out from the front of the passage to wrap around Garen’s waist.

“En?!” Garen’s eyes were wide open from shock but instinctively, his right hand chopped down like a knife on the tentacle.

Peng!!

The tentacle was chopped by the knife-hand and its surface became full of injuries in an instant. Before the tentacle had managed to even touch Garen’s body, it had been divided into countless small pieces that flew past Garen’s sides and landed on the ground behind him. The remaining part of the tentacle twitched and quickly shrunk back into the darkness before disappearing completely.

A strong sour odor was in the air.

Garen frowned and covered his nose. He fanned with one hand and created a whirlwind to disperse the odor.

The pieces of tentacle on the ground were twitching and some of them were crawling.

Garen squatted down and picked up one of the pieces before giving it a pinch.

“It has a strong corrosiveness.”

Having the ability to act freely here, it should be a creature from another dimension. It should be our hope of getting out of here.’ Black Sethe said.

“Should be.”

Garen nodded and looked at the direction of the tentacle in front of him. He sped up his pace and chased it.

*************************

Boom boom boom!!

Three tentacles waved around and tried to attack AG and the others. The other three masked people hid in a small corner. Their bodies were covered with the smelly sour liquid from the tentacle.

AG and Nasira were covered in bloodstains, and their clothes looked as though they had been attacked from the side. Manasi was dragged by Nasira and avoided the tentacles’ attacks again and again.

Lava splashed around as the debris from the crushed wall fell in.

Soon, another tentacle rushed out from a passage and joined the attacking team.

“Burn!” AG shouted.

Blisters formed on the tentacle in front of him but it quickly returned to normal.

One tentacle came flying from the side.

Peng!

AG was smashed down from the air like a baseball and crashed into the wall, creating another hole there.

“AG!!” Nasira shouted as a look of anxiety appeared on her face.

She took out a small purple fruit. It was round and looked like a peach with a sharp tip.

Touching the purple fruit, Nasira’s face showed reluctance but when she glanced at AG on the wall, he was wrapped around by a tentacle that was tightening up. Blood was being squeezed out from his nose and mouth.

She gritted her teeth.

“Go!!” She threw the small fruit in the direction of AG.

The fruit exploded in midair and turned into a purple mist. The mist condensed into an obscure human form with a presence similar to AG.

Purple light flashed and AG, who had been constricted by the tentacle just a moment ago, appeared directly in the purple mist. He flew towards Nasira with his cane.

His hand pulled out a pile of things which seemed like medicine drugs and threw them into his mouth.

“Go!”

Black light surrounded them and the three of them disappeared again into a dark light arrow that sped towards the middle of the garden. A few tentacles pursued them from the rear but when they crossed into the garden, they suddenly wilted and dried up as though something had absorbed all the moisture in them.

The tentacles hissed and retreated quickly as if they’d been electrocuted.

With a poof, the three of them collapsed into the huge garden and rolled on the black and yellow soil. They were breathing heavily and sweating everywhere. Manasi took off his helmet and revealed his black bald appearance. He was a young black man with a calm demeanor. The blue fire in his eyes was actually a special effect from the helmet.

“Are you guys alright?” AG asked. He wiped the blood from his body with a defeated look. He appeared to have aged a few more years.

Nasira stood up. Her injuries were the least serious but it might be the effect of the purple fruit she used. She looked depressed at the moment.

“I’m okay but Manasi’s leg is broken,” she responded with a wry smile, “and where is this place? Aren’t we in the garden?”

Once she said so, the other two reacted and scanned their surroundings. They were in a lush forest, surrounded by towering dark green trees. There were pine trees, broad-leaved trees, red maple and many other species of trees.

There were thick roots all around them. Some roots were entangled around other tree trunks and some were intertwined to form strange shapes.

Nasira looked up at the sky. The crescent moon in the night looked like a sickle emitting a bright halo.

Weng…

Suddenly, the ground vibrated.

Huala!

In front of them, a black-clothed masked man ran with frightened eyes. His body brushed against the plants, making noticeable sounds.

“Stop where you are!!” Nasira shouted. She needed to ask someone about this place.

A purple vine flew out from her hands, wrapped around the masked man and dragged him back.

That man was struggling while he was dragged by the vines.

Nasira took a closer look at him. This person was unable to speak. The mask on his face was not worn but grew out of his face.

This person seemed to have been born without a mouth and nose. There was only a pair of black eyes. He struggled with all his might but he could not speak, and only his eyes could show how frightened he was now.

Below his eyes, everything else was dark and seemed like linen fabric.

“This guy…!” Nasira was a little surprised but quickly calmed her mind. After all, in all the years she lived, she had seen all kinds of strange things.

“Do you understand my words?” she asked loudly.

Wuwuwu.

The man only managed to make these sounds but his eyes were still full of horror.

“He doesn’t understand,” AG said at the side and touched the man’s head. “This man was just like the three people just now, a native from here. They don’t understand our language and intelligence…” He pondered for a bit and seemed to probe around the man’s head through the palm of his hand. “Intelligence is not good. Equivalent to a few years old child.”

Weng…

The vibration in the ground had increased and seemed to be shaking.

The land cracked and something seemed to be rising from the ground.

Ah!!!…..

A deep male voice as though chanting, sounded from the ground.

“Dodge!!” AG’s expression changed and he leaped to the side. The other two, though slightly slower, also jumped to the other side.

With a poof, the earth erupted and a thick large arm with a length of seven or eight meters burst out from the ground. It was a human arm!!

Boom!!

Another arm shot out from another place. The two arms which appeared to be dark red with a wooden texture grabbed on to the ground.

Ah~~~~!!!

A low groan which sounded like a mixture between a man’s helpless sigh and a scream burst forth. The sound shook the whole forest.

The soil between the two large arms was lifted. There seemed to be something even larger coming out of the ground.

“Run!!!” AG roared. A black light came out from his cane again but the black light was trembling, unstable and unable to spread.

AG’s expression changed. He bit on the index finger on his other hand until it bled and touched the top of the cane.

His index finger immediately withered and became black, thin and without energy.

The black light finally spread and wrapped around him. This time, it sped away without changing into an arrow.

Nasira pulled Manasi back and ran towards another direction away from the emerging arms.

A few minutes after they left, the ground was finally broken through.

Three heads with a diameter of seven or eight meters came out from the ground. Each of their expressions showed happiness, anger, and anguish respectively. The three heads were close together in a triangle shape, looking very strange.

As the ground shook even more, the height of the three heads continued to rise. Below was a huge body with a width of seventeen or eighteen meters. The huge body grew taller with the three heads on top and gradually, the entire body was revealed.

This monster that came out of the ground had a height of more than thirty meters! With three heads and six arms, the body seemed to be made out of wood with a wood grain texture all over it. The surface was carved into magnificent cloth and armor, similar to an ancient warrior with a long cloth wrapped around him. The six arms were each holding different weapons. The hair on top of the three heads was like flames and screams rang from their mouths.

As soon as the monster came out, the head with an angry expression looked towards AG and the others.

This monster had a very strange shape and there was an oriental feel to it. It did not seem to have a gender and between its eyebrows was a vermillion dot.

A hand holding a large ring came crashing down, bringing the wind with it. The moon was hidden by the arm and the whole area was enshrouded in its immense shadow.

Strangely, although the movement of the arm was slow, its target, which was AG, seemed to be unable to move his legs. His body was stiff and he could only helplessly watched as the huge arm with the ring dropped down.

When the ring was a few meters away from his head, AG opened his mouth.

“Mula!!!”

A huge sound erupted from AG’s mouth. The sound rapidly distorted from its formless and invisible state into a cloud of smoke that rushed up like a rocket.

Looking from afar, it looked like white gas burst out from AG’s mouth and rushed towards the ring.

Peng!!!

The ring with a diameter that was more than ten meters came crashing down like a huge rock on the white gas.

Chapter 714: Monster 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

At this moment, blood burst out from all over AG’s body. He felt as though he’d been struck by lightning. He trembled and the white gas was quickly sucked back into his mouth before a huge force picked him up and flew him a distance away.

On the other side, two more arms holding the cloth and dagger smashed towards Nasira and Manasi respectively.

The two of them were equally miserable and bloody. They did not know how they’d evaded that attack just now. Especially Manasi, his body looked dried up. One look and anyone would know he had used a taboo technique. His armor had already been smashed to pieces and there was nothing left of it.

The mountain-like monster with three heads and six arms stepped towards AG.

*******************

Swish swish swish!!!

With three consecutive sounds, three black tentacles as thick as a barrel came rushing from the passage and smashed towards Garen with a huge force.

Garen narrowed his eyes, giving the impression that he could either be opening or closing his eyes. He took a step and left afterimages while avoiding the collision from the three tentacles. He made a circle with his fingers and lightly tapped on the tentacles.

Peng peng peng!!!

The three tentacles exploded without any resistance and broke into countless pieces before splashing on to the ground. The rest of the tentacles shrank back rapidly.

Garen sped up his pace and chased after them through the passages left and right. The broken parts of the tentacles were constantly within his sight and unable to get rid of him.

Garen’s speed had increased to a frightening extent. Every few seconds, he had to stomp on the wall or the ground to rush forward. When he reached a corner, he was able to turn in a weird way and get through it.

Soon, there was a green light in front of him getting brighter and brighter.

Hu!

With a gust of wind, Garen rushed into a giant egg-shaped cave following the tentacles.

He rushed out of the entrance and found himself in mid-air before falling down in a curve.

The walls around him were covered in green fluorescent moss. These moss became the only light source in this cave. In addition, there were numerous holes in all sizes that were passages leading to other places.

Just as Garen was falling down, numerous tentacles flew out from these holes and came crashing towards him.

These tentacles could be numbered at hundreds.

“Waterbird Fist’s Profound!” Garen crossed his arms in front of his chest.

“Dual Blade!!”

With two snapping sounds, two invisible wind blades snapped out beside him to form an X-shaped white wind blade that danced around Garen.

He moved slightly and his body was suspended in mid-air with his two arms making a complete circle.

At the same time, the crossed wind blade moved. The ten meters long blades rolled and spun, forming a huge white circle that diced the hundreds of tentacles.

Countless tentacles convulsed in pain. The chopped pieces fell down while dripping black blood everywhere, and it looked as though it was raining blood and pieces of meat onto the sea of white bones below.

This scenes lasted a few seconds before Garen slowly landed with the tip of his feet on a bone. He stood on top of the tip of a sharp bone. The tip that was sharper than a needle was unable to pierce through the sole of his shoes.

‘You are getting better at using secret techniques…’ Black Sethe said while heaving a sigh. ‘The constant fights with Nadia, together with the long period of training that kept your life on the brink of life and death, has pushed you closer towards the style of secret techniques during our era.’

“Isn’t that good?” Garen asked while scanning the numerous convulsing tentacles.

‘The fist techniques of our time were simple and efficient without any extra flashy steps. Every move was created for killing. Each fist technique had its own unique characteristics and each and every one of them was profound to the extreme,’ Black Sethe sighed. ‘Your present style is very similar to ours and this is the true path without any useless actions.’

“Yes, secret techniques were originally created for killing,” Garen said and jumped from the bone towards a small stone door at the side.

There was the smell of AG and the others from there.

With the realm he reached now and his terrifyingly strong body, even if he did not activate the Seven Star Life’s Secret Point, he would not have any problem with the numerous tentacles here.

He had an average of seven points of attributes, ten points of vitality and eleven points of intelligence which determined his speed of reaction.

Such a terrifying body allowed him to even carry out adjustments to the secret techniques he performed, which was equivalent to manipulating the effect of his secret techniques, just like what performed just now.

The forte of those tentacles was their power and speed together with their toxic mucus, but all of these did not pose any problem to Garen. The characteristics of Waterbird Fist was its ability to stimulate the blood of anything it touched and achieved an effect similar to an explosion.

Dahm had trained this explosive characteristic to the extreme. As long as he made contact, a violent explosion would occur. The power was higher than the original Waterbird Fist by a fold. On the other hand, Hochman made this explosion into a stealthy trick which traveled along the blood vessel of his enemy and attacked their heart, achieving the goal of weakening his opponent. The more he fought, the heavier the burden would be on his opponent’s heart. His opponent would end up dying due to a heart attack or ruptured heart.

This was the difference in their development trends.

Only Garen was using the most primitive Two-Faced Waterbird Fist, which had the Profound Three Strikes: Dual Blade, White Jade, Flight. Among them, Flight was the final profundity which combined the essence of West Phoenix Fist. The more an expert grasped the essence of Waterbird Fist, the more they were able to use this technique to control the power of air and formed a turbulent flow of attacks. This turbulence would naturally form a giant bird which served as proof that it originated from West Phoenix Fist.

******************

In the moonlit forest.

The mountain-like three-headed monster with six arms swung one of its arms forward. The cloth in the hand immediately spread open and became wider and wider before turning into a red gigantic serpent. The serpent’s crimson eyes stared down and two laser beams shot out from its eyes, cutting through numerous trees and boulders.

Below, Nasira was unable to dodge in time. The layer of black gas that shrouded her body was touched by the red light. The black gas roiled around and was unexpectedly polluted, changing to a murky red. The red gas crept towards Nasira while polluting the rest of the gas.

Nasira screamed and threw out a black token in her hand before escaping the black gas and retreating away.

The black token exploded mid-air and left nothing behind.

Before she had the time to be heartbroken, the hand holding a flask in mid-air turned towards her. The mouth of the flask was aimed at her.

Hu…!!

Suddenly a huge force of suction came from the mouth of the flask, sucking in the trees, stones, and soil. Those things which got sucked shrank and became smaller before disappearing into the flask.

The red flask which was not even ten meters in height was acting like a black hole. It absorbed a lot of things but it did not even have the slightest hint that it was reaching its capacity.

The suction force pulled Nasira towards the sky. She tried desperately to grab hold of some of the sturdy roots but anything that she grabbed would be sucked into the flask.

Finally, seeing that she was flying higher and higher, her eyes turned vicious. Her left arm broke and fell off and her whole body turned blurry for a moment. A rotating weird text lit up on her forehead and flashed, before her body disappeared, reappeared in mid-air more than twenty meters away and she plunged down towards the ground.

The blood that leaked from her missing arm sprayed around. Nasira endured the pain by gritting her teeth. She tumbled downwards to the bottom. Not far away, both Manasi’s hands were gone, and one of his legs was also halved. Apparently, he’d used the Broken Lizard Tail method three times and ended up in his current miserable state.

In the face of a monster which had high strength, high speed, high resistance, and an overwhelming difference in abilities, other than escaping, they had no other way to deal with it.

This three-headed monster had a surprisingly high resistance towards witchcraft. All six kind of weapons each had different abilities. The dagger could attack from a long distance, the tomahawk could deal a large web-like abnormal attack, the cloth could turn into a giant snake that attacked automatically, the flask could suck in a large number of things and the ring represented absolute strength. All the strength was concentrated on one point. If it were other weapons, they could possibly resist them, but the strength of the ring was several times that of other weapons. If they were attacked by it head-on, it could only mean trouble.

The final weapon was a long stick that could deal damage to a wide area with a stun effect. Even if it was sweeping the wind, it could still produce the stunning effect.

In the forest, AG concealed his presence and hid beside a fallen tree trunk. The other two learned from him and quickly concealed their presence. Their body lit up for a few moments before they blended into their surroundings.

“Hush… This monster does not have a sense of smell. It only has the sense of sight and hearing. If we’d hidden like this from the beginning, we wouldn’t have ended up this miserable,” AG’s voice crossed hundreds of meters directly into Nasira and Manasi’s ears.

“Is there any way? How do we get out of here?” Nasira used the same witchcraft to send her voice over. She took a look at herself and Manasi’s conditions and smiled bitterly. “This is really a place of absolute death. No wonder those who came in never got out. Even people like us ended up like this.”

In fact, the biggest difference between Upper-level, Middle-level, and Lower-level Blood Breeds was not in their pure strength and speed. They paid more attention to secretive and complex means because when they reached the level of Death Apostle, power meant nothing in the face of technology like missiles and bombs.

Therefore, the strength of an Upper-Level Blood Breed was not very strong. Just like the methods of killing a person, the bullets from a pistol and the shells from a cannon had the same result. Although the difference in power was like day and night, the result was the same, so they no longer developed in this direction.

Entering this place and encountering this sort of monstrous existence with terribly high resistances, landing themselves in this kind of mess was actually quite normal.

Chapter 715: Civilization 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Inside the magma hall.

Peng!

A hand stabbed through the stone wall and scattered pebbles everywhere.

Garen strolled out from the hole. His upper body was naked and he wore a pair of trousers with leather shoes. He gave off a neat and tidy impression, looking as if he had just finished changing his clothes and was out for a casual walk.

He looked around the hall that was scattered with pieces of bloody meat and sniffed at the sour odor that was in the air.

In the center of the hall was a circular garden. Taking a look from afar, it was filled with monstrous giant plants.

Swish swish swish!!

Three tentacles came from behind him.

Garen grabbed towards his back with one of his hands and grasped a tentacle. He pulled the tentacle forward.

Wu!!

A sharp scream came from a distant place. The transmission speed of the sound wave was faster than the general sounds and reached Garen’s ears in an instant. The surrounding stones trembled and shattered into dust and crumbs.

Ordinary people would have their eardrums broken and receive a concussion when they heard this sound wave.

However, Garen only frowned and pulled the tentacle again.

Peng!

With a snap, the tentacle in his hand was ripped out by him and thrown aside by him.

The remaining two tentacles had already shrunk back when Garen grasped one of them. They seemed to have their own independent consciousness from the way they curled back as though they were scared.

Garen noticed this when he turned his head back.

“Interesting…” the edge of his mouth curled into a smile.

‘Don’t complicate things.’ Black Sethe voiced out and cautioned against his intention to go back to trace the source of the tentacles. ‘If I’m not mistaken, these tentacles should be parasitic tentacles that have infested this place. They’ve merged with this underground palace and acts like its organs. Unless you completely destroy this underground palace, you won’t be able to kill them off.’

“Is there nothing for me here?” Garen said and frowned.

‘Go and take a look at the garden, there’s a fluctuation of teleportation there, maybe it’s the entrance to another place,’ Black Sethe suggested softly.

Garen leaped and avoided the magma-filled cracks everywhere while darting towards the central green garden.

After a few breaths, he fell on top of the garden’s white wall and peered inside.

The strange scene inside the garden appeared before his eyes.

Inside the garden was not some flowers, grasses, and giant plants but a twisted black vortex swirling around emitting a black glow. The edge was filled with giant plants which formed a huge garden.

“No wonder there’s so many green plants when there’s no water and light. It’s all an illusion that acted as a bait.” Garen said.

‘This is Void Flower Seed. There’s a small space inside that acted as a world inside. You can go and take a look inside. This thing is not dangerous because it’s just a simple teleportation gate,’ Black Sethe replied. Black Sethe was well-informed, and there seemed to be nothing that he did not know.

Garen nodded his head. He and Black Sethe shared the same body. There was no need to worry about him having malicious intents.

He jumped slightly and fell towards the black glow. In the middle of the air, he felt a huge suction force pulling him suddenly. He immediately disappeared into the vortex of black light.

***************

“Buddha Mother… Holy Phoenix!”

AG touched the surface of a huge tree with an indescribable horror in his eyes.

“This place is the land of Buddha Mother Holy Phoenix!” he said. His lips were trembling and he seemed to be in utter astonishment.

Nasira and Manasi were at a place not far behind him. They concealed their presence, leaving only the smell of blood in the air. They looked no different from the surrounding trees and were completely hidden.

“Buddha Mother Holy Phoenix? What is that?” Nasira asked. She had only used an emergency treatment for her internal bleeding. She was looking exhaustedly at AG now. He seemed to have discovered some clues about this place.

The giant’s footsteps were still shaking the ground in the distance. The only thoughts the three of them had now were on the way to leave this place.

The amazement on AG’s face soon returned to calmness but the horror in his eyes remained.

“There was a legend about an ancient eastern sect. The origin of this sect was a terrifying existence known as Buddha Mother. It was said that this existence appeared at the same time as the Blood Breeds, and they were the product of myth from the same era. As for Holy Phoenix, it refers to the secret method of that sect. Holy Phoenix Celestial Clothes means a divine bird that wore the light from Buddha or a feather coat that came from a divine bird. It could be an item or it could be a legacy. A shame… That sect had deteriorated into a thoroughly ordinary sect. There is no longer the brilliance of that era. Unexpectedly, their history could be found here!”

“Myth…Something that came from a myth really appeared in reality?” Nasira exclaimed. She was shocked and a little disbelieving. It was like telling a person that the oil lamp before their eyes was the legendary lamp that granted wishes to Aladdin, totally unbelievable.

“I’ve also heard of it…. In the Buddhist Hindu mythology, Buddha Mother is the Holy Phoenix. Holy Phoenix was also known as The Great Luminous King of Peacock with the title of Buddha Mother. Rumor has it that she swallowed Bodhi Lotus and wailed for ten days and ten nights before giving birth to Buddha,” Manasi said weakly. “Once, I went to the Buddhist headquarters but I found nothing extraordinary so I thought that it was just a myth. I never thought that…”

Kacha!!

Blue lightning flashed by and caught the three people’s attention.

They looked up at the place where the lightning flashed by.

Under the night sky, lightning flashed continuously with a hissing sound and weaved into a large net of blue lightning.

In the middle of the net, an eyeball the length of a human slowly turned into a black vortex gate.

A figure came out of the door slowly.

It’s Garen!

His eyes were vacant as though he had not figured out the situation.

Weng!!!

A huge shadow came crashing towards him. It was the ring weapon that belonged to the three-headed giant.

The sound of lightning not only attracted the attention of AG and the others, it also caught the attention of the giant. It did not mutter any sound and went directly to smashing down the strongest weapon in its hands.

“En?” Garen looked up. The electricity that flashed in his eyes disappeared and he saw the huge ring that came crashing down on him.

‘It’s a creature from another dimension! Hahaha! Heaven did not disappoint us, Kill it! Get the core inside and we can get out of here!’ Black Sethe suddenly became excited and shouted in his mind.

Garen took a deep breath which formed a whirlpool that swallowed the air in his surroundings.

From the terrifying pressure that came down on him, he knew he had to get serious here.

“First star!!”

The fingers on his right hand tapped across several acupuncture points.

“Second star!!” a dozen more acupuncture points were activated.

“Third star!!”

Hu!!

All the hair on Garen’s body stood up and the muscles all over his body bulged to form an armor-like outline.

His height increased and his palms became as big as the size of a human’s head.

There was no technique involved. He only clenched his right hand and raised it to smash the ring.

Activating the third star, Garen’s originally seven points immediately increased to around twenty points. This punch looked very normal but when the fist shot through the air, it created shockwaves. It was a shockwave that was created by powerful force together with secret techniques.

“He… He has the guts to face it head on!!” Nasira knew the power of that ring. It was at least two to three times the power of other weapons and it also had a suction force that made it hard to dodge.

Now that Garen was facing the ring head on without a change in his expression, she felt that her heart had skipped a beat and her body was almost jumping.

Comparing Garen’s three meters height to the giant’s dozens of meters was like comparing an ant to an elephant! However, with such a gap, incredibly, he still dared to face it!

AG turned aside his body with the same stunned expression on his face while watching the scene in the sky. Manasi was gritting his teeth while staring at Garen as though he was looking at a dead man.

At this moment, the sky flashed a bright light. A knife-like white light traveled across the giant’s ring.

Garen had traveled across the ring in the blink of an eye and appeared at the back of the giant’s arm and stopped in mid-air.

He stretched his body and paused for a moment before falling straight down.

Ah!!!

The giant let out a roar.

Boom!!

There was an explosion on the arm that was holding the ring. A yellow gas spread everywhere but the arm itself was not broken from the explosion.

The giant seemed to be furious. The rest of his arms came crashing from different directions towards Garen. All the different weapons started their effects and shined with crimson light.

Five crimson lights combined and formed a giant crimson hand before pressing on Garen.

Peng peng peng peng!!! Weng weng….

The sound of explosions occurred continuously and overlapped with one another. In the end, only a buzzing sound could be heard. Intense tremors spread out in all directions.

The three-headed giant’s six hands displayed a terrifying speed and left afterimages. They waved numerous times and seemed as though it became hundreds and thousands of arms, just like Thousand Hands Guan Yin.

The huge crimson hand shone with bloody red light and came crashing down on Garen like a towering pillar.

Boom!!!!!

The terrifying shockwaves had made the surrounding trees collapsed. Nasira and the others had no choice but to retreat further but were still affected by the shockwaves.

“Fourth star!!”

In an instant, a clear voice traveled through the air, calmed down the shockwaves and spread in every direction.

The voice sounded cool and calm with a tinge of viciousness.

It was Garen!

Chapter 716: Civilization 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A warm, gentle breeze blew past suddenly, and it felt as pleasant as a mother’s soft touch.

An ear-piercing cry could be heard throughout the sky immediately. It was a bird’s cry!

A terrifying shroud of whirlpool-like air currents gathered on the ground below the giant. It resembled a huge mouth that was waiting to swallow the giant’s arm.

Chirp!!!

The clear sound of a bird’s cry rang out suddenly.

“It’s back!!! That move!” AG’s eyes flashed while he glared at the abnormal changes in the sky.

“Waterbird Fist’s Profound, Soar of the Evil Phoenix!!” Nasira had also remembered this frightening move from long ago. She was terrified of reliving that previous experience ever again. In fact, anyone who had seen this move would never dare to forget its terrifying strength.

At this moment, two wings abruptly flapped open from the gigantic air currents before the shadow of a gigantic flying bird flew upwards from the ground. It flew slowly at first but sped up quickly before swooping towards the forehead of the giant.

The shadow of the giant bird was almost as large as the giant itself.

However, a strange phenomenon appeared.

When the three-headed and six-limbed giant saw the shadow of the gigantic bird, an apparent look of fright appeared on its face suddenly. The giant took a few steps backward quickly in an attempt to dodge the attack but to no avail.

His gigantic arms stopped attacking at once before he lowered all three of his heads simultaneously while pitiful and fearful expressions appeared on all three of its faces.

“Phoe…!!!” this was the first time that a sound other than ‘ah’ had escaped the giant’s lips.

“Phoe…!!! Phoe!! Phoe!!!” all three heads made the same noise loudly simultaneously.

The gigantic flying bird approached the giant’s head suddenly. However, it flew away moments later and perched somewhere where its beak was less than one meter away from the giant’s head and did not come any closer.

Boom!!!

The terrifying air currents dispersed suddenly before Garen landed on the ground in front of the giant gently.

“Phoe!!!” the giant raised his arms up high and pressed his three heads against the ground while kneeling there in a subdued manner.

‘I think that he’s mistaken you for his previous master,’ whispered Black Sethe beside Garen’s ear.

The giant’s heads where like humongous objects when they were directly in front of Garen. They formed black shadows that almost covered him.

At this moment, one of the giant’s smiling faces turned around and faced Garen. It opened its mouth and stuck its black tongue out to expose the exquisite, luxurious blood-colored throne that was embedded on the tip of its tongue.

Garen hesitated for a moment and looked at the giant before his instincts told him that he had no ill intentions.

He walked over immediately and sat on the chair slowly.

Kachak!

A cracking noise could be heard before one of the mechanisms on the chair was triggered suddenly.

The giant retracted his tongue and brought the chair back into his mouth.

Under the moonlight, Garen was instantly dragged into the giant’s oral cavity from the outside world. However, it was not a regular oral cavity. Within the darkness, the seat seemed as if it was being pushed by an unknown force before it slid downwards. The path that he had entered now seemed like an elevator that was going downwards.

His surroundings were filled with dots of blue light that twinkled like stars.

‘I’m afraid that this is a large war weapon that possesses free will but can also be controlled by you,’ said Black Sethe in a slightly grave tone beside Garen’s ear. ‘There aren’t any traces of Void Creatures at all… How strange… To think that such a terrifying and advanced civilization would exist here!’

“You’ve never seen something like this either?” asked Garen quietly.

‘No,’ answered Black Sethe surely, ‘this civilization is extremely powerful and prosperous. The glittering lights on the walls are actually energy matrices that can absorb various kinds of energy from the outside world such as light energy, wind energy, and even thermal energy. It really is a frightening skill… It’s easy for us to use a single form of energy, but to arrange and fuse so many energy matrices together while using skills that I cannot even comprehend is truly the work of an extremely advanced and developed civilization!!’

Garen had never heard Black Sethe speak in an astonished tone before. Black Sethe was one of the Ancient Endorian Demon Kings of the past. Therefore, as a strong individual who was standing within this civilization, his opinion would naturally be of value. His tone had always been terrifyingly arrogant, but now he was subdued by this three-headed, six-limbed giant.

“After hearing you speak like this, I have some expectations now,” a sliver of a smile appeared on Garen’s face. He did not hope to return empty-handed after coming to this underground palace.

‘I hope your expectations will be met,’ Black Sethe was somewhat looking forward to it as well.

The seat took Garen on a downward ride continuously before a gentle golden light appeared in front of him out of the blue.

The golden light came closer and grew brighter.

Whoosh!

The seat entered the golden light suddenly before embedding itself into another mechanism and stopping immediately after a clicking sound was heard from the slide below it.

Garen’s eyes adjusted themselves to the blinding golden light slowly. Soon, he could clearly see the scenery in the golden light.

This place was an average-sized golden circular house.

His seat was supported in mid-air by a pillar and was coincidentally positioned in the center of the entire house.

His surroundings were filled with various mystical golden symbols that were inscribed on the wall. They twinkled and constantly reflected golden light while the faint smell of sandalwood wafted through the air, and the sound of quiet chanting echoed through the surroundings.

‘The symbols around you are written in Sanskrit. Since I can read them, do you need me to translate for you?’ Black Sethe’s tone was somewhat pressing.

“No need.” Garen had already become a master in linguistics long ago and had learned Sanskrit when he was ten years old.

His eyes scanned the words around him.

The sea of over a thousand characters was only talking about one incident.

An existence called the Holy Phoenix created the Buddha Mother and gave her life and consciousness. However, only the Buddha Mother remained after they were defeated during a great war with enemies from the outside.

Most of these symbols were extolling the supreme power of the Holy Phoenix and its radiant love. There was no other information besides that.

‘Really…’ Black Sethe did not know what to say either. ‘Within the time and space of the universe, countless brilliant and powerful civilizations emerge and disappear like resplendent nightblooms that fade after dawn. No one knows the true meaning of eternity…’

Meanwhile, Garen sat on the seat quietly.

He did not know why he could feel a strange type of Qi lingering around him.

“Even if we transformed ourselves into existences that were as hard as diamonds, we would still disappear and be worn away by time and space…” he spoke softly before standing up suddenly. He stood in front of the seat and looked around at the golden symbols in his surroundings.

He carved the shapes of the symbols into his memory continuously. Strangely enough, these symbols turned into golden threads that organized themselves into brand new characters in his mind.

This was related to the true intentions of his Secret Technique, the Waterbird Fist. The general ideas and awareness of the original symbols would be echoed within these brand new words.

He simply closed his eyes, released his mind and searched to realize their true meaning.

The golden words formed golden lotus flowers in his mind that were constantly rotating and floating around.

“Holy Phoenix Scriptures…”

Once he had scanned the entire text of golden words, Garen opened his eyes and exhaled hurriedly.

“This is a practicing technique that is completely different from Secret Techniques. I can’t learn them because the other person’s body structure was unlike my own, but I can learn from its true intentions. This powerful awareness and direction resemble Nadia’s Ominous Space Path. I can also learn of other practicing techniques from the other existences in the Void that existed during other unknown times.”

A plan formed in his mind quickly.

These golden symbols had recorded the legendary Holy Phoenix Scriptures that the Holy Phoenix had practiced previously.

These scriptures would lead him on the path of absolute tyranny!

Heaven and earth would be ruled by him alone! No one could surpass him! No one would be on par with him! It would be otherwise impossible for him to achieve absolute rule, even with the Void Nine-Headed Dragon’s Will in his soul.

Garen could vaguely feel that this civilization was related to the Buddhist teachings on Earth. Otherwise, the unexpected air that surrounded these familiar words would not exist in this world.

‘Do you wish to tread on this path?’ Black Sethe’s voice echoed over. ‘The path of tyranny, I mean. Nadia chose this path but lost in the end while her army was obliterated. You will encounter worse perils if you continue on this path. You cannot afford any failures if you chose this road and you must ensure that your soul and intentions are completely pure. You must remain true to yourself and disregard the rest!’

“Deep in my heart, I know that everything will be fine!” Garen recited the first passage of the Holy Phoenix Scriptures. “What are the side effects of practicing the Holy Phoenix Scriptures?”

‘According to my assumptions, these Holy Phoenix Scriptures are more potent than Nadia’s Ominous Space Path and the Nine-Headed Dragon King’s Will. It is simply a practice that should not exist in this world. If you want to tread on this path, you must be prepared to face many enemies. You must only exist in your own physical body and cannot be contained by the Earth or even the universe. Existing only in your own physical body challenges you not to subvert the rules. As you are unable to latch on to others that are stronger than yourself, those existences will naturally become your enemies. All of these are unavoidable obstacles.’

He paused for a moment. ‘It’s like a river with choppy waters. Everyone else will follow the flow of the water and go downwards while practitioners like ourselves go upwards in the opposite direction. Meanwhile, these Holy Phoenix Scriptures are more insane as they require one to charge towards the origin of the river instantly and occupy its deepest source which is above all other existences.’

“This is clearly impossible,” said Garen while shaking his head.

‘Yes, but since this will is too strong, the existence of this civilization will continue to be utterly terrifying even if no one is able to achieve it,’ said Black Sethe surely. ‘Although it is unsuitable to be practiced by you, if you’re able to fuse its true intentions and add them to your Fist Techniques, you will reach brand new heights. Perhaps it will not be impossible for you to form a Soul Seed either.’

Soul Seed.

Garen’s mind began to heat up. He’d collected the mask to suppress Nadia and compiled the Demonic Book to form a Soul Seed. However, a new road had opened up in front of him.

‘The Demonic Book will not conflict with this. You can merge and grasp the will of the Holy Phoenix Scriptures completely before fusing them with the Demonic Book to form a stronger and better Soul Seed. I assume that once you have fully grasped the Holy Phoenix’s will, fused and recorded it in the Demonic Book, you will probably be able to form a second Soul Seed that will be worthy of a true battle with Nadia’s past thirty lives!’ it seemed as though Black Sethe was wholeheartedly praising these scriptures.

“The most important thing is that we won’t go if I’m unable to grasp the Holy Phoenix Scriptures,” Garen shook his head slightly while a forced smile appeared on his face.

‘It’s good that you understand that. The dimensions of the movements and operating methods of this war weapon are probably stored in the Holy Phoenix’s true intentions. The only thing that you must be careful about is that these true intentions may affect your will and soul. Therefore, you must fuse it into a Soul Seed in the end or it will limit your future progress. All of this is due to the fact that this is not your path, but someone else’s comprehension.’

“Understood,” Garen nodded.

He sat on the seat again and placed both of his palms flat on the armrests. He closed his eyes before the countless lotus flowers flew around in his heart like the snowflakes that danced around gently during winter.

Chapter 717: Break Away 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The outside world

AG, Nasira, and Manasi sat around a burning bonfire silently.

The flames flickered and illuminated the faces of the three people there. There was not much warmth and the atmosphere was somewhat stressful.

“Other than the three-headed, six-limbed monster here, there are definitely other troubles as well,” said AG softly after recuperating for a while.

A strange and undistinguishable air permeated throughout the gloomy woods in their surroundings.

“I wonder what happened to Garen after he entered that monster’s stomach?” Nasira furrowed her eyebrows and looked at the faraway giant. That three-headed, six-limbed monster had stopped moving completely after Garen had entered it earlier.

However, the other three people did not dare to approach it. If the monster were to move again, they might face even worse consequences and would not be able to escape at all in their heavily injured states.

“Don’t forget the reason why we entered this place,” AG stood up and began to stroll through the surrounding undergrowth and woods. His face was grim and slightly ashen from his injuries by the monster earlier. However, looks of happiness occasionally flashed in his eyes.

“If my assumptions were not wrong, this is the true garden of the underground palace.”

He bent down and gently snipped off a piece of black grass that was as dark as ink and as small as a tiny person from the bottom of a large tree. Next, he kept it in his pocket and continued searching for something with his head lowered.

“Since no one has entered this place for so many years, the medicinal herbs that grow here are frighteningly potent!”

Nasira and Manasi looked at each other. Neither of them knew how to use medicinal herbs and could only look on while AG collected these plants from the side and walked further away from them after a while.

After more than half an hour, while the rest of them were eating the baked rations that they had taken out, AG finally returned with a big bag of medicinal herbs.

When they saw the look of sheer joy on his face, they were certain that he had reaped great rewards.

“If I get to go out this time, my cultivation will definitely be able to enter the final phase!” he was able to obtain a large quantity of exotic medicinal herbs effortlessly. No matter how calm he remained, he could not help but show traces of emotions whenever he faced qualitative changes.

As for Manasi and Nasira’s broken limb injuries, the Witch thought that it would not be too difficult to connect them with the limbs of other people.

The important thing was whether or not it was safe now.

After collecting the medicinal herbs, the gazes of all three people turned to the faraway giant’s body again. They did not know when Garen would be coming out and were unsure of whether Garen had fallen into the monster’s snare and was trapped there.

The only thing they could do right now was to wait.

“If my assumptions are not wrong, this monster should be the second guard here. A monster like this is definitely concealing a lot of secrets throughout its body. It’s best that we wait for Garen to come out before making our next move,” AG decided quietly. He took out two bone plates from unknown animals and smashed them on the ground gently before many cracks appeared throughout them at once. This seemed like a divination method as he studied the cracks under the light of the fire carefully.

“I never expected that the three of us would be trapped here while the normal humans would able to…” Nasira forced a smile.

“What do you think of Garen and the Holy Fist Palace?” asked AG quietly.

Nasira smiled bitterly while Manasi shook his head with a look of utter incomprehension on his face.

Manasi glanced at the giant monster that was further away.

“I don’t know how to describe that person, but it’s simply unbelievable that a normal human like himself, neither a Witch nor even a Blood Breed, was able to achieve such great heights.”

He paused for a moment, “As for the Holy Fist Palace, I think that it will definitely play a role in the future Supernatural World!”

His tone was almost resolute and certain by now.

“The Death Apostles will not forgive him. Meanwhile, the Blood Breeds are still dominating,” AG shook his head. “It won’t be so simple.”

“But no one knows everything, right?” although Nasira was seriously injured, her arrogant personality had not been tamed at all. “For some reason, I really dislike standing with Garen. He has a dangerous air around him.”

“Me too. I don’t know what he’s hiding,” AG nodded.

Bang!

Suddenly, the three-headed, six-limbed monster stood up slowly and got up again from its kneeling position while shaking all three of its heads slowly.

“What is it trying to do?!” Nasira and the other two people stood up and warily observed the monster from afar.

*******************

Garen shut his eyes tightly while faint rays of golden light gathered around him slowly. These rays of golden light resembled golden threads that were flying and rotating around him.

He felt as if he had suddenly turned into a golden flying bird that resembled a phoenix and was currently flying through the endless void.

The sound of unclear but unusually ethereal sounding Sanskrit chanting drifted into his ears continuously, as if a crowd of people had gathered around him and were reciting passages quietly.

Holy Phoenix Scriptures… Holy Phoenix’s true intentions!

Garen’s mind sank into a state of ultimate purity in an environment where he was able to truly understand himself. All of his feelings and thoughts were concentrated within himself and the only person who could detect and ponder upon them was himself.

He closed his eyes and looked at the skill pane on his attribute pane and noticed that an additional faint gold symbol had appeared in the skill section of the Secret Techniques that he specialized in.

‘Holy Phoenix Scriptures: Inherited from an unknown civilization. It comprehends the Holy Phoenix’s true intentions and possesses a probability of improving and condensing Soul Seeds, as well as upgrading the strength of the seed.’

The Soul Seed determined the strength of the soul while the strength of the soul determined the limits of the physical qualities of the body.

The current limits of Garen’s physical body was an average of thirty points, and this was after it had been strengthened by the first Soul Seed.

There were three main phases of a soul. According to the Ancient Endorian legacy, phase one was the normal soul, phase two was the Soul Seed, while phase three was the True Soul.

Whenever a Soul Seed was formed, it meant that an awareness that had achieved a certain degree of strength had been condensed. Throughout a lifetime, complete and intact experiences were signs of independence.

In other words, each Soul Seed represented the coagulation of the peak moments of one’s life. It represented the paths and trajectories in one’s life when they tasted success.

Garen did not know how the other Ancient Endorian Warlocks crossed this path, but he was forced to walk on the path of coagulating the entire essence of his lifetime in order to achieve higher levels that would allow him to form a complete seed.

‘When you concentrate and realize things, more Soul Seeds will form and the likeliness of creating a True Soul will increase as well. Each Soul Seed can become a substitute soul that will be able to block one fatal blow towards your soul,’ Black Sethe’s voice echoed beside Garen’s ear.

The Holy Phoenix’s true intentions and the Demonic Book’s realization were already sufficiently powerful to fuse and form a Soul Seed. This was something that Black Sethe was hoping to see as well.

When the second Soul Seed was formed, Garen’s entire body would reach a higher level, and by then…

Hum!!!

Suddenly, the sound of a violent vibration interrupted Black Sethe’s train of thought.

He condensed himself and formed a black smoke figure behind Garen before looking around his surroundings.

He could only see that shrouds of golden gas were permeating inside the monstrous Buddha Mother. The large quantities of golden gas began to gather in front of Garen slowly and solidified before quickly turning into a golden, diamond-shaped gemstone that was suspended in mid-air.

A golden arc of electricity flashed across the surface of the gemstone before pictures of sceneries from the outside world floated upwards slowly.

Garen opened his eyes slowly and felt as if his entire body was enveloped in warmth. It felt as if he was basking under the midday sun or soaking in a steaming hot spring.

Two rays of golden light from the gemstone reflected into his eyes and shone into the center of his pupils as clusters of information and words glided past his eyes quickly.

All of the information regarding this monster was pouring into his eyes in a mere moment.

A look of understanding appeared on Garen’s face at once.

This information explained the origins and source of this monster and the methods of leaving this dangerous situation.

This three-headed, six-limbed monster was called Buddha Mother. It was actually created by an existence known as the Holy Phoenix. Strangely enough, the information regarding this Holy Phoenix was similar to the Waterbird Fist’s Profound: Flight of the Evil Phoenix. Moreover, the Buddha Mother was ancient, had chaotic memories and just a simple consciousness. Therefore, it had mistaken this for the previous Holy Phoenix and had submitted itself without any resistance at all.

‘Is there a way to get out?’ Black Sethe asked.

“Indeed there is. However, it’s somewhat troublesome.” Garen furrowed his eyebrows. “Large quantities of our energy resources will be depleted if we wish to escape. The Buddha Mother itself does not possess enough energy and it’ll require me to burn a part of my life energy on my own.”

‘Life energy?’

“Yes,” Garen nodded, “just like the bioenergy inside the bodies of living creatures, most humans naturally do not have it, but my strength is abundant and my vitality is strong enough. Therefore, it doesn’t matter to me.”

According to his assessment of the Buddha Mother, he estimated that if they were to leave, they would need to abandon the Buddha Mother’s large body while he would need to contribute a portion of his body’s life energy as well. This was equivalent to the vital energy and blood energy in Secret Techniques. It was a good thing that he still had potential points to make up for it. If it were anyone else, he assumed that they would just die in this place.

Garen muttered to himself for awhile. He followed the methods that were recorded by the Buddha Mother while tweaking his state of mind.

Hum…

The entire space began to move faintly.

***************

The gigantic Buddha Mother stood up slowly and swayed its three heads and six limbs. It resembled a little hill that was looking in the direction of AG and the other two people slowly.

On the Buddha Mother’s right shoulder, a blurry figure appeared there suddenly before they realized that it was Garen who was half-naked.

The taut muscles on his body resembled black armor while a terrifyingly ferocious air wafted from his body.

“AG, I’ll need your help if we’re going to leave this place.”

Garen’s voice drifted over from afar and passed through the thick woods before finally arriving at the bonfire where AG and the two others were located.

“Garen…” AG and the two others stood up.

“You know how to get out of here?” a look of surprise and delight flashed across AG’s eyes.

“Of course.” Garen leaped lightly off the body of the Buddha Mother that was over ten meters tall. While the wind made whooshing noises, a banging noise could be heard suddenly when Garen landed on the floor and made a small crater in the ground while he remained half-kneeling there.

After standing up, he took a few steps forward and seemed as if he had crossed over ten meters in less than ten seconds when his figure appeared in front of the trio instantly.

“That monster?” AG glanced fearfully at the monster from afar.

“Its call Buddha Mother and it can help us leave this place,” said Garen without explaining anything in detail.

The Buddha Mother was actually a living creature that possessed simple intelligence. Its absolute loyalty towards the Holy Phoenix caused it to hide here for many years without leaving.

“What do you want us to do?” AG buried his fear of the Buddha Mother before the man in front of him. It was obvious that Garen was currently able to control and influence the extremely powerful and large fellow that stood far away from them.

“Not only do we have to deplete all of this guy’s energy sources in order to leave this place, we will also need to burn a certain amount of energy to support it,” Garen described it as the source of all its energy to simplify the situation and the explanation that followed.

“According to the records, something even more troublesome exists in the depths of Anil’s Garden. However, we don’t have to go deeper because this space is a typical cycle. In order to break this cycle, we need to gather our strongest powers at once and condense them in one area inside the space to form a distorted and temporary hollow space before we can seize the chance to leave.”

Garen continued to explain, saying: “My strength alone will be completely insufficient. Although the Buddha Mother’s energy has occupied a large part of the consumption proportion, we still need to make up for it slightly. However, the additional amount is not something that I can endure alone.”

“Can you prove that the things you’re saying are accurate?” asked Nasira quietly.

“We don’t have any other choice,” said Garen lightly.

“We don’t have to discuss this any further. Make the necessary preparations,” commanded AG at once. He was the leader among the trio. He complied with Garen’s instructions and decided on their direction at once.

Chapter 718: Break Away 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The four of them began their preparations quickly while adjusting their state of mind.

This forest was not completely boundless and limitless. When Garen sat on the Buddha Mother’s body and observed his surroundings, he noticed that this entire space only spanned a radius of five or six kilometers and was actually very small. The sky appeared boundless and endless but was actually covered by a layer of transparent, semi-circular overlay, making it impossible for them to fly through.

Two hours later.

Within the forest, the Buddha Mother knelt on the ground on one knee slowly before AG, Garen and the other two people hid within its mouth. They used their palms to grip tightly against the inner walls of the Buddha Mother’s oral cavity so that they wouldn’t be flung about.

Faint, golden lines gradually spread across the Buddha Mother’s body. There were only a few lines at first, but soon there were ten, more than a dozen, over a hundred before they increased and spread across the Buddha Mother’s entire body.

Tch!!

Suddenly, the Buddha Mother’s gigantic body surged through the sky and rose upwards towards the transparent and almost invisible overlay above.

When it touched the overlay, the space around it became slightly distorted for a while before instantly behaving as if it had not been touched at all. Major changes occurred throughout the scenery suddenly. The night sky disappeared and was replaced by a wide magma hole above them.

The Buddha Mother did not stop at all and continued charging upwards.

Crash!

The hole shook instantly for a while before a gigantic black hole was smashed open.

The entire Buddha Mother charged towards the surface frantically like a drilling machine that was trying to excavate something. During its terrifying spurt, the spaces around it twisted continuously as if a powerful strength was determined to pull it back. However, this strength could not surpass the Buddha Mother’s own tremendous power in the end.

Ahh…!!

The Buddha Mother howled quietly before its large body speeded up suddenly. Its six limbs had begun to rotate slowly while the weapons they held moved faster to form a high-speed rotating drill.

Its entire body began to burn while strange black flames started to light up on its wood-like body. The flames increased and burned brighter. As the flames continued to burn, its body became smaller and smaller.

The surface of the ground seemed extremely far away before the last trace vanished from sight.

The Buddha Mother’s body was growing smaller and smaller.

Kachak!

One of its arms that was holding a battle ax broke off into pieces suddenly before being engulfed by the black flames.

While its arm burned, the Buddha Mother’s speed increased gradually before it resembled a ray of black light that was flying from the ground and piercing upwards quickly.

Kachak!! Another one of its arms broke off into little pieces before it burned with its weapon. This time it was the arm that was holding a long rod.

The Buddha Mother’s speed increased again before it rushed forward like a black rocket. However, the ground level seemed endless and it was clear that Garen and the others had not considered its depth when they came down.

Immediately after that, the arms that were holding the ring and flask respectively broke off and went up in flames at the same time before its speed increased once again. However, they were still unable to see any trace of the surface.

Next, the arm that was holding the silk ribbon and the last arm that held the short dagger broke off into smithereens together and began to burn.

The final stage of burning increased the Buddha Mother’s speed to a terrifying degree.

Inside the oral cavity.

Garen and the other three people sat in a circle with their palms pressed up against the inner walls of the oral cavity tightly.

“Begin,” Garen stimulated his thoughts and transferred an idea to the Buddha Mother. Once he’d inherited the Holy Phoenix Scriptures and wiped off the scriptures and passages from the inner walls of the Buddha Mother, he became the only person who could control the existence of this gigantic living creature.

The moment he used his thoughts to transmit his orders, a strong suction began pulling at his palms suddenly.

At this moment, the blood essence and aura from his body gushed outwards quickly through his palms.

The same thing happened to AG, Nasira, and Manasi. Their faces became flushed when the blood essence and witch powers from their bodies were being absorbed.

Boom!!!

There was a loud noise beside their ears before the scene before their eyes was filled with light!

The four of them could neither see nor hear anything momentarily. Their visions were only filled with the endless white light.

****************

Within a yellow sand desert that seemed boundless on first glance.

A continuous stretch of rolling sand dunes stretched towards the edges of the horizon. Layers of dust and sand resembled mist when it was stirred up by the wind. Soft, scratchy noises could be heard when they danced about.

Beside one of the sand dunes, a black flame flashed before the fire disappeared and four silhouettes appeared at the foot of the sand dune suddenly.

One of them had a body full of taut muscles and seemed too muscular to be human. Meanwhile, the other three people comprised of two men and a woman, though all of them looked unusually confused. Their clothes were torn and the elderly male was even covering his mouth tightly, as if he was determinedly suppressing his need to vomit.

Garen held a black wooden ball in his hand. It was only the size of a fist and was the core of the Buddha Mother that had remained after the creature was burned completely. As long as he had this thing, he could easily use materials from the outside world to reconstruct the Buddha Mother again. The body of the previous Buddha Mother was mainly created with wood because it lived in a vast forest.

“Where is this place?” Garen kept the Buddha Mother’s core and scanned his surroundings.

“We’ve definitely left the area this time,” beside him, Nasira had already taken her phone out and checked it, before noticing that they had phone signals here.

“There are phone signals here. Looks like we’ve truly left,” AG nodded. “My phone was smashed completely. Nasira, determine our current location.”

“Doing that now.” Nasira lowered her head and focused her eyes on her phone.

All of their other equipment had been destroyed during the journey. Although Garen was not injured, he did not have a handphone with him. Therefore, he merely climbed up one of the surrounding sand dunes and stood there before looking into the distance.

The strong winds blew the sand and dust upwards and obscured their vision, making it impossible for them to see their surroundings clearly.

Soon, Nasira was able to contact the headquarters of the Dark Colors’ witches to determine the location of herself and the three other people.

They were in the deepest part of the Ganneling Desert which was also the world’s largest desert.

Even with their strength, the four of them still felt unusually hot here.

The temperatures here reached forty to fifty degrees. Only Garen’s exceptionally strong vitality could ensure that his pores would shrink on their own to prevent the water in his body from evaporating. As for the temperature, although the lack of water loss would cause his body temperature to increase, his 10 point vitality could resist temperatures of hundreds or even a thousand degrees. Therefore, he was not worried about the temperature at all.

The other people found other ways to combat this respectively.

AG’s skin was pale and somewhat discolored but could turn mirror-like whenever light was present. His skin could reflect large amounts of light and heat which created the effect of lowering his body temperature.

Nasira was even stranger as beads of water would form on the surface of her body occasionally. She seemed to possess the ability to absorb and condense water directly from her surroundings. It was obvious that the condensed water droplets on her body were not sweat.

Finally, Manasi was slightly worse-off, but he still had his own methods of beating the heat. Purple patches began forming all over his body before the remaining pieces of armor on his body released cold air quickly and continuously to help him cool down from the broiling heat.

The four of them decided on one direction before moving forward quickly. The rows of footprints that they left in the desert were covered in less than 30 seconds, leaving no traces behind.

Although they were heavily injured, the powers of these four people allowed them to easily surpass the speeds of average humans and achieve the speed of a moving car.

Midday passed and late afternoon arrived before the temperature decreased gradually. Soon, they entered the area of the desert that was further away from the center.

Two weirdly-shaped white cars stopped right in front of them. A group of people got down from the car and walked towards Nasira and bowed in front of her respectfully. All of them were wrapped in white gauze, making it impossible to see their faces and bodies.

When they sat in this white car, they noticed that it was traveling at a frightening speed. The vehicle left the desert while the sky was dark before entering a little town on the border.

Only then did AG contact his own people. Throughout the journey, he did not mention the Thousand-Legged Serpent at all as if he was completely unconcerned about whether it was dead or alive. Perhaps Garen’s presence made it unnecessary for him to ask questions.

Garen contacted his own people as well. They were currently in the southern part of Africa where the Nighthawks’ base was also located.

At nightfall, some of his subordinates from the Nighthawks rushed over to the little town called Damu.

During the final burst of speed and flames, the four people, including Garen, had suffered serious injuries. Therefore, they returned to continue recuperating. They did not say much to each other before joining their own subordinates.

“I’ll definitely visit you at the Holy Fist Palace when I’m free,” faint red light flashed in AG’s eyes before he left.

“You are very welcome to do so,” Garen could feel the flourishing and terrifying Qi that was being released from AG’s body. It seemed as though he was anxious to return and seal his practice. Moreover, it was also clear that the big bag of medicinal herbs that he was carrying was extremely precious to him.

Compared to Nasira and Manasi, AG had already been much stronger than them previously. Now that he was given this opportunity, it was only a matter of time before he would be able to proceed with the terrifying living creature sacrifice that he was planning.

Although three of them had suffered heavy losses of power and were badly mauled this time, they were able to reap great rewards. It seemed as if AG was more likely to enter the Death Apostle level now while Garen had gained the Holy Phoenix’s true intentions and the Buddha Mother’s core.

Nasira and Manasi did not reap any physical gains, but this experience served as a great training experience for them. They were originally AG’s subordinates and part of his Lightless Alliance. Moreover, Nasira had once mentioned that AG had trained them since they were young as if they were his disciples but also his lovers, making the relationship between them very unusual.

When they left, Garen got into the Nighthawks mercenaries’ armored car and tidied himself up before leaving this little town called Damu.

Under the night sky, he sat in the car and looked at the nighttime scenery of Africa from afar. Along the yellow roads, gazelles would leap by occasionally while lions lay lazily by the roadside, waiting for the night which was their true hunting time.

Roar!!

A few lionesses and a male lion walked slowly and obstructed the middle of the road. When the heard the noises of the car, the pride of lions turned their heads and looked over. When the car lights shined on them, a glossy green sheen appeared in their eyes.

Usually, the armored cars would wait for the lions to back off upon realizing that they were in danger. However, they did not need to trouble themselves when Garen was in the car.

Behind the car window, he glared at the lions in front of him. His shadow that was in a sitting position twisted itself quickly and grew longer before extending towards the lion pride like a black shadow monster.

Whoosh!!

A few lions ran away in a frenzy before disappearing into the night without a trace.

The deputy of the convoy was a young muscular black man whose expression turned respectful and enthusiastic immediately.

The convoy continued moving forward. More than ten armored cars cruised through the road leisurely. Even elephant herds would flee in panic when they noticed Garen’s aura.

“Commander, Master Hochman and Marshall Dahm have already arrived in Africa. They are currently on their way to meet you at top speed,” said an informant behind him softly at this moment.

The atmosphere within the car turned slightly stagnant at once.

“Meet?” Garen chuckled. His face was utterly defeated and his entire body had suffered heavy injuries because his blood essence and aura were burnt. Moreover, his levels had deteriorated by a few degrees as well.

“Looks like we went missing for a long period of time. Their injuries have healed completely. They still have the energy to meet me?”

Garen laughed coldly.

“Get rid of everyone in the third car,” he commanded suddenly.

The deputy was slightly shocked, and so was the informant behind him.

“Do you not understand?” Garen eyed the deputy. The latter felt his entire body tremble suddenly before he turned on his communication device quickly and contacted the cars in the back.

Numerous armored cars stopped suddenly and blocked off the front, forcing the entire convoy to stop. Large groups of people in armor got down from the car before a series of loud gunshots could be heard shortly after.

Garen remained in his seat. There was a calm expression on his face but a hint of a sneer had appeared at the corners of his mouth.

Chapter 719: Situation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Meet?” Were they really here to meet him?

Deep in his heart, Garen had already understood everything. After the battle with the Blood Breed Wellington, both Hochman and Dahm’s powers had reached extremely powerful levels. That battle resulted in qualitative changes that upgraded the seeds within their bodies. Furthermore, their natures would not allow them to resign themselves to being controlled by the Holy Fist Palace for an eternity.

Loud gunshots could be heard outside the car but Garen remained in his seat quietly. He did not move and waited silently for the noises outside to cease.

After a short while, the gunshots stopped before they were replaced by the sound of someone yanking a heavy object out of the ground and smashing it against the floor.

All of Hochman and Dahm’s planted agents within the convoy were taken care of completely. Not a single one remained.

The sound of car doors opening and closing again could be heard from the back quickly.

The deputy got into the car again and spoke respectfully.

“Commander, all of the people in the third car have been taken care of properly.”

“Continue on our journey, quickly,” said Garen casually.

Engine noises could be heard throughout the convoy again as they began to move forward.

Seconds and minutes ticked by and the drivers switched twice. Finally, they reached a part of the road that was much better maintained. There were even simple fences on the border. Meanwhile, advertisement boards on the roadside passed them slowly.

Soon, many cars drove towards them from the opposite directions. Most of these cars were cross-country jeeps. More passersby appeared on the side of the road as well.

“We’re going to reach Ansett soon,” said the female driver softly.

Garen nodded and opened his eyes. He suddenly noticed that the road in front of them was getting wider.

“Get ready to stop the convoy.”

“Yes,” the female driver did not object at all. She used her communication device to contact the vehicles behind her before slowing the car down gradually.

Moments later, two separate convoys of cars stopped beside the road in front of them from afar. Those two convoys seemed to separate the people on both sides. From afar, they could hear the sound of the engines roaring while people got down from the cars on the left and right sides respectively.

The ones leading the way were Hochman and Dahm. One of them was extremely muscular and dressed in a black shirt and trousers while the other one had a slender body and was wearing a tight-fitting bright red leather jacket. Both of them looked strange.

Hochman and Dahm watched the convoy approach them from afar before lowering their heads slowly as a sign of respect.

A faint smile appeared on Garen’s face while he remained inside the car.

The car stopped within less than five meters in front of the two men slowly while driving close to the side of the road.

Garen opened the car door and got down before his eyes scanned across the duo in front of him.

“You arrived really quickly,” he said casually.

“Since our Master was in trouble, our natural response as disciples was to rush over and help at the first moment. This was the right thing to do,” answered Hochman quietly. “We’ve already made the necessary arrangements. We will go to the airport in front immediately and take a personal jet that will fly directly to New York. Master, please get in the car.”

“Everything has been arranged accordingly over at the Holy Fist Palace as well. You don’t have to worry, Master.” Dahm stood on the sidelines and spoke respectfully in a voice that was neither feminine nor masculine.

“You’re truly my beloved disciples, huh…” Garen smiled happily before taking large strides towards the luxurious and exquisite sedan that had been prepared behind the two men.

Behind him, Hochman and Dahm clenched their fists simultaneously before a strange atmosphere began to permeate around them slowly. The power that they were concealing gathered in one place like the silence before the storm.

Both of them glanced at Garen’s unprepared back from the corners of their eyes unconsciously.

Garen’s face seemed abnormally defeated and this was the first time they had seen him in such a tight fix. Although they did not know the reason behind this, it was still a once in a lifetime opportunity…

Faint blood red auras and light burned throughout Dahm’s body. He clenched his right hand gently and released it before the blood red nail polish on his five fingers turned brighter.

Clap!

Suddenly, a hand grabbed his right shoulder.

Dahm was shocked and turned his head around to look before realizing that it was only Hochman. The other man was shaking his head at him faintly.

Clap!

The sound of a car door being opened could be heard from the front.

Neither of them dared to make any more moves. Instead, they dispersed quickly and followed behind closely.

“I just received the news that all of my men have died. It happened last night on the way back,” Hochman whispered in Dahm’s ear quietly while the latter felt his heart sink slightly.

Both of them glanced silently at Garen who was now sitting inside the car. Although Garen was not looking in their direction, they could feel a strange gaze that was directed towards them from Garen’s body.

“Go! Return to the headquarters!”

Hochman spoke quietly.

Dahm took a deep breath. After being tortured previously, his whole body had become skinnier, and a fearful shadow flashed in his eyes while he followed Hochman closely.

*************************

Half a month later…

Wellington Manor

“What?! Those three people have left!” inside the dark hall, a frail voice could be heard suddenly. The voice sounded extremely shocked.

Before him was a half-kneeling figure clad in a black cloak.

“Four days ago, two of the elders left Kaska. We don’t know of their whereabouts as they did not leave any messages. However, we have intensified the search. Elder Tu Lan wanted to let you contact them personally.”

The figure spoke quietly.

“That guy…” the frail voice became softer. “Get up first and then speak, Pigus.”

“Thank you, Elder,” the man in the black cloak rose respectfully. “Great Elder, your subordinates want to deliver something that they found in the surroundings of the family’s secret passages. Once we appraised it, we realized that there is a seventy percent chance that this object is an important item that belongs to the Holy Fist Palace.”

“Oh?” the Great Elder sat upright in his seat while a strange expression appeared on his face. “Bring it here.”

“Yes.” The man in the black cloak removed a little box with a pitch-black cover. No one knew what was inside.

He held it with both hands respectfully before walking towards the Great Elder’s seat and passing it to him.

“This is?” the Great Elder outstretched his hand and received the item before opening the box at once.

But there was nothing inside!

Bang!!!

The man in the black cloak pressed both of his palms together in the shape of a sharp claw before striking at the Great Elder’s chest suddenly.

Hahahaha!!

A tearing noise could be heard from the man in the black cloak as if a powerful invisible Qi had torn him into many pieces.

Pigus’ ferocious guffawing face was exposed underneath the cloak.

“Great Elder, Master Dahm from the Holy Fist Palace sends his regards!”

Boom!!!

The Great Elder smashed one of his fist’s against Pigus’ body before sending him flying violently.

Pigus was sent flying and crashed into the wall painfully. A large depression formed there before he bounced off and rolled on the floor. He rolled more than ten times consecutively and his entire chest had been stabbed through.

However, the low rumble of his laughter continued to echo throughout the hall continuously.

“You… You…!” the Great Elder’s chest had sunk inwards. Although he was an Upper-level Blood Breed, he was unable to defend himself from a Middle-level Blood Breed’s powerful punch, which could pierce through his chest. The injuries that he had suffered could not be ignored at all.

The thing that shocked him even more was that the injured areas were becoming unbearably itchy. It felt as if numerous little insects were constantly biting his wounds and crawling into the deeper parts.

He glared at Pigus below him with a mixture of fear and rage. This was the core of the Wellington family that only the Elders could enter. Furthermore, its insulation effects were also extremely strong. Pigus had always been one of his most trusted confidants and one of the most elite leaders within the Middle-level Blood Breeds.

On the ground, Pigus crawled upwards with much difficulty. However, his nimble movements allowed him to leap backward quickly before closing the distance between them in a flash.

“Great Elder, the glory of the Wellington family has passed. There’s an ancient Asian saying that goes ‘A wise man submits to circumstances’. As long as you’re willing to submit and pledge your allegiance, Master Dahm from the Holy Fist Palace will not treat you unkindly at all. Instead, he will definitely place you in a higher position!”

A deceitful and ruthless look appeared on his face.

“You… Why did you have to betray me…” the Great Elder could feel that the itchiness from his chest was spreading throughout his whole body. His body’s self-healing abilities were completely useless now. He had never been a fighter, and although he possessed the physical qualities of an Upper-level Blood Breed, he could not release his fighting abilities at all. Therefore, in reality, his power was only sufficient to suppress Middle-level Blood Breeds.

“We can only learn the ways of the supreme Fist Techniques by submitting ourselves and pledging our allegiance to the Holy Fist Palace. This is true power! As part of the secret party, didn’t we only gather to pursue power?”

This Middle-level Blood Breed named Pigus was already being controlled by the Waterbird Fist Primer that Dahm had passed on to him.

After the Wellington battle, Dahm and Hochman began attempting to pass on the Waterbird Fist by using their auras to set up primers as measures to control the Blood Breeds.

These measures could truly create powerful functions that could control the life and death of a Blood Breed. However, the most important aspect was that it was still being completely supplied by Garen.

Generations of Blood Breeds could always be suppressed by the blood in their bloodlines. The Upper levels would control the Lower levels, making the latter completely unable to resist due to the difference between their powers. However, Garen’s research regarding the soul and flesh had greatly surpassed this world. He was finally able to solve this issue after some probing.

Using the experience that he had gained from dissecting creatures in the Totem world, Garen successfully implanted his soul primer into the blood of a Blood Breed before fusing it completely as one body. He was able to achieve his goal of properly suppressing the instincts of this blood.

Although Garen was unable to return for half a month, he was finally able to find a way to control the Blood Breeds’ Secret Techniques. He could quietly control Middle and Lower-level Blood Breeds now, and once he obtained the poison that old man AG was refining, the scene before him would occur again.

****************

Simultaneously, within the barren hills of South America

“Dead Waterbird Fist!”

A red shadow flashed past quickly and drew a blood red line in the air before falling on a large white stone gently.

This place was actually a narrow valley.

Within the valley, a figure in white clothes was sent flying horizontally in an extremely embarrassing manner. The figure crashed against one of the stone walls in the valley with a ‘bang’ before falling into a pile of rubble and sand.

After he was struck, the clothes of the figure in white were stained with a grey layer. He crawled upwards with much difficulty while faint scars could be seen all over his hands and body.

This was a pale but handsome man who had a head of beautiful blue hair that was currently dripping with sweat and sticking to his forehead. Despite his scars, his beautiful face could still be seen.

He turned his head around determinedly and looked at the red figure that was standing behind him on a large rock. His eyes were filled with panic and fear.

“I’ve always hated those who are more beautiful than me…” a voice that was neither masculine nor feminine echoed from the large rock.

Bang!!

A horrific gash was opened suddenly on the left side of the man in white’s neck. Bright red blood sputtered outwards and fell on the ground. Strangely enough, the blood attempted to move backward and flow in the direction of the man in white, as if it was a living creature. However, it was immediately intercepted by a black shadow, causing it to lose its activated abilities at once. It condensed and solidified before turning into normal blood.

Although the man in white had just suffered serious injuries, his neck was still able to heal quickly in a strange manner. The wound shrunk quickly at a speed that was visible to the naked eye.

“You…!!” an expression that displayed his fear of death appeared in his eyes, exposing his thirst and desire for his life.

“Don’t… Don’t kill me… Don’t!!” He begged loudly before his entire body slumped to the ground lifelessly. He was not out of strength; he had merely lost every bit of resistance in his heart.

Chapter 720: Situation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Is this really the Wellington family’s high-level elder? You’re too weak…” the red figure leaped lightly and landed before the man in white. His crimson leather boots clicked past the coagulating blood puddle.

“I merely chased you for about ten kilometers, but that was already too much for you. You’re just like that Middle-level Blood Breed previously… All of you are truly a decaying race…” Dahm lowered his head and looked down contemptuously upon the Wellington elder who was crawling on the ground and begging.

After his fierce battle with the Upper-level Blood Breeds previously, his Dead Waterbird Fist had finally improved to the next level and he’d successfully created a terrifying Secret Technique. He combined the essence of the various martial arts sects and merged it with the most profound principles of the Waterbird Fist to form a fatal move that utilized steel wires and threads as weapons.

The vibrations of his terrifying Dead Waterbird Fist were transmitted through these wires and threads to achieve the effect of death upon contact. Even though his destructive power had decreased slightly, his fighting angles were trickier and scarier as his destructive range had been increased greatly.

At this point, the Dead Waterbird Fist had finally left the basic domain of the Waterbird Fist. It had become a Fist Technique sect that Dahm created on his own that was equivalent to the Waterbird Fist’s branching fist techniques. In theory, there were three realms of the Dead Waterbird Fist, and each realm could be separated into five levels.

This realm relied on the control of the steel wires and threads.

There was one wire in the first realm, two in the second realm, and three in the third.

As for the levels of each realm, they were determined by the length of the destructive powers that controlled the steel wires.

Dahm currently stood within the first realm, meaning that he could only control one wire. However, his length reached the fifth level and was enough to allow the steel wires to kill its enemies even after extending to a length of fifteen meters. This skill could produce terrifying fatalities and injuries; as long as an enemy touched it, their blood would burst out.

“Don’t kill me… Don’t… The head of my household will come back soon and he’ll never forgive you!” the blue-haired man half begged and half-threatened him while yelling.

“The head of your household, huh…?” Dahm licked his lips while his blood red lipstick stained his tongue.

Looking down at the terrified, blue-haired elder in front of him, Dahm narrowed his eyes and took a few steps forward, before reaching his hand out and patting the other man’s head gently.

“Don’t worry, of course I won’t kill you… You’re still very useful after all…”

**************

America

Naberdarth Mountains

The highest peak named Ares seemed as though it could pierce the heavens. The tip of the mountain penetrated the sea of white clouds and extended into the endless sky.

After passing through the cloud layer and continuing upwards, there was a large depression on the side of the mountain peak. Within the depression was a large, exquisite snow-white castle, one that resembled a gigantic white harp that gradually increased in height from the left side to the right.

There was a large cylindrical pipeline extending from the left side of the castle. A substance that resembled white gas flowed out slowly and continuously down into the sea of white clouds.

The white gas billowed like extremely cold air. The cylindrical pipeline that was releasing it had a diameter of ten meters while it was bordered by a winding mountainous path that led close to the peak.

The snowstorm made whistling noises while snowflakes fluttered downwards like feathers. Although they piled up on the peak of the mountain continuously, somehow, there was no buildup of snow upon the path.

The sky was bright now while snow continued to form thick clumps. A line of people walked up the little path slowly. They were all dressed in black coats and wearing hoods over their heads. Although they were walking on the slippery frozen steps, they seemed unusually steady.

There were five people altogether, and each of their faces was fully hidden underneath the black hoods.

Crunchy, scratching noises could be heard whenever they trod on the piles of snow on the steps.

The person who was leading the group raised his head. He looked at the pointy white castle, which was still a few hundred steps away from them, from afar. He pulled off his hood to reveal a male face that was persevering against the cold. Only then was it obvious that this was Hochman, who had just returned after completing a mission.

“The weather here has become increasingly abominable… Ever since Master decided to move here,” he murmured softly.

Although he did not speak loudly during the snowstorm, the four people behind him were able to hear him clearly.

“Boxing Overlord Master, aren’t these abominable weather conditions and environments coincidentally suitable for sharpening the willpower and perseverance of the students who came forward to learn from you?” this person removed his hood as well, revealing the face of a man with a burn scar on the bridge of his nose.

This man had no hair and yellowed skin. There was a dark green tattoo of a tiger on the top of his bald head while a large gold hoop dangled from one of his earlobes, making him look unusually exotic.

Furthermore, he spoke English with somewhat inaccurate pronunciations because he often curled the tip of his tongue.

“Eastern Pole Gate Master has pretty good ideas,” nodded Hochman in agreement.

“Warriors should focus on Fist Techniques from the start. They should always use their external conditions as forms of nourishment to sharpen themselves to reach even higher realms!” Eastern Pole Gate Master, the diplomatic representative of the Eastern Pole Technique of the east bowed his head and spoke sincerely. He possessed a kind of revered pursuit and fanaticism regarding Fist Techniques.

The three main Fist Techniques of the world, Eastern Pole Fist, Sandt Fist, and Mocksaw Sword Sect each had a specific niche. Their combat and martial arts styles were formed by the history, culture, beliefs, and national spirits of their own countries and it was obvious that they were influenced by their local characteristics and manners.

The Eastern Pole Fist sect had the most techniques. They had bare-handed palm techniques, leg techniques that focused on energy, as well as techniques that utilized various weapons. However, its specialty was focusing on the strength of one’s own body during moments of killing to unearth, evolve, and train one’s own potential.

The Eastern Pole Fist was a large organization that used ancient cultures that were inherited as the core energy of its Fist Technique. Their main focus was the discovery of the direction in which the forthcoming Eastern Pole Gate Master’s expertise lay. They prioritized training to strengthen their bodies and practiced moves to complement them.

Hochman was bringing him to the Holy Fist Palace as he had previously communicated with the Eastern Pole Gate Master and knew that his terrifying powers were on par with his own. Hence, the Eastern Pole Gate Master had wanted to find out if Hochman’s current powers had truly reached the frightening peak upper levels.

A major factor that influenced this was caused by Garen’s continuously terrifying improvements. However, Hochman’s strength was insufficient to take down the Eastern Pole Gate Master as that man was unimaginably powerful.

When he saw the Eastern Pole Gate Master Du Xinglong’s sincere expression, Hochman sighed in relief.

Other than the Blood Breeds, there were other mysterious powers that were hidden in this world. It was only that the Blood Breeds had been too prosperous that they were forced to hide their strength quietly.

However, the current internal strife among the Blood Breeds had resulted in heavy losses. Therefore, the other forces had become involuntarily restless as well.

“We’re almost there. The housekeeper has already prepared a banquet in the palace to welcome and entertain a few honored guests,” said Hochman gently.

“Thank you for your trouble,” Eastern Pole Gate Master Du Xinglong nodded.

The line of five people quickened their footsteps and rushed towards the mountaintop where the pristine white Holy Fist Palace was located.

Both sides of the arched palace doors were already pushed open by the servants in preparation to welcome their guests.

Hochman and one of his subordinates led the Eastern Pole Gate Master and his two disciples through the palace doors. They walked into a white pointed hall that was over a hundred meters tall and followed the carpet-like stones on the ground directly towards the deepest hall.

Both sides of the hall were formed with exquisite walls that were engraved with various patterns. Strangely enough, it fitted perfectly with its crude and ancient exterior, as if there was a kind of faint harmony between them.

A young person in white led them out of the deepest hall while walking on the left side, before passing through a long corridor that had fortified glass on the left. Through the glass, they could look down at the endless sea of clouds that created mind-blowing sceneries.

The young person in white who led them was a local youth who had been training here regularly. These people had learned about the existence of the Holy Fist Palace through its reputation from the World’s Combat Competition. Furthermore, factors such as the large quantity of potential seeds that were sent here, the interesting combat competitions that constantly renewed people’s outlooks on general knowledge, the martial arts that could allow one to dodge bullets, strengthen vision, or even unearth one’s reactions and intelligence, as well as exiting combat and fights had attracted many youths who were interested to learn martial arts.

Of course, the most important reason was the chain of effects that had formed after the competition, such as the individuals who practiced martial arts who relied on their five powerful senses and terrifying skills who could now excel in various jobs. Some of them even surpassed regular humans greatly. It was evident that these exercises had greatly influenced the previous employment issues of martial arts practitioners.

This was especially apparent in the combat club that Hochman and Dahm had organized. In the initial stages, their martial arts had produced terrifying results and could even shock the American military force. Moreover, both of them were even hired as special trainers in the army. Although the effects were not extremely obvious, it still served as a test of their power.

These reports naturally spread rapidly to the powerful countries throughout the world. Within a few years, Hochman and Dahm had transformed from regular youths who knew nothing about martial arts into terrifyingly strong martial arts masters that were regarded as overlords in their own groups.

After Hochman was able to single-handedly defeat fifteen armed special forces soldiers, the world instantly regarded martial arts with a newfound passion.

These were Hochman and Dahm’s plans all along. They wanted to form a holy site for martial arts in the world to upgrade the Waterbird Fist to unprecedented and terrifying heights.

The initial results of this plan were already beginning to appear now; whenever they faced financial issues, they would receive a large amount of aid and support from the Rexott Group. Currently, the Rexott Group had already become collaborative partners with Holy Fist Palace.

Eastern Pole Gate Master followed the guide and walked forward. They passed through ring-shaped stone doors that led to stone halls, where there were maids who helped them put on specially cleaned clothes while taking their original coats off to wash and dry.

The row of five people arrived at a spacious training hall where ten people were currently split into two groups to practice sparring constantly. Each of them used all of their strength and did not hold behind at all.

The eyes of all three members of Eastern Pole Gate widened.

The sound of fists and feet colliding with one another and tragic howls could be heard continuously, while medical personnel occasionally removed the injured individuals.

None of the ten practicing students were over thirty years old. All of them were dressed in dark grey uniforms with focused expressions on their faces. Their movements were extremely normal and only comprised of a few basic striking techniques. Nothing was exceptional except for the fact that they seemed to be unusually strong.

“This is the training hall that is specially used for the Holy Fist Palace’s White Cloud Gate,” Hochman explained.

“White Cloud Gate?” Eastern Pole Gate Master furrowed his eyebrows slightly. “As far as I know, when the Holy Fist Palace was established, His Excellency only possessed the Shooting Shadow Secret Technique and the Waterbird Fist that were combined into eternal Fist Techniques. This White Cloud Gate is…?”

“The White Cloud Secret Technique is a powerful and new martial art that was hidden by the Master and was not taught to the others previously. This Secret Technique requires longer practice durations,” smiled Hochman. He raised his hand and pointed towards the highest row of seats in the hall from afar.

“The Master is over there. The ones beside him are the chief disciples of the White Cloud Secret Techniques.”

Eastern Pole Gate Master looked towards the direction where Hochman’s finger was pointed before instantly noticing a handsome golden-haired man with a terrifyingly powerful body and a relaxed face who was seated upright on the white stone seat.

There were more than a hundred meters between them but his gaze was detected by the other man. The man turned his head over while a bolt of lightning flashed in his eyes.

Eastern Pole Gate Master Du Xinglong’s head became dizzy for a moment and his body shivered slightly. He had almost lost his balance as well.

“There’s electricity in the room!!”

He was astonished.

Chapter 721: Situation 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Welcoming, from the East, Gate Master Du of the East Pole Gate.”

A clear voice traveled over a hundred meters, reaching their ears.

“The banquet is ready, be my guest!”

Garen stood up, gesturing his invitation with one hand, and then he walked into a small door on the right.

The others hurried after him, Hochman nodding slightly at Garen, as though hinting something, before he walked away alone, without a word.

Du Xinglong and the others followed Garen through the door, into a medium-sized private room, with a round table in the center that was already laden with a variety of dishes. Most of the dishes were oriental, they could tell that this was prepared beforehand.

After the few of them took their seats, maids immediately served them appetizer soups.

It was steaming hot and smelled delicious.

But Du Xinglong’s attention was not on the food, his gaze wandering instead to fixate on Garen, who was sitting in the top seat of the table.

“The representative of the Sandt, Tamms, is already here, and is currently showering and changing. They will be here soon, so kindly wait a while.” Gare clapped, and instantly a few pretty Asian girls sat beside Du Xinglong and his two disciples. They were pure and cute, with a hint of childlike innocence. Their white robes proved that they had been selected from among the disciples and students.

Ever since the Holy Fist Palace was established, and after the World Fistfighting Championship was held, they kept accepting combat enthusiasts from all around the world.

Dahm and Hochman, who were good at business, straight-out began recruiting pretty and cute girls under the age of sixteen from all over the world to work in the palace, their status allowed them to learn some fistfighting basics occasionally, but they also had an enviable salary. Their job was specifically to attend to guests at parties, serve the elite members, and so on.

These were all young girls who had signed ten-year contracts, they took shifts every half a year, after they left the mountain, they could enter the prestigious private university founded by the Hochman family and the Rexott group.

Du Xinglong, on the other hand, was fairly unwavering, he was not affected in the slightest. His two disciples, however, were passionate to begin with, so now that they saw so many pretty Asian girls sitting so close to them, their gazes were instantly fixed onto the girls.

Garen and Du Xinglong casually discussed the current situation regarding East Pole fistfighting, and the conversation moved to the World Fistfighting Championship that had just been held.

“The main objective of the World Fistfighting Championship was to properly show off fistfighting to the world, instead of constantly hiding everything in an unseen corner. As martial artists, we should spread the glory of martial arts. However…” Du Xinglong said with a frown. “Many fist techniques were meant for killing rather than performance, once we get serious, permanent injuries or even death are all possible, the destructive power is huge. And if we treat it as merely an exchange of techniques, that would be like a tiger whose claws and teeth were wrapped up in thick cloth. Without sharp teeth and claws, the intensity of the move would naturally be reduced greatly. That way, we naturally would not be able to demonstrate properly useful fist techniques… May I know what Mr Garen thinks of this?”

“This sort of situation is bound to happen,” Garen said calmly. “But we are living in a society governed by laws, martial arts are no longer a weapon of war, now they have become merely ways and methods to train one’s body, this is the general trend, and no one can change it. What we need to do is to stay calm and focused, we need to treat both competitive fists and killing fists objectively.”

“It seems Mr Garen already has an opinion?” Du Xinglong said fixedly.

Just then, two more middle-aged men wearing golden headscarves walked in, both of them were dressed in white robes embroidered with snakes and birds, and they folded their palms, bowing respectfully at Garen after they entered.

“Your Excellency Thams, welcome.” Garen stood up with a smile. “Please, sit.”

Immediately young girls from Europe and Arab respectively came up to serve them at close quarters.

The two of them took their respective seats, and two more entered just behind them.

This time the two guests carried long, thin swords on their backs, wrapped in cloth. One was a man and the other a woman, their gazes piercing and flinty, so they gave off a very sharp vibe.

They both wore long black tight-fitting clothes, with long sleeves and trousers. The sleeves reached up to half of their arms, their fingers long and fair, as well-maintained as a pianist’s fingers.

“The current Sect Masters of the Mokso Sword Sect, Masters Sabik and Lorrisa, welcome,” Garen smiled. “Now the representatives of all the top-level fistfighting techniques from all over the world are gathered here. This is the true gathering of international fistfighting!”

“You exaggerate, Mr Garen. We merely represent a small part of the martial arts world, there are still countless legacies hiding everywhere.” Sabik’s expression was serious, he seemed to be a humorless person.

All eight of them filled the banquet table, accompanied by the girls.

Garen had carefully selected these people, they were all the strongest martial arts sects and families in their areas, with the most influence, and each of them represented a huge step in martial arts as they attended this banquet.

This was all due to the operation the Holy Fist Palace joined recently, in exterminating the Wellington Family from the Blood Breed’s secret party. As normal people, they actually faced the Blood Breeds head-on without falling to a disadvantage, and their main forces returned unscathed, while the Wellington Family suffered heavy losses. Although the Dark Colors witches did participate, this was still enough to prove how deep and terrifying the power of the Holy Fist Palace was.

The groups from all over who had treated the invitations they had received with disdain instantly felt a jolt, and they each sent their people to this banquet in response. At the same time, they wanted to see if the Holy Fist Palace truly had the level of power the rumors said.

Of these people, the East Pole Gate Master seemed the most mysterious, he sat in his place, his aura faintly seeming to become one with nature.

Thams, the representative of the Sandt fist was the complete opposite, he had a striking presence all over his body, a strange sensation that made him impossible to ignore.

And the two masters from Mokso remained silent, they did not seem to be the talkative type.

After the few of them chatted for some time, they began to argue, not one side giving way. They all had martial arts knowledge dating over a century, so since they could not come to a consensus, they naturally wanted to try out some moves themselves.

“I heard that Mr Garen from the Holy Fist Palace has the title of Fist Saint(2), known as the strongest fistfighter in America.” The East Gate Master went straight to the point, “I, Du, came here to experience Mr Garen’s famous peak-level fist techniques for myself.” He actually challenged Garen directly.

Garen understood it well in his heart, every person present here had spent years perfecting their art, becoming the strongest opponents. They had practically thrown away all the luxuries in life, dedicating all their time to martial arts. They were not very well known among the sects, but they were truly the strongest of humanity, they had reached terrifying peaks in many areas. They had each surpassed the human limits using their own unique styles and ideals, elevating their skills to heights beyond human imagination.

These people’s bodies were probably already approaching the pinnacle of human genetics.

As soon as those words were spoken, the atmosphere in the banquet fell quiet, evidently this was everyone’s true goal.

Garen clapped his hands, and the girls at the banquet immediately got up and left, closing the door behind them.

He noticed that after Du Xinglong said that, his entire aura changed even more obviously, he seemed to blend in perfectly with the surroundings, his breathing even resonating vaguely with the air in the room, giving off an intense, natural pressure.

“I created three fist techniques, the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist, the Shooting Shadow Secret Technique, and the final White Cloud Secret Technique. Which do you want to experience, Gate Master Du?” He was smiling, but the sound of his words kept assaulting Du Xinglong’s merging, and his body emitted a huge and terrifying qi.

This qi was almost solid, everyone present could feel a huge current brush past their faces like a blade, but when they came back to their senses they realized it was merely an illusion.

This qi was enormous and extremely powerful, pressing down on the whole room, and most of the area around Du Xinglong were all suppressed completely. He was not forced out of his merger, but the natural area he tried to merge into was also completely controlled by Garen, so he could not move at all.

Du Xinglong’s face was slightly red, he felt the space he was in get isolated all of a sudden, his lungs began to lose their breath, a heavy pressure pressing down hard on him.

“As expected of a master-level fighter who has achieved qi-to-mind refination…” He held his fist in salute and lowered his head, with just that simple test, he could already sense his opponent’s bottomless power. Even if he wanted to ask for some sparring, he could no longer say it now.

Just the terrifying oppressive power of his opponent’s aura was enough to make his breath catch and his blood pause. Add that to the lightning on his brow (1) from before, and even if Du Xinglong was reluctant, he still had to lower his head and admit defeat.

Eastern martial arts were divided into three main levels, namely spirit-to-qi refination, qi-to-mind refination, and mind-to-null refination. Even now, he was merely at the peak of spirit-to-qi refination, there was an entire level between him and Garen. Just by standing there, Garen could easily force him down with his body’s vitality, only qi-to-mind refination could truly break the body’s genetic barriers, and constantly strengthen oneself through one’s life.

Garen was exactly like that, in the process of constantly gathering his soul seed, he had actually undergone the spirit-to-qi refination process, the two were very similar in principle.

Beside them, the Sandt Fist, Thams, and his disciple, also had shocked gazes. That enormous power Garen just emitted made them feel as though they were facing a sandstorm in the desert. The suffocating pressure caused even the flow of their powerful Daylight Martial Arts qi to stutter.

The Sandt fist was a bit like the Eastern fist technique, neither could surpass their genetic limits, so instead they cultivated many different attributes of qi, storing them in their bodies to support themselves. That was the true essence of spirit-to-qi refination, this stored-up qi could be emitted to harm enemies, or it could be used to stabilize themselves and activate their potential.

As the peak-level fighter of the desert, although Thams’ qi had achieved a very high level, it was still a certain ways away from the East Pole Sect Master, Du Xinglong. Seeing Du Xinglong submit like that, Thams was shocked beyond words.

“We don’t understand anything about qi-to-mind refination, martial arts were created for real battle, and we won’t know who’s stronger unless we actually cross fists. Therefore, why don’t we all show off our respective levels, whoever’s higher will be the winner, and we won’t need any more wars.” Master Sabik of the Mokso Sword Sect, who had been sitting beside them, stood up slowly. “I am only here for one thing, the word ‘Holy’ in the Holy Fist Palace indicates that it is at the very pinnacle of the field. If the sect holding that position does not have the power to back it up, they would be a shame to our martial arts world.”

He stared at Garen fixedly, taking the long sword covered with black cloth off his back, and quickly unsheathing the sword.

“I, Sabik, officially challenge you, Fist Saint Garen Thomas, on behalf of the Mokso Sword Sect.”

He raised his blade, gripping it in one hand, and his other hand waved as though he was performing a magic trick. Instantly an intricate black handgun appeared in his hand, it was exactly the same color as his clothes, completely inconspicuous, but it gave off an unspeakable sense of extreme threat.

The Mokso Sword Sect was famous for their gun-and-sword technique, a terrifying form of martial arts that merged a hot weapon with cold weapons. It was not based on any qi or spirit at all, relying solely on the edge of a sword and the destructive power of a gun to kill or maim their opponents.

Similarly, this sword sect’s ideals had been greatly promoted throughout all the European countries, giving them a shocking degree of influence.

Garen sat in his seat, watching Sabik quietly. He was just about to speak when suddenly his expression changed slightly, and his gaze wandered to the right, as though seeing something in the far distance through the walls.

This was a female disciple he had put a lot of hopes on, after practicing for so long, she had finally made her move, beginning her first official important mission.

“Fine, I accept your challenge.” He brought his attention back here, looking at Sabik, whose anger was brimming at the seams.

Translator’s note:

拳圣, very similar to his other nickname, Holy Fist (圣拳). A phenomenon where people with great qi flow has that power manifest in a bolt of lightning between their eyes.

Chapter 722: Situation 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

At the foot of the Holy Fist Palace mountain, there was a rather prosperous little white town — Moyo Town.

There were small white buildings all over the town, each house had many colorful fresh flowers. Every time the breeze blew past, there was a waft of sweet floral fragrance everywhere.

The sky was cloudy, and in the middle of the town, beside the river flowing down from the snowy mountain, there was a white three-story house.

“It’s not bad to come for a vacation here, huh?” Arisa ate her homemade ice-cream, her feet propped up on a deckchair. She wore red sunglasses, shorts, and a T-shirt, looking young and pretty.

Beside her, Garen’s little sister, Vivien was lying down, the two girls resting freely under a large sun umbrella.

“We went to all those lengths to trick Mom and Dad over here for a vacation, but we can’t stay long here, either,” Vivien said exasperatedly. “What could it be, why do all of us have to come here?”

“I don’t really know either, but Big Sis and Uncle Pritto should be here soon too. Ask them when they get here.” Arisa sipped some pear juice, smoothing down her hair as she replied.

“Big Sis Isaros is coming? Great, then we can swim together, the river water is really comfy recently.” Vivien had practically partied off her rocker, with Rod from the Rexott group obeying her every desire, there was almost nothing she could not reach. It was only her brother Garen’s side that remained mysterious to her, but she was not one to insist on finding out anyway.

Although Arisa said she did not know, she knew everything.

She was being protected under the Holy Fist Palace. Most of the people living here were families of the Holy Fist Palace’s inner circle members, plus she was in constant contact with her sister Isaro. Nothing was a secret from her there, so naturally she knew everything about the events happening outside.

A war had officially broken out between a large Blood Breed family and the Holy Fist Palace. They had been placed here so that they would stay out of danger, even though they were told to take a two-month vacation, the truth was that they were here to avoid the revenge of the Blood Breeds.

There were powerful fighters patrolling all around the town, as well as all sorts of high-tech security equipment, so it was extremely safe here.

But the situation here was stable for now, instead, she was more worried about her sister’s side.

Her sister and Pritto had gone to investigate whether the secret party’s Scarlet Moon leader was still alive or not, but she did not know how they were progressing right now. Once they found Lord Scarlet Moon, and contacted the number one Death Apostle, Lord Ashen, that would truly be the light party’s best chance.

Arisa knew how hard it would be, and especially after she got to know just how much stronger Blood Breeds were from Pritto, the shadow over her heart just grew darker by the day.

The last time her sister came back to visit her, the scent on her had gotten even deeper, and when they bathed together, Arisa noticed that there were more scars on her sister’s body.

“I wonder when this kind of life will end…” Arisa raised her head to look at the small building next to her, she could vaguely hear Vivien’s parents chatting and laughing inside, while her older brother Jason whined.

“Arisa, Vivien, haven’t you had enough fun? Come on in here to help!”

Trish yelled from inside the house.

“Coming!!”

The two of them hurriedly got off the chairs, and brought their cups into the house.

Trish was wearing an apron, placing dishes onto the table, they were all new dishes that she had just learned to cook.

Emmer was reading magazines at the side with his legs crossed, looking completely carefree.

“I wonder when that punk Garen will come back for a visit, even if he’s gone out to work, he should stop by home once in a while!” Trish complained as she served the food.

“Exactly, he barely even joins us when we go out on vacation as a family,” Vivien agreed hurriedly. “But he rarely even meets us like this, I bet he has something important to handle. After all, he has his own company now.”

“Let him be, as long as he can survive on his own, I can’t be bothered with him.” Trish and Emmer did not know what their son was doing, they just understood that Garen had started his own private company, and was now so busy that they could barely even see him.

“Let’s eat, let’s eat!” Emmer put down his magazine and sat at the table, “Isn’t Garen doing pretty well, forget him!”

******************

Wellington Manor, family headquarters

At night, several dark shadows floated out of the darkness lightly, landing beside the manor. One of the shadows pulled something round of his pocket and pressed it lightly, then seemed to wait for something.

The time ticked by.

There was no movement at all in the manor.

“What’s the matter?” the shadow spoke softly, in perfect French. “We agreed to meet here, what is the Wellington Elder doing?!”

“Could it be broken?” another shadow asked in a low voice.

“No way, I used it once just now,” the first shadow said hesitatingly. “Elder Tu Lan and I made an agreement, and the people from Wellington were always quick to greet us. Even if they were attacked this time and are low on manpower, it makes no sense for there to be no reaction whatsoever.”

“The news I got earlier said that they had all retreated into the underground palace for hiding, and are currently trying to recover. Could there be some special equipment blocking the signal?” The other shadow hazarded a guess.

“Let’s go in and check.”

The few shadows floated lightly into Wellington Manor, it was completely empty and silent inside, giving off an air of abandonment.

“Something’s not right.”

The first shadow seemed to have smelled something.

“Come, let’s go down!”

Several shadows floated soundlessly to a piece of lawn in the middle of the manor, and activated some trigger.

The floor immediately moved aside to reveal a pitch-black underground tunnel, with twinkling lights inside, but it seemed to be similarly deserted.

They looked at each other, and quickly entered the tunnel.

They went through various tunnels, pitch-black ash covering the walls and the floor. There was blood everywhere in some places, in both the underground tunnel and connecting underground palace, but there was nobody to be seen anywhere.

The few of them ran straight for the Elders’ Room as though they knew it well, this was not their first time here at Wellington. Now that they noticed something wrong, they sped up despite themselves.

Bam!!

The tightly-shut stone door was knocked open abruptly, and as the shrapnel rained down, it revealed the dim interior of the Elders’ Room.

In the middle of the room, a large long black robe fell onto the ground, but there was no one else in here. At the same time, there was even a considerable human-shaped hole in the wall.

One of the shadows landed in front of the robes, picking them up for a sniff.

“These are the Wellington Great Elder’s clothes…”

He exchanged glances with the Blood Breed behind him, and both of them read a hint of shock in the other’s eyes.

“Who could destroy the whole Wellington without a trace like that?!”

“It’s the light party…! It must be!” The other one clenched his teeth, “They must still have eyes watching this place, let’s go! Now!”

The others were all shocked, grabbing the robes and retreating rapidly.

But none of them noticed the cracking sound made by a small black stone-like object at one corner of the walls, that was a hidden micro camera.

*******************

Eastern area of America, Wynea State.

14:17 in the afternoon

Heavy downpour

Tu Lan walked on the streets of Benar City with a red umbrella, waiting for the traffic lights with the people who had just gotten out of work. Walking down the pedestrian sidewalk, she would even occasionally glance at the pretty clothes boutiques.

She wore a long pale blue dress and a black silk belt around her waist, her fiery-red waist-long hair straight and smooth, glowing luxuriously.

Her white heeled slippers stepped on the bricks lining the ground, and occasionally she would disturb some puddles.

A few uniformed students had just gotten out of school, wearing raincoats and riding their bikes. When they passed by her on the sidewalk, the boys’ gazes were all gathered onto her, and every one of them was shocked by her beauty.

Boom!

In an instant, Tu Lan’s vision blurred, and everything in front of her turned pitch-black. A huge and long figure, like that of a snake, appeared in front of her slowly.

That was a Serpent Dragon, with the same metallic black copper color!

The Serpent Dragon rose slowly, its joint-like body looking just like a real Eastern dragon. Its huge dragon eyes stared at her slowly, there was a huge door, ancient and dull, behind it.

Her vision blurred again, and Tu Lan returned to her senses, to find herself still standing on the main streets of Benar. The rain pattered onto the umbrella in her hand.

“Is it another illusion?” She touched her right hand, the one that seemed ever so slightly differently-colored from her left eye.

Serpent Dragon, that was the symbol of her achieving the level of Death Apostle. If she could truly break through that Serpent Dragon someday, and enter that door of darkness, that would be the moment she became a Death Apostle.

This was the Black Dragon Tao Technique that she had learned from the East five hundred years ago, when she had gone traveling around the world. She merged it with her family’s holy technique, and after several centuries of perfecting and practicing it, she was approaching the final levels now.

Moving the side of her umbrella away, Tu Lan looked up at the sky from beside the umbrella. The rain came down like silk, floating down endlessly. If one followed the rain silk all the way up to the sky, they would find what seemed to be an endless ocean of clouds.

“Tu Lan Wellington.” Suddenly, someone called her name from behind.

Tu Lan lowered her head, and turned around to look.

It was an Asian girl in a white dress, with porcelain skin, and waist-length pitch-black hair as smooth and lustrous as silk. Her features were delicate and flawless, reminding others of clear jade.

But most strikingly, the girl held a small violin upside-down in her hand, the body of the violin a bloody red.

She held the violin in one hand and the bow in the other. She stood quietly in the flow of the crowd, but strangely, not a single person around her seemed to notice her, treating her as though she did not exist.

“You are?” Tu Lan was very sure that she did not know her, although she had seen many very different types of girls after living for almost a millennia, but not a single one had this type of aura.

“My name is Ninox, I’m here for your life.” The Asian girl held up the violin slowly, and an indescribable, strange scent began to emanate around them.

Before they knew it, in an instant, only the two of them were left standing alone on the streets.

The rain from the sky vanished slowly, and a pale yellow beam of sunlight shone down from the sky, landing on the two of them.

“This is…!?” Tu Lan’s heart gave a jolt. The passersby and cars around her also began to fade slowly, she somehow could not see anyone else at all in this city.

“Fantasy Fist’s Profound…” Ninox said softly, the violin bow sliding across the strings.

Chapter 723: Contact 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen sat on his seat, looking at Master Sabik of the Mokso Sword Sect with a calm expression.

But his heart had already moved to where Cece was, far in the distance. Ninox was someone he had started raising ever since the combat club, she was one of his first students together with Hochman, Dahm and the others. Her talent was the best among them, and he had the highest hopes for her.

Her powers had raised up to terrifying levels as his own power evolved tremendously, but none of that was the most important. The crucial key was that Cece had never faced an opponent as powerful as an upper level Blood Breed on her own before.

Thankfully the previous two elders of the Wellington family were not much, they did not really have any combat awareness at all. They merely had the physical qualities of a powerful fighter, but had none of the power, their combat awareness was lower than even some middle levels, so they were perfect to train her with.

“Do you plan to accept my challenge just sitting there?” Sabik’s expression grew more distorted. His opponent’s pride and arrogance were making his chest heave slightly, unlike the East Pole Gate, his techniques were not meant to raise his attitude as well as his power.

“Be it sitting or standing, they are all the same,” Garen said calmly.

“Arrogant fool!”

Before Sabik even finished speaking, he retreated backward abruptly, the sword and gun in his hands making a sudden sound.

Brr!!

Bang!

The sound of a single gunshot and a flash of silver, blurred the eyes of everyone present.

Garen blocked with one hand in front of him, smiling slightly. There was a mangled bullet caught between his fingers.

Sabik’s expression changed, he had used the sword’s movements to hide the angle he truly intended to attack from, but he did not expect his opponent to predict it anyway.

And he could actually catch a bullet with his bare hands…

Without changing his expression, he pushed the power of his gun up another notch.

“One more time!!”

With a low roar, he transformed into a blur of spinning silver light.

Bam!!! A hint of firelight blinked amidst the silver light.

Everyone around them looked slightly shocked, only the East Pole Gate Master remained unmoved, his expression calm.

Smack!!

Garen’s right hand blocked an area slightly to the left in front of him, his expression unmoved.

“Thank you for allowing me.”

He said calmly, reaching out his hand and opening his palm. It was not just one bullet, but there were three complete black bullets in his hand, as well as a piece of the silver blade tip that had been broken off.

The silver light stopped, and Sabik was as pale as mud, he even stumbled back a few steps, looking at Garen with an expression of shock. Even if he had used harmless rubber bullets, the explosive power and speed of his gun were already the strongest power he could muster to kill his opponents, and yet Garen acted like he was playing with a child, not using any of his true power at all.

“Lord Holy Fist… You truly are powerful, we of the Mokso Sword Sect admire you.” The female master beside him stood up and spoke frankly, but there was still a hint of unhidden shock in her eyes.

Only then did Sabik recover, but he had no idea what to say, pulling back his gun and sword as he retreated to his seat, flushed red.

Garen replied with a polite smile, placing the bullets and sword tip onto the table lightly. The people present all noticed that his palm showed no hint of any scratches despite catching a bullet, and were even more shocked at that.

To these fighters, who were the strongest in the world, such power was already as extreme and terrifying as that of the Blood Breeds.

They were powerful, but humans could naturally be hypnotized and controlled by Blood Breeds, and even the strongest wills would be influenced to some degree, so their powers deteriorated. Everyone seated here had tasted that disadvantage to some extent.

It could be said that the people present here were the very pinnacle of humanity, the strongest in the world. They looked young, but people such as the East Pole Gate Master were already more than seventy years old. Nobody else here was younger than sixty, they had all used their entire lives and all their talent to work hard and persist, before they could achieve such dominating power.

This time they came here especially to meet Garen, mainly because they were shocked that Garen could join the extermination of the Wellington family.

They believed that their individual explosive power was not weaker than that of upper level blood breeds, but with the power of human hypnosis and the Blood Breeds’ terrifying physical capabilities, they were unable to resist the oppression of upper level Blood Breeds.

“Now I believe that Lord Garen truly did join the Wellington raid,” the representative of the Sandt Fist, Thams, said slowly.

The atmosphere in the room was slightly heavy.

“Don’t be formal, we are all members of the same family. How about this, will Lord Garen tell us about the battle when you raided the Wellington family?” the East Pole Gate Master spoke softly.

Garen smiled slightly and clapped, and the pretty girls who had just stepped down came up again, standing behind the guests and serving them wine.

The atmosphere calmed down a little as well.

Only then did he speak slowly.

“All of you have come here to the Holy Fist Palace together this time, so this makes this quite a big event for our fistfighting world. Let us first eat, everyone, and then we can go to the arena to exchange techniques.”

He was actually quite curious as well, masters like those from the Mokso Sword Sect were not as powerful as middle level Blood Breeds, and they relied completely on their guns in battle, so there was not much to see there. On the other hand, he could not quite see through the power of the East Pole Sect Master and the representatives from Sandt.

They seemed to be trying to become one with nature, using the human limits to activate the power of nature, thus indirectly transcending the obstacle that was the inadequacies of the human body.

Garen had always been taking the path of strengthening his own body, so he paid extra attention to these naturalistic techniques that reminded him of the Tao practitioners back home on Earth. This also represented a path completely unlike that of the Warlocks.

*********************

America, Wynea state.

The amber-colored sunlight fell onto Ninox and Tu Lan.

The two of them stood, alone, in the middle of the city. Tall buildings surrounded them, cars frozen, but there was not a single person to be seen.

Tu Lan stared at the Asian girl in front of her.

“That’s a very interesting fist technique, very unique, and very impressive.” She looked around her, and seemed to have noticed the key to this fist technique.

“To be able to such a powerful hypnotic power with a human body, that really does impress me. However…” Although she was in an illusion, she did not seem panicked in the slightest.

“However, I had already overcome such a hypnotic illusion several hundred years ago…”

Psst!

Tu Lan’s figure instantly appeared where Ninox was, one palm stabbing mercilessly into her stomach. But immediately after that, the person in front of her slowly faded and vanished. It was merely an illusion.

Slowly, the soft sounds of a violin playing rose around her, the music was soft and gentle, but had a hint of suppression to it, as though it was going to explode but kept pulling itself back, it made the listener feel upset.

A figure abruptly appeared behind Tu Lan, palms slicing towards her waist like swords, her form soundless.

Bam!

The figure was struck apart by Tu Lan’s palm, turning into countless black shadows before vanishing.

And then another figure pounced down from above, sharp and unrelenting.

Bam!

Tu Lan burst it apart as well

Immediately a third figure appeared, and the violin music surrounding them grew gradually faster.

The fourth, the fifth, the sixth…

As Tu Lan destroyed the shadows one by one, more and more appeared around her, each stronger than the last.

A hint of coldness began to appear in her expression and in her gaze.

Her body spun abruptly, her arm pulling out a short sword that glittered with silver light, and she cut apart three of the figures pouncing at her with a single whoosh.

She had vaguely noticed that the figures all around her were all shaped like that girl Ninox, but these figures were all just pitch-black shadows, they had no true form at all.

Smack!

Suddenly one of the figure’s palms hit her forearm, and in that instant alone, Tu Lan actually felt the blood in her arm jolt harshly, as though there was an energy trying to pull it out of her skin.

“Waterbird Fist?!” She retreated rapidly and abruptly, leaping into the air and landing in another empty spot, but before she could steady her footing, two more figures pounced from behind her.

“Would you quit it already!” Tu Lan’s expression sank, her eyes widening abruptly, and her pupils began to spin slowly, beating like a heart.

“Illusive Counter!!”

Woo…

A strange sound disturbed the violin music all of a sudden.

The scenery around her twisted and spun, like an overturned bucket of dye, making a complete mess of things.

Tu Lan vaguely sensed a powerful wind approaching from ahead, she closed her eyes and opened them again abruptly, and found herself looking at a small city alleyway.

That Asian girl Ninox was rushing at her like a rocket, her body suspended in mid-air, something red beating in her palms as she shot straight for her chest.

Tu Lan raised her hands, her arms seemed to teleport in front of her chest, her palm slicing forward like knives.

Bang bang bang bang bang!!!

A series of palms hitting each other erupted between the two of them, Ninox faced Tu Lan while suspended in the air, the blood around her heart boiling.

Her Fantasy Fist Profound had been broken, and this seriously damaged her own spirit and blood. She had thought this opponent would be easy to beat, just like those few middle level Blood Breeds from before, but to think she was this troublesome. How was this just slightly stronger than the other two elders that Senior Brothers Dahm and Hochman were talking about?!

Boom!!

Ninox’s palm suddenly missed, landing on the wall to the left. She immediately left a large handprint there, and her hand somehow crashed through the entire wall. Thankfully there was no one inside, so she did not cause any commotion.

But immediately after that, her heart gave a jolt, her vision blurring, and she suddenly felt a pain in her right rib.

Pff!

An enormous force slammed into her right ribcage, and Ninox was thrown into the air, shooting backward, moaning once in pain.

Tu Lan had no intention of pursuing her, and instead leaped in the opposite direction, easily jumping across the alley walls. Within a few leaps, she had disappeared down the entrance into another alley.

Only then did Ninox fall hard onto the ground, spitting out a mouthful of blood.

After she stood up with some difficulty, Tu Lan was already nowhere to be seen.

“So powerful…”

She looked at the direction Tu Lan had vanished in and murmured softly. At the same time several men and women in tight black clothing also rushed out of the alley behind her, they all had the words ‘Holy Fist Technique’ sewed onto the right side of their chests.

“Is this the power of true upper level Blood Breeds?” Cece knew that her two senior brothers had probably met regular upper level Blood Breeds with no combat awareness, that Great Elder had even been obliterated by a middle level Blood Breed using witch poison. But this one, the only female elder among the three Wellington Great Elders, was surprisingly the only one who was truly powerful.

Seeing that her subordinates were still going to give chase, Ninox waved her hand to stop them.

“Don’t chase them! Retreat!”

She allowed them to help her up calmly, giving the direction Tu Lan had left in a long look.

The opponent was much stronger than her, only such an upper level Blood Breed could demonstrate how strong Blood Breeds were meant to be.

Looks like even if they had been rotting for a thousand years, these Blood Breeds still had some hardy roots.

She did not know why Tu Lan did not kill her, Tu Lan was evidently one level, or even several levels higher than her in power, so if she gave chase now, she would just be running to her death.

“But Captain, our mission…” One of her female subordinates still tried to protest.

“We are no match for her.” Ninox interrupted her, “The opponent has no intention of spilling blood, she probably has some other motive. Now is not the time to engage her in combat.” Ninox had always been a decisive person, just like how she dared to stand up against Garen’s pressure way back then in the combat club. She did not lack courage, but continuing on now would only anger the opponent, resulting in their meaningless deaths.

“Cece, you’re fine, right?” Amidst the rushed sound of footsteps, Quentin rushed up to her, all dressed in black. She held Ninox up, her expression somewhat worried. “I can’t believe it, is this Tu Lan really so strong, so much so that even your successful Fantasy Fist could not take her down?”

“It’d be very hard…” Ninox shook her head, “The opponent’s Illusory Counter is too powerful, it’s practically a hundred times that of a normal middle level Blood Breed, my illusion was destroyed in one go. And that’s because she was being cautious from the start, so she did not show her explosive power at the very first opportunity.”

“Your injuries are really serious, we need to return to the palace now!” Quentin checked her injuries, and instantly frowned.

Chapter 724: Contact 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Cece was gravely injured, and the opponent got away?” Garen sat in the highest seat of the practice hall, watching the disciples spar together with the other important delegates. When he received Quentin’s call, he frowned slightly.

“The opponent is very powerful! She cannot be compared to the other two elders, Cece’s Fantasy Fist Profound was broken, and she was injured in the right rib, after checking I found that there’s some internal bleeding from the shock. Thank goodness I saved her in time.”

“Tu Lan, was it? The other people from Wellington were dealt with?” Garen asked softly.

“All dealt with, only the Elder Tu Lan is left,” Quentin replied.

“Get Cece to come back and meet me,” Garen said calmly.

“Yes.”

Putting down the phone, even Garen was slightly surprised. Looks like he had been careless, this last Wellington Elder was actually a true upper level Blood Breed with real power, he had intended for her to be Cece’s trial run.

Seems like everything had all gone too smoothly, so he had begun to neglect some details.

When he returned to his senses, the people from the three main fist techniques around him were still chatting away happily, along with Hochman and some other representatives from his disciples.

After Garen faced Master Sabik of the Mokso Sword Sect just now, the few main sects all understood that Garen’s true power was far stronger than they imagined, so they no longer dared to test him head-on. Instead, they were trying to elicit information from Garen’s disciples about his level of strength.

According to the East Pole Gate’s estimates, Garen’s power should be equal to a Grand Master. He was only one step away from mind-to-null refination, and the level of legends. Right now in the East, there were no longer any masters at the qi-to-spirit level, only the masters of history could achieve that step.

But they never could have imagined that Garen’s true strength lay in his terrifyingly powerful body, and not in his mind. He could instantly apply up to a thousand tons of force, that was a level far beyond his understanding. And let’s not mention the power he had upon activating the Seven Star Life’s Secret Point.

Right now, two of the figures on the arena were leaping and jumping, intersecting with each other non-stop, each time they made contact, there would be a dull explosive sound.

It was one of the masters of the Waterbird Fist under Hochman sparring with one of Thams’ Sandt Fist disciples.

Strangely, the Sandt Fist gave off an impression of extreme softness, but while it was soft, it could instantaneously burst out with a force like a spring. It was just enough to fight against Hochman’s man, they were relatively well-matched.

The people sitting at the top did also seem to treat Garen as their leader, his impressive blood qi had unconsciously covered the entire arena. Especially now that he had mixed it with the Holy Phoenix Scriptures, his dominating aura had gotten even stronger.

That almighty aura also leaked out slightly, forcing uneasiness into the hearts of the representatives from the three main sects.

Only the East Pole Gate Master, Du Xinglong, was slightly more relaxed. But that also meant he was even more aware that the power of the Holy Fist Palace was indeed far stronger than he ever imagined.

“I hear that Palace Master Garen is looking for clues about the Sleepless Faces everywhere.” While everyone else was focused on the sparring going down below, Du Xinglong spoke slowly. “It just so happens that I have some information about a mask that had wandered off to the East.”

“Oh? What do you mean by that, Gate Master Du?” Garen brought his attention away as he said calmly.

“We have already sent our men out to gather the masks. We of the East Pole Gate are also rather in awe of the Holy Fist Palace’s martial arts level, so I would like to send my young grandson here for a long-term martial arts exchange program.”

“That would be fine, of course.” Garen nodded. He wore a mask, but although no one could see his actual expression, they could tell from his tone that he had no intention of rejecting them.

Du Xinglong knew very well that a chance like this, to allow his young grandson to be this close to a qi-to-mind level Grand Master, would be unthinkable of in the East. If he did not make full use of this chance, by the time more people approached Garen, he might not be able to benefit as much anymore. Once there were more people, naturally the Holy Fist Palace would place less emphasis on them.

He understood what the Holy Fist Palace had planned, they wanted to reach a true position in the international martial arts scene, and become the true holy land for all martial arts sects.

Since they had a Grand Master standing guard over the Holy Fist Palace, that title was naturally theirs for the taking.

“I just happened to have the same intention.” Beside them, Thams smiled as he said, “And my allied sects will surely have the same plan. When the time comes, I hope Palace Master Garen will help out our youngsters in their training.”

“Of course, of course.” Garen nodded with a smile.

For a moment there, the host and the guests were all perfectly happy, the main martial arts sects had also found a glimmer of hope in their battle against the Blood Breeds through Garen. But the truly powerful Blood Breeds were not the regular Blood Breeds, but the Death Apostles at the very top. They were the ones with power comparable to a nuclear weapon, and it all depended on whether or not the Holy Fist Palace could defend against the Death Apostles’ revenge,

The Wellington family was not that easy to provoke, the Death Apostle Wellington would surely not let this slide, so it all depended on what happened after this.

After some more exchanges, Garen also understood that Thams had always been close to the higher-ups of the Rexott group, his arrival here this time obviously represented the Rexott Group’s attitude to some extent.

Manpower, financial power, and martial power, he had them all. The only thing he needed now was a chance to show off the true power of the Holy Fist Palace.

***************

Standing in front of Cece’s sickbed, Garen was dressed all in white, wearing a mask as he checked Cece’s condition.

He reached out his hand and touched Cece’s injured right ribs a few times, then he pulled his hand back slowly. Next, he opened Cece’s eyelids, checking her pupils.

The others, Quentin and Xander, all stood at the side respectfully.

There were only a few members of the Holy Fist Palace’s higher-ups present in this room.

“Teacher, how is Cece’s condition?” Quentin asked, slightly worried.

“The destruction of the Fantasy Fist Profound damaged her spirit and cranial nerves, she needs some rest. To normal people, cranial nerves cannot be regenerated, but to us, it’s possible. It just requires a longer time. Add that to the internal bleeding and shock caused by her injuries, and she will need at least two months to recover.”

Garen replied as he pulled back his hand.

“Thank you, Teacher.” Ninox hid under the covers, her face slightly red. The place on her right ribs where she was hurt was near her chest, even if it was her teacher touching her like that, she was still embarrassed to no end.

“Is this Tu Lan really that powerful?” Xander was rather incredulous, “The other two Elders could be defeated by even a slightly stronger middle level Blood Breed, why is this one Elder so ridiculously powerful?”

“That is my mistake.” The door was pushed open, and Dahm strode in, wearing a bright red cape.

“Greetings, Teacher.” He first lowered his head in a bow to Garen, and then he began to explain the reason. “I learned about Tu Lan from one of the Blood Breeds under my control. Although as Elders, they don’t usually fight, but some of the older middle level Blood Breeds were aware of some things. Tu Lan used to be the strongest general in the Wellington family other than their chief, Wellington. Even among the upper level Blood Breeds, she was one of the very best.”

His androgynous voice revealed a hint of rare solemnity.

“If you want to kill Tu Lan, either Hochman and I have to personally fight her, or Teacher…” He did not continue, but his intention was very clear. Unless Garen fought her personally, they would not be able to ensure that it would go one without a hitch.

“How are things with the Blood Breeds’ secret party?”

Garen did not continue that topic, and switched to another one instead.

“The secret party has the main advantage now, most of the light party’s power had been suppressed and taken apart. As for the attack on Wellington, it looks like there’s no reaction for now, but it’s most likely gathering momentum for a bigger impact. We need to be constantly prepared for a counterattack by the Death Apostle Wellington at any time,” Dahm replied seriously.

“No news about the Death Apostles Scarlet Moon and Ashen?”

“A little, they say that Ashen has gone missing, this is also the main reason the light party is completely falling apart. Right now, even the power of the Lion Mother cannot suppress the flames of the secret party,” Dahm replied quickly.

Garen fell silent.

For some reason, he suddenly remembered the sisters, Isaros and Arisa, as well as that strange Scarlet Moon Blood Breed. Inexplicably, he felt as though Isaros and the others may know a bit about Ashen’s disappearance.

The last time he secretly visited his parents, he had seen Arisa’s condition, that little girl’s air of worldliness had gotten stronger. That feeling of being part of the world’s path had grown stronger and stronger.

Isaros and her sister was evidently the core trigger to these events, he had to be constantly aware of any developments on their part as he gathered the masks.

Touching his right eyes lightly with his hand, that one completely blind eye kept reminding him of the approaching danger from the Void Nine-Headed Dragon King.

He needed to pick up the pace…

********************

Secret party Blood Union

In a wide open white hall, in some mysterious ruins.

There were countless crystal chandeliers hanging from the ceiling, like so many small red suns, emitting a bright and gentle red light.

Underneath them were three giant silver balls floating in mid-air.

Each ball was more than ten meters in diameter, huge and round, filled with an unnamed amber fluid that bubbled occasionally.

Strangely, there was a well-proportioned white-skinned human figure suspended in each ball of liquid.

There were three bodies in the three balls, two male and one female. Each of them wore different but equally elaborate long robes, even the men wore long black dress-like robes with golden hems.

“Wellington, your old base was destroyed by those witches, but you don’t seem too bothered at all.” One of the blonde men in black robes opened his eyes, looking at another handsome man with otherworldly features.

“There’s too much trash in there, so I borrowed some outside power to clean it out. My family has been rotten for too long.” Wellington had short purple-red hair and a cold expression, as though he did not care about his clan’s survival at all, “After all, it’d only take me a few years to start another family again anyway.”

“Ashen has been critically wounded, without the help of the Lion Mother, he cannot hide for long. Scarlet Moon, on the other hand, that guy’s always been missing.” The blonde man was thoughtful.

“Wellington, I think you should still go back for a visit, that kid Tu Lan should be close to a breakthrough, don’t let her be interrupted just like that. There are only so few of us in this world, it’s been so long since we had a new face around here, it’s too boring…”

The woman in the last sphere had completely white eyes and no pupils, her long green hair reaching her waist.

“Oh?” Wellington looked slightly surprised, and after thinking for some time, he spoke softly.

“Then I’ll go out for a bit. But are you sure it’s okay for just the two of you to suppress Ashen’s Blood Nucleus?”

“Then why don’t you just get it settled sooner?” the woman laughed softly.

“True.” Wellington nodded, and turned around slowly, swimming backward lightly. Soon enough, he began to gradually disappear into the sphere.

Chapter 725: Hunt 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Portugal, Vesnan City

Near the seaport, there was a smattering of pale yellow boats floating on the sea. Some of them were small fishing vessels, but there were also mid-sized rafts.

Under the twilight rays, the red light dyed the surface of the sea by the port a bright red.

There was a constant flow of carriages by the seaside, two locals were taking their child on a walk in a stroller. On the flat concrete floor beside the port, there were several young men and women dressed in coats, one of the women had pretty features, but she looked rather cold. Surprisingly, there was a gruesome scar on the right side of her neck, it extended from her neck to the middle of her chest, and then it was blocked off by her clothes so no one could tell just how long it was.

The woman had shoulder-length hair that was naturally red, and not dyed.

There was also a middle-aged man standing with her, as well as a young girl.

“Why did you call me out so late? I’m in a rush to get back for dinner,” the red-haired woman said calmly.

“Isaros, it’s been over half a year since I got you sisters involved in this mess, hasn’t it?” the middle-aged man said in a low voice, his expression guilty. “If I hadn’t met you guys back then, perhaps you would still be living peacefully in that little town.”

“What’s the point of saying that now?” Isaros said calmly. “Whatever you have to say, just spit it.”

The man looked even guiltier, hesitating for a while. Instead, it was the other girl beside them who could not take it anymore.

“Let me be the one to say it,” the girl stepped up and spoke. She looked no older than seventeen or eighteen, but the aura in her eyes was as deep as that of an old woman.

“As we are all Scarlet Moon Blood Breeds, we hope that we can contact the human organization, the Holy Fist Palace, through you, and thus contribute to our light party.” The girl spoke with no restraint whatsoever, as though this was only natural.

“Contact the Holy Fist Palace?” Isaros frowned slightly.

“Yes, your sister is protected by the Holy Fist Palace, so you should be pretty close to them. If you can contact them to join our forces, as a Scarlet Moon Blood Breed, I can make an exception and obtain another Blood Breed position for you.” The girl spoke as though a Blood Breed position was such a glorious thing.

Isaros frowned. Ignoring the girl, she looked straight at the middle-aged man.

“Pritto, is this your intention?”

Pritto smiled bitterly, it had been several weeks since they escaped the secret party in America and ran here to Portugal, and now they had officially joined an organization allied with the light party. This organization was centered around two light party upper level Blood Breeds, and secretly resisted the secret party in hiding.

“We are too weak right now, so we do need your help to contact them, then we’ll go to America together.”

“Contacting them is no problem, but I cannot guarantee that they will give you face and agree to cooperate.”

“No problem, we’ll take over negotiations after that,” the Blood Breed girl said confidently.

*********************

On a snowy mountain peak

Holy Fist Palace

The snow danced in the air, covering the entire building of the Holy Fist Palace with a thick layer of white.

Garen sat in a room on the rightmost edge, nearest to the cliff. Sitting at his desk, he raised his pen and began to write something slowly in a black notebook.

The room was lavishly decorated, covered in all white and gold. There was a fire burning away merrily in the fireplace, emitting a faint warmth, raising the temperature of the entire room.

Sofa, bookshelves, single bed, and a super-thin television hanging on the wall.

The floor was smooth white marble, strangely clean.

Garen sat in front of a desk, it was the one he had brought over from Berlin, unchanged in the slightest.

The black notebook underneath his hand was giving off a strange and blurry feeling. If someone wanted to see the outer appearance and the inner content of that notebook more carefully, they would end up feeling slightly dizzy. But once they moved their gaze away, they would still be naturally attracted to it, it just pulled others’ spirits into looking at it.

The scrawling sound of pen on paper echoed through the room.

Garen wore a mask over his eyes, and his only functioning eye, the left one, was actually shining with a hint of gold.

After goodness knows how long, he put down his pen slowly, closed his eyes and rested for a while. Only then did he close that strange notebook.

“I’ve already recorded down the true essence of the Holy Phoenix Scriptures, but it’s still missing something,” he said softly, as though to himself.

‘You’re still lacking some deeper understandings, if you could understand the Holy Phoenix Scriptures at a deeper level, perhaps you could speed up the completion of your Demonic Book,” Black Sethe suggested.

Garen nodded slightly.

The Holy Phoenix Scriptures were divided into three levels and nine different states. But if one intended to really delve deep into this cultivation method, they would first need to investigate the compatibility problem he was facing with the Hellfrost Peacock Technique he was currently practicing.

Up until now, Garen was still in the midst of finding his own path. The Peacock Technique could achieve Army Level, but it was still lacking in practice supplies and resources. He did not know how far he could take the Holy Phoenix Scriptures either, and he could even tell that this was a path doomed for destruction, yet it helped with his gathering of the Soul Seed.

‘This is a matter of your own priorities,’ Black Sethe said softly. ‘The Soul Seed strengthens your soul, and there is a high chance that you’ll encounter a dead end with the Holy Phoenix Scriptures when you need something you don’t have. The other way, with the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, you still won’t be able to level up without the required resources. It might be better for you to just practice the Holy Phoenix Scriptures first. Leave thinking about it until the incompatibility happens, right now your main job is to increase the strength of your Soul Seed. That’s where your foundations lie.’

“True.” Garen nodded, and was no longer hesitant.

The Demonic Book was more or less complete. He had recorded all of his techniques in there, including the Holy Phoenix Scriptures that he had just learned. He should have fully completed his second Soul Seed by now, but because he did not have a deep enough understanding of the Holy Phoenix Scriptures, he was still lacking that last push.

He glanced at his current condition and attributes.

Garen Thomas.

Strength 7. Agility 7. Vitality 10. Intelligence 11. Potential power 7966%. Soul limit 30.

Soul Seed: Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique

‘Void Pursuer: inheritor of the Ancient Endor civilization, arch enemies with the Void races. Has the natural ability to heal and strengthen oneself by hunting the Void Creatures’ Cores. That is a natural power bestowed eternally by the mysterious power of Ancient Endor.’

‘Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Grade one elementary level (Total of five grades, with three grades of derivative grades, a total of eight grades) Every time the practitioner reaches the next level, their blood and veins will be purified, and they will slowly approach the Hellfrost Peacock body type, finally becoming the ultimate form, the Hellfrost Peacock King, with Army Level being the limit.’

‘Seven Star Life’s Secret Point: fifth grade (maximum of seven grades).’

‘Violin Skill: Grade 2, Proficient Grade (Total of three grades).’

‘Slaughtering Hand: first grade.’

Looking away again, Garen was slightly disappointed that he had only accumulated so few attribute points after obtaining five masks.

Thankfully, after the martial arts exchange event, the students that Hochman and Dahm recently taught, such as Caesar and the others, were all leaving the Holy Fist Palace to find Garen new masks. Of these groups, Dahm was heading to Memphis Forest, the sixth mask at the moon river. It had been several days since he departed, and Garen did not know how the situation was going.

Standing up from his desk, Garen looked at the snowflakes floating down in front of his window, and suddenly felt inexplicably lost.

Ever since he reincarnated this time, he had still been chasing after power, and he had even gotten himself involved with the huge history of war between the Void Creatures and the Ancient Endor civilization. With the threat of Nadia constantly approaching, he had no choice but to continue pressing forward.

But the resources in this world were far too lacking, they were not nearly enough to fulfill the requirements of a peak-level secret technique. That was why he had no choice but to stop, and use his own invented technique to gather his second Soul Seed.

If he could truly practice the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, the speed of his forming his Soul Seed would surely be exponentially faster, and he might even activate some legacies that continue from there. He would not be so at a loss about the true soul levels after that.

Black Sethe helped him a lot with that as well, every Living and Dead Secret Technique was an extremely complex system containing part of the truth of the universe. These were not things to be created just like that.

It seemed as though there were thousands of these peak-level secret techniques, and any one of them could lead to an extremely high level. But all of them began with caution and wariness, these steps that looked complicated or simple, each of them could lead to extremely serious results if they were changed even a little. Grievous injuries, paralysis, disabilities or even death, all were possible.

Every step in these secret techniques had to undergo thousands of trials and countless agonizing lessons learned, before they could truly become a path to take.

And the supplies or resources needed were also compulsory.

Compared to the situation back there where the resources were plenty, Garen’s current situation was like eating white rice without even oil to cover it, and trying to build muscle from there.

It was the same with peak-level secret techniques, if you wanted to be extraordinary, you would naturally need better resources. And this world had none of those.

Looking for the training materials for the Hellfrost Peacock Technique was like looking for dry sand in the ocean.

‘How do you plan to handle the matter with Tu Lan?’ Black Sethe asked quietly.

Tu Lan Wellington had escaped after injuring Cece, and was now rapidly approaching the other family’s territories. If she was not dealt with quickly, and managed to escape into the other family territories, she could incite another war on an even larger scale.

After destroying the Wellington family, the whole northern America had become part of the Holy Fist Palace’s territory. This included the few smaller countries that AG and the Dark Colors witches would cover. This was all allied territory.

And now the Blood Breeds were still busy raiding the light party. After the battle last time, the other families knew that normal power was nowhere near enough to take down the Lightless Alliance, so they had no choice but to call a time-out. They probably planned to stabilize their internal ranks, and then gather up a force to dismantle their opponents.

“We’ve already gathered sufficient information about Tu Lan, she should have returned to the state of Mintosa, that’s one of the secret party’s Blood Alliance bases, I’ll make a trip there myself,” Garen said calmly.

Cece was grievously hurt, there was no way he could let that slide. And those people from the Bailey Group got mixed up with the Primary Colors, so it was time he dealt with them.

Chapter 726: Hunt 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

California, America

After a week…

As she looked at the huge red and white structure of the theatre, Isaros rearranged her hat and walked into the theatre with the crowd.

The theatre was playing the Spanish musical Wild Cats, and the female lead was singing beautifully in a clear voice.

Beyond the stage was a half-full seating area, from which applause could be heard once every now and then.

Isaros looked for a seat at a higher elevation while the buzz of the audiences’ chatter surrounded her. She was constantly checking on her hat as it was an aura covering hat that’s been enchanted with witchcraft, and it could alter her aura for short periods of time in order to distort the Blood Breeds’ sensing abilities.

This was one of the assets belonging to the Holy Fist Palace’s Combat Association, and this was one of the fastest channels to contact the Combat Association.

The seats above Isaros was empty. She waited for a while, looking as though she was paying attention and was enjoying the musical, but she was actually staying wary of her surroundings. In case Combat Association had any replies, the seats would definitely be occupied.

Half an hour had gone by unnoticeably, when two silhouettes finally emerged silently from Isaros’ right side and were walking towards the two empty seats above Isaros as they traversed the crowd.

The duo sat in two seats above her.

Isaros suddenly smelled a familiar body fragrance enveloping her.

“Sister,” the person beside her finally spoke.

Isaros turned around, her pupils dilated.

“Arisa?! Vivien!?”

The people sitting beside her were actually these beautiful sisters of hers, Arisa and Vivien.

“Why are you here?” Isaros’ head suddenly looked stern.

Once we heard news of sister, we proactively asked to come, since we haven’t met you for a long time,” Risa immediately explained as she observed her sister’s concerned look. ” Relax, we came out under very secretive planning. Nobody would have known.”

Now that Secret Party is pursuing me closely, it’s too dangerous to be around me!” Isaros said with a stern tone. “You’re too rash, Arisa, you even brought Vivien over! What if something dangerous happened?”

“Relax, we have experts protecting us,” Vivien raised her fist and shook it around. “Sister Quentin brought a few men over on a trip anyway, so we have followed along.”

“Quentin? One of the four warlords of the Combat Association?” Isaros also knew of the situation during the ambush on Wellington, which was directed against the Holy Fist Palace. There were two names that had begun circulating in the underground society; the Two Generals and the Four Warlords, The Two Generals were obviously referring to Hochman and Dahm, who possessed terrifying abilities comparable to high-level Blood Breeds, which could shake any Blood Breeds or Witches. Whereas the Four Warlords referred to the four people who were always managing the external affairs of the Holy Fist Palace.

These four people were Xander, Cece, Quentin and the Vice President of the Nighthawks, Baldy. They managed most of the daily affairs and public relations, as well as directing large amounts of personnel, whether it was Combat Association’s extensive network within and beyond America, or the world-class web of relationships developed by their second batch students, or even the training and employment of Nighthawks, the purely violent organization of mercenaries.

“That’s good if Quentin was here,” Isaros sighed in relief, after knowing that Holy Fist Palace didn’t simply let these kids out without any protective measures in place. “I am here on some official business so bring me to Miss Quentin, I have some matters to discuss with her. Also, Pritto and other Light Party representatives are waiting for me outside.”

Seeing that there were indeed some official matters, Arisa had also become serious.

“Sister Quentin is in that seat over there discussing business with someone else, let me bring you there.”

“Okay,” to be honest, Isaros felt helpless too; now she was too deeply intertwined in the Scarlet Moon Clan of the Light Party. Not only had she killed off countless vampires of the Secret Party, she’d even killed off a few Low-Level Blood Breeds up to this point. More importantly, Pritto’s Scarlet Moon Holy Technique was indeed deep within her consciousness, planted by the Death Apostle of the Scarlet Moon Clan. She would be unable to remove it unless another Death Apostle extracted it.

This has caused her to climb even higher on the Secret Party’s hit list.

As she stood up with Arisa and Vivien, Isaros walked out of a door on her left, through a dark corridor covered in black carpets, into some sparsely distanced mid-air suites hanging from the second floor. In front of a door was a muscular woman in a black shirt who was playing with a silver knife in her hand. As that lady laid eyes upon Arisa and company, she immediately stood aside to allow entrance without uttering a word.

Arisa smiled at the lady politely and then knocked on the door.

“Sister Quentin.”

“Oh, Arisa, Come on in,” a clear woman’s voice could be heard from within, as she spoke was a clean, neat American accent.

The door was opened slowly from the inside. The trio walked into the suite, which already had a beautiful lady wearing a red silk cheongsam inside. Even though she was wearing such a seductive cheongsam, the lady maintained a strong, elegant vibe; and that was Quentin of the Holy Fist Palace.

Quentin’s brows were drawn diagonally together and were straight as a pen. Her eyes were very spirited and a sharp nose coupled with her lovely fair skin; her elegant look was completed with a glass of wine in her hand and crossed, long slender legs.

The man sitting opposite her was a balding, middle-aged man who looked terrified and as though he was showing respect towards her. Although he was obviously older than Quentin, the power hierarchy gave a misconception that she was the more senior than him.

At this instance, the man was breaking out in cold sweat and had lowered his head in fear of looking Quentin in the eyes, which made people wonder what had happened just now.

“Alright, since Miss Quentin have some company at the moment, I shall take my leave.”

“Please,” Quentin waved her hand, “remember that you must give us the stock in time, as promised.”

“Of course milady, of course,” the middle-aged man stood up and bowed repeatedly. “Thank you very much, Miss Quentin, I hope our cooperation runs smooth.”

“Likewise.”

The man then left the room hurriedly, and one could even faintly hear his relaxed sigh at the instant the door was closed.

Quentin then moved her eyes to the trio, and her gaze landed upon Isaros who was standing behind.

“I believe this is the Arisa’s sister, Isaros?” she stood up, indicating to the server to pour them some drinks.

Isaros had felt a strong aura suppression upon entering the suite, which was a natural sensing ability of hers, acquired from the long period of combat with and killing of Blood Breeds and vampires. She realized that when she was against some stronger foes, the opponents’ aura would naturally produce a form of suppression.

It was the same as Quentin who was right in front of her; the aura within her was so strong that it was beyond comprehension for humans.

“As expected of an expert of the Holy Fist Palace,” she nodded as she admitted her identity.

Quentin smiled and took a sip off the wine in her glass.

“Even though I really couldn’t wait to greet you, it wouldn’t have looked courteous if I didn’t take care of a few guests who’d come from faraway towns.”

She looked at the suite’s left side of the door with some deep thoughts, as though she saw through the wall there into some scenery beyond the walls.

Bam!!

A group of shadows suddenly barged in and rushed straight towards Quentin like black arrows. Despite the speed of their attack, they didn’t produce a single noise.

“Ambush!” Isaros’ focus shuddered and she grabbed both Arisa and Vivien’s collars with each hand, lifting them up with ease to avoid the collision with the shadows.

What followed were more shadows rushing into the building, targeting the trio while ignoring the waitresses’ screams.

At this point, Quentin had already single-handedly taken down the shadow who’d first engaged her by tapping onto its head. The shadow broke down and turned into ash, obvious signs that identified a vampire.

With a turn on her head, the slender legs beneath her cheongsam had launched a series of kicks towards the shadows outside, with a speed that seemed to be slightly above those shadows.

As Garen’s ability had increased, her strength had also taken a giant leap forward, which made handling these vampires and Low-Level Blood Breeds a breeze.

“Since you’re here, why don’t you stay!”

Just as she ended her sentence, both of Quentin’s legs had hit every single shadow within a flicker of an eye.

Bambambam!!

With a few consecutive bursts, the shadows were sent flying and exploded into ashes.

But in this instance, one of the shadows did not have any reaction. It advanced instead of being blown back, took a sharp turn and produced a burst of speed, rushing into Quentin’s proximity.

With a crackling sound, the smile on Quentin’s face turned stern.

“You are??!!” she had not even completed her sentence before she was sent flying backward, crashing onto tables and chairs in the suite, only stopping when she hit the bulletproof glass wall. There was a trickle of blood flowing from her abdomen, and it was seen dripping on the black shadow’s hand as well.

“You…!!” Quentin displayed an unbelieving look as she glared at the black shadow. She could barely protect her vitals in the heat of the moment, but she still couldn’t avoid being heavily injured.

To the surprise of Arisa and Vivien, the black shadow pulled the hood off its head, and bright red hair was flaunted. It was actually a seductive-looking, beautiful lady.

“To be able to catch so many small fries, all the prep work I did was well worth it,” Tu Lan had a satisfied smirk on her face.

By faking that she was headed for other states and lure away the pursuer of the Holy Fist Palace, she had actually collaborated with people from the Secret Party to wait for a time to retaliate. Now that she had done it, she’d managed to catch these small fries and important people, on top of the successful retaliation.

“Such hard work, how can I go back empty-handed?” Tu Lan smiled. She suddenly moved her wrist and blocked Quentin’s knee that had been abruptly launched towards her, before Tu Lan took a few steps back and stood in the middle of the suite.

“Indeed… it’s rare that you come out, how can let me go back empty-handed?” a calm male’s voice was suddenly heard from the doorstep behind her.

Tu Lan’s smiling face turned ice cold in that instant. She slowly turned around to see a handsome young man, who had not been there previously, standing by the door. That man was as perfectly radiant as Apollo himself, but one of his eyes was not radiant; it held nothing but a cold gaze.

“Garen…!”

Bam!

Tu Lan rammed the right side of the wall immediately, and chose to flee in that instant!

Chapter 727: Hunt 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Fantasy!”

Unexpectedly, Garen did not give chase but simply flung out his right arm to catch Tu Lan from afar.

Weirdly, his right palm slowly became bigger and wider, and an odd feeling that the sky was being engulfed shivered through the crowd.

As the surrounding environment was distorted, the entire hallway felt like a twisted glass tube that was churning and shaking violently.

Tu Lan was stunned by the sudden loss of balance but only for an instant, and she resumed fleeing at a speed that looked to be unaffected by gravity, rushing straight for the nearest theatre exit.

Bam!!

A large hole suddenly opened at Garen’s position, and one could directly see the space within it.

His entire body tilted slightly before he disappeared in the blink of an eye. He was definitely hot on her heels.

What was left was Quentin, Isaros, and co, who had only reacted only moments after the two had disappeared and dense footsteps could be faintly heard from the outside.

“Let’s leave immediately!” Quentin could barely stand upright, with one hand pressing onto her abdomen. A sizeable wound should have broken open there as blood kept oozing from it, but it wasn’t as terrible as before; she compressed the blood vessels with muscle contraction, preventing more blood from oozing out.

Arisa and Vivien had just recovered from the shock. Both of them wanted to help Quentin but were gently pushed away.

“Let me do it!” Isaros carried Quentin with a stern expression and fled while leading the two other girls.

“With Teacher here, that person would never return, but I’m afraid this is a trap. Go to the parking lot and immediately inform the allies outside and have them leave first, we will be in contact soon,” even though Quentin had suffered heavy injuries, she was still conscious enough to plan ahead.

“I know. Your injury looks bad,” Isaros looked at the wound the size of a fist and her eyes couldn’t stop twitching. While Quentin was speaking with relative ease, if it had been anyone else, this injury would be enough to cause a blackout or death by shock.

Soon, a group of people in black uniforms ran into the suite in a trained manner, and carried the heavily injured Quentin and escorted them up to a vehicle that was specially prepared for them.

“Brother… was that…. Brother?” Vivien asked after boarding the car, as she felt a strong sense of disbelief when recalling the golden silhouette. “Was he actually this strong? For that man to run without even attempting to combat.”

“That’s just the first time you’ve seen Teacher in action…” Quentin’s face was pale, but she seemed to reply with a relatively easy smile. “With Teacher here, that person won’t be able to flee. It’s obvious that Teacher took a trip here just to pursue her.”

As she spoke to the end, her expression seemed to turn cold.

******************

“Black Dragon!!”

In the rural forests, two silhouettes of black and gold were toe-to-toe in their chase.

As the black colored silhouette roared in front, her speed increased explosively and a thin layer of black smoke seemed to dissipate from her entire body, looking like a long tail. Her speed, however, was leagues above her previous speed.

Under the blazing sun, the golden silhouette behind didn’t seem to be alarmed; he created crater after crater on the ground under his feet with help from a terrifying explosive power to continue his pursuit.

Suddenly, a large tree trunk beside him exploded and the blazing flames halted his momentum, creating a great distance between the two silhouettes.

“Oh? That’s a lot of nifty toys she’s got there.”

In the high-speed movement, Garen squinted as he observed the fleeing silhouette. That explosion just now wasn’t anything special; it was just a simple technological tactic, but such a pressurized explosive bomb would still somewhat affect him in his usual condition.

Bam!! Bam Bam Bam!!!

Suddenly, a series of thunderous explosions coupled with an orangy-yellow flame formed a vortex around him, the tremendous impact and heat completely engulfing him.

Taking advantage of the instance Garen was stopped, Tu Lan took a few larger leaps forward and hid within the dense forest on her right. A thick white smoke began propagating behind her out of nowhere, which seemed like an obvious escape plan.

She actually had zero plans to return to engage in combat.

The flame vortex engulfed the woods in the radius of tens of meters, and under the intense combustion, the smoke rose thickly into the sky and was observable from afar.

From amidst the flames, Garen walked out without any damage. Oddly enough, whether it was the flame or the smoke, they automatically dispersed from him within a ten-odd centimeters radius, as though there was an invisible protective barrier around him.

As he walked out of the areas affected by the flames, Garen waved his hand to disperse the smoke. He raised his head to find out that Tu Lan was nowhere to be found, even though he could still sense the remnants of her aura nearby.

With Garen’s arsenal of Secret Techniques, peerless physique, and extra-sensitive sensory abilities, he could easily locate traces Tu Lan’s scent within the forest. The scent was as clear as a guide, leading towards the direction that she’d escaped towards.

Jii!!

Garen disappeared instantaneously and gave chase while he followed the scent.

From that devastating explosion which was supposed to be powerful enough to demolish an entire skyscraper, Garen had walked out of it without harm, without even minor injuries.

That devastating explosion had completely razed the woods and shrubs of the forest in a twenty to thirty meters radius from the detonation point, creating a charred dome-shaped area, but other than greatly reducing his speed, Garen was unaffected.

****************************

Tu Lan’s high-speed fleeing had caused her to pant heavily, but she’d taken the chance to place multiple traps and bombs which were activated by Garen who was behind her. Terrifyingly, his speed was never reduced to a halt.

In the heat of the moment, she planted the rest of her miniature high-concentration explosives in one spot, behind a large tree and set a timer of detonation. Finally, after the incredible explosion, complete with a few smoke grenades and poison gas grenades, she finally managed to flee from Garen’s pursuit. After changing directions a few times, she soon came to a halt with a bergamot forest ahead of her.

After an extended period of full-speed sprinting, as well as high levels of mental focus to sense the pursuit behind her, even she would have greatly exhausted her mental energy.

As she rested upon a bergamot tree, Tu Lan felt that her scalp was still numb from the imminent sense of danger of being pursued, and it felt like it hadn’t stopped, and Garen was right on her tail.

However, following the increasingly intense sense of danger, she was pleasantly surprised to find that the Black Dragon Tao Technique had become slightly loosened.

That Serpent dragon that guarded the gate was actually feeling the same kind of pressure, so much so it let out a deep hissing sound, as though it was asking her to advance faster.

Secretively, Tu Lan turned her head around to feel that the sense of danger’s aura seemed to be concentrated the air around. Her surroundings had begun shaking and he was apparently coming towards her.

“It’s all or nothing!” Tu Lan’s entire body shivered uncontrollably under that tremendous feeling of danger, but her intents were solid. She sat cross-legged, shut her eyes, and deep dove into the Black Dragon Tao Technique as her body innately guided her Blood Core into a Holy Technique state.

In the instant she entered the Holy technique state, all of her aura disappeared instantaneously; her scent, her aura, all of it vanished without a trace in that instant, alongside every other element that could make her whereabouts trackable. It was as though she no longer existed at all.

What was even more baffling was that the remnants of her scent also soon dispersed after she entered this state

Tu Lan, who was sitting under the tree, had begun turning transparent and more illusory, as though she was transmigrating into another dimension.

In order to advance to Death Apostle rank, the largest hurdle needed to be addressed; finding her own secret dream realm, and deposit all of her, including her will to live there. If she were to succeed, then even if her physical body and Blood Core were destroyed, she could resurrect from the hidden dream realm. That was the true immortality.

Tu Lan’s biggest weakness now was that she was unable to deposit the entirety of her life and will into the Serpent Dragon Dream Realm that was created by the Black Dragon Tao Technique.

The SDDR seemed to be independent on its own and equipped with its own consciousness and abilities. In reality, the so-called hidden dream realm was actually an invisible life that possessed an odd existence, they were very much alive, and had their own life-force.

Death Apostles needed to be in unison with them and truly let their own life force combine inside an unknown area within a Dream creature, achieving a realm when they would not die.

But this kind of creature normally had their own consciousness, and it would be extremely challenging to obtain their approval, moreover, the merging would take an extended period of time as well. But for some reason, either due to the Black Dragon Tao Technique or some other reason, the Serpent Dragon Gates seemed to be fond of Tu Lan, and so in this dire situation, it had finally let up a sliver, with the intention of allowing Tu Lan to advance earlier.

Under the pressure of life and death, Tu Lan finally entered the Serpent Dragon Gates and began the process to deposit her life and will.

This process was made to separate one’s life and will and combine them with the dream creatures. The process was extremely risky, as she would be forever lost in the dream if she made a misstep, and the entirety of her existence would be devoured by the Serpent Dragon Gate.

But if she were to succeed, her gains would naturally be more lucrative; she would officially reach the Death Apostle Level and obtain everything that belonged to the Serpent Dragon Gate.

Her consciousness continued to dip lower and she became half conscious.

As the time passed, Garen who was far away was still trying to find the scent that had gone missing abruptly, making him lose the trace of Tu Lan.

Even so, his aura told him that Tu Lan was definitely not too far away, she had merely used some sort of technique to hide.

After more than ten minutes, suddenly, the place where Tu Lan disappeared at began glowing white.

The white light was about the size of a firefly, but it slowly expanded, becoming bigger and brighter, until it was the size of a basketball.

Just as the white light expanded, hints of an ancient aura began spreading from the light, as though one was walking through a historical site and experiencing an unknowing sense of vicissitudes that traversed through years of life.

As the aura spread outwards, the trees and grass began to wilt visibly, as though their time had been hastened dramatically.

Jii!!!

At that instant, a pillar of light the girth of an arm shot up towards the sky, piercing through the leaves and the clouds, looking as though it limitlessly extended into space.

The light pillar looked like an endless light rod that connected heaven and earth, and it caused the sky to grow heavy with dense clouds after it pierced into the atmosphere.

Ca-Crack!

Lightning struck down, followed by rumbling sounds of thunders as the blueish white light illuminated the entire forest.

Garen slowly stopped in front of the forest and looked up at the pillar of light.

“Is this…. Advancement?”

A surge of ancient aura was spreading from ahead of him. This aura was completely different from the usual Tu Lan; although it carried her aura, there was an additional extreme ancient, rotten feel to it. as though it was the rotten aura of a creature nearing the end of its life.

He was unknowingly right; if a dream creature’s life wasn’t nearing their end, they would never agree to combine with and be devoured by a Blood Breed. Even though this would prolong their lifespan, to be part of another’s life meant that they would completely lose their independence. Everything would be controlled by the Blood Breed host.

“This aura…. Is this the Death Apostle level?” Garen murmured as he noted this unprecedented aura. He did not take immediate actions but instead, he silently gauged the differences within.

He then slowly turned his head around.

At some point, another silhouette that was tall and slender had walked out. It was a handsome young man with short purple hair, and he was observing from behind a shrub with a cold expression. Oddly, he also had a similar ancient aura emanating from him.

“Oh? There were two?”

“Holy Fist Palace, Garen.” the man said with a deep voice, and slowly walked over. His body had an unsettling emptiness to it as if nothing but air was there. “Today, you will meet your end.”

The white light had suddenly diminished as well, and a silhouette slowly walked out. It was actually Tu Lan, and her injuries seemed to have healed completely, looking as good as new.

Chapter 728: Hunt 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Clan Leader?!” Tu Lan’s eyes turned big, and she had to take a while to calm down.

Two people were standing opposite to each other, with Garen in the middle.

Oddly enough, even though Garen was in the middle, he could not sense the presences of the duo, as though they were merely imaginary.

Bam!!

A sudden surge of purple goo spewed from the purple-haired man’s body and morphed into tentacles mid-air, whipping violently towards Garen. Their speed was terrifying yet they seemed to be enveloping the earth; it was as though the entire space was being completely engulfed by the purple goo.

“Holy Technique number 5…. Pierce!!” the purple-haired man’s eyes suddenly flashed with a blinding purple light.

At that instant, all of the tentacles that had poured out flew up and turned into spikes that rushed towards Garen from all directions, completely surrounding him.

At the same time, Tu Lan too raised her hands. She now seemed like a changed person, as the back of her hand had a black serpent dragon tattoo. As she waved her hands lightly, a formless aura quickly condensed, forming a ferocious translucent serpent dragon about 5-6 meters tall and over ten meters long.

The serpent dragon seemed as though it had been condensed from a stream of water. It let out a loud roar and rushed at Garen.

With countless spikes ahead of him, and a giant serpent dragon with unknown powers diving at him.

Badum!!

A strong purple explosion happened and translucent shockwaves rippled away from the epicenter of the explosion.

Strong gusts of wind floored many trees in the surrounding areas. What was even weirder was that this rippling wind had wilted the green woods by severely dehydrating the water in the plants. Even the birds and squirrels that did not escape in time lost all signs of life, and plummeted directly down to the ground, all of their vitality drained.

Ca-Crack!!

A bergamot tree more than ten meters in diameter had been split in half due to the strong explosion and uprooted. The tree smashed straight into the epicenter of the purple mist.

“Is that all?” a deep voice was heard from within the mist, which rippled quickly across all directions for hundreds of meters beyond.

The purple haired Wellington’s pupils constricted as the remnants of his senses vanished and his aura was completely depleted of vitality. Both eyes were locked upon the center of the mist.

“Even after being in my poison cage, you actually could…. Bam!!” a terrifying tremor suddenly exploded from within the mist.

With a flash of golden light, Garen’s mask appeared before him in an instant. What followed closely was his huge, thunder-like attack which landed precisely on Wellington’s chest.

Without any resistance, the impact of up to a thousand tonnes easily pierced through Wellington’s chest, destroying all of the organs inside of it as a bloody mist sprayed out from his back.

Garen’s right arm had pierced through Wellington’s chest, as though he had been stabbed by an iron rod.

“You…!” Wellington’s eyes were filled with surprise before a large amount of bloody foam started gushing from his mouth.

“Holy Technique. Ultimate New Star!!” suddenly, an invisible hook swung towards Garen from behind and struck his back with immense force.

Tu Lan’s hands were connected to the other end of the hook. Her face was pale and her breathing was irregular. Although her body was visibly weak, she’d obviously put all her strength into that strike.

Her head had gone blank when she saw Garen punching through the clan leader single-handedly. Her lips were trembling, but she didn’t know what to say. There was only one thought: I don’t want to die! Don’t want to die!!

This intense thought had allowed her to release the accumulated explosive power that she just got from advancing.

The Ultimate New Star’s translucent hook was continuously drilling into Garen’s clothes like a corkscrew and digging into his skin, as though it was trying to pierce through his body.

“Just like that?” Garen turned around and looked at Tu Lan, a cold, calm, even slightly disappointed look on his face.

Bam!

The translucent hook was being bounced back with a strong counter, exploding into nothingness in mid-air.

Tu Lan and Wellington’s scalps had gone numb, and chills were running all over their bodies.

This was leagues beyond a human’s capabilities!!

This kind of absurd sturdiness, he was clearly a monster clad in human skin!!

Wellington’s eyes were filled with desperation, and he flung both of his arms around Garen. Ignoring the immense pain from his wound, the purple light from him became more and more concentrated.

“Holy Technique. Ultimate Explosion!!”

Bam!!!

An intense purple tidal wave of flames exploded with Garen at the epicenter of the explosion.

The intense explosion stirred up a gust that was strong enough to push Tu Lan a few meters back, as a translucent serpent dragon immediately materialized to block the explosion for her.

That explosion just now had already gouged a huge crater, but with this second explosion, the ground was marred by a gigantic crater measuring up to sixty meters in diameter. The crater looked as smooth as a mirror.

After some time.

The purple flames had burnt out at last and the purple mist had similarly dissipated. The deepest part of the crater was about thirty meters below ground level.

Garen stood there alone, and the clothes on him were somewhat scorched, and his face finally had a slight change in expression.

In that instant just now, he’d felt a sliver of danger and so he had immediately activated the first star. As his body was strengthened by one fold, at the same time, his aura had exploded and faced Wellington’s explosion head-on. But just like that….

He raised his right hand and gently brushed a wound on his own left shoulder. It was a red bruise that was about as thick as an index finger, but the surprising thing was that bruise was actually recovering at a speed visible to the naked eyes.

“Interesting…” the original disinterest in his eyes was finally gone and had been replaced with a hint of excitement.

Even someone who had activated the Seven Star Life’s Secret Point could be injured?

Even though it was only the first star, but this situation was unheard of even for Garen.

“So Blood Breeds aren’t that weak after all,” he looked up and gazed into the distance, as he observed a certain aura on the boundary of a crater.

Bam!

The glass-like crater beneath his leg suddenly cracked as Garen rushed straight towards the aura while dragging a long afterimage. His speed in that instant had ramped up to an audible level, as the howling from breaking the sound barrier could be heard in the air.

His body began igniting from the friction against the air, looking as though he’d combusted simultaneously, as he charged towards the aura at the side of the crater.

“Die!!”

As he rammed through the soils of the crater that was in the way, Garen stood right in front of Tu Lan.

At this moment, Wellington who should have self-destructed instantaneously appeared behind Tu Lan and hugged her tightly.

“Run!”

The duo vanished into thin air, as though they had dived into a different dimension.

“Trying to run?” Garen sneered.

While moving at immense speed, Garen made a grab before him with his right hand as his palms began glowing with black lights.

The Fantasy Fist exploded instantly, and even though it was just a momentary mental illusory attack, it shocked Tu Lan and Wellington enough that the speed of their escape was disrupted.

It was at this instance, that their fates were decided; otherwise, they might have been able to completely disappear before Garen caught up with them. They could no longer shake him off due to this momentary stun.

Bam!!

The palm with black lights exhibited an immense power, striking down as though it was a giant hammer, and came crashing upon them. Tu Lan and Wellington were actually crushed and their flesh and bone were splattered, much like grapes in a tub, and they became two blobs of meat lumps mixed within the soil.

“I will be back!! Wait and see!! Garen Thomas!!” Wellington’s voice could still be heard with a gritty tone.

Garen’s ears twitched a bit, and his right arm extended suddenly and grabbed onto something in the air.

With a tug, a purple silhouette was pulled out of thin air, and it was actually Wellington who was crushed into mush.

He was completely naked, and his lower half was connected to a poor pangolin, which was constantly twitching. It seemed that he had been regenerating from the pangolin’s flesh and blood.

At this time when he had been yanked out by Garen, he couldn’t even finish his sentence before his head was slapped and exploded from the power behind it, leaving a headless corpse that fell to the ground. The remaining flesh quickly disintegrated and melted into a puddle of flesh that could no longer move.

“You’ll never be able to kill us…. Kekekeke…” Wellington’s voice was heard again. “Our flesh and blood are spread across the entire world, even if there’re no longer any regenerating materials for us here, we can regenerate in other places in the world. Garen Thomas…. You’ll definitely die! I will slowly take away all that you cared about, those that you deem precious and destroy all of them!”

Instantaneously, Garen appeared in the wood several tens of meters away and extended both of his arms. both hands simultaneously tugged two naked people out, which were actually Wellington and Tu Lan.

“You!!” Wellington nervously wanted to blurt out, but before he could say anything, his body had exploded, reduced to countless minced bits of flesh by the Waterbird Fist.

Tu Lan screamed out of fear but she exploded as well, reduced to flesh bits and a pool of blood.

The surroundings had been dyed red from the bloody rain that fell.

Garen seemed unaffected at all, and he looked at the surroundings coldly.

“Want to try speaking again?” he asked coldly.

This time Wellington did not dare to speak again, he clamped his lips tightly and did not dare to speak at all.

He was regenerating inside an ant’s lair underground, using the flesh and blood of ants to regrow the most basic Blood Core and head, and he didn’t dare speak again.

Abruptly, Garen’s head turned and he suddenly appeared on the branch of a large tree on his right. Tu Lan, who was completely naked, was there, and as Garen rushed over, she was petrified beyond reacting and could only scream.

Ahh!!

She could not die again! She wasn’t Wellington, who has spread countless flesh and blood all around the world, and as long as his descendants didn’t completely die off, he could still regenerate. Furthermore, his real body was within the dream, so even if all the flesh had been exhausted outside, he could still regenerate, just that it would take a bit more time.

But she was different.

She had just deposited her life successfully, and not only did she have insufficient flesh and descendants spread across the world, even her dream where she had deposited her life would become unstable after successive deaths.

“No!!!

Dang!!

A white light suddenly appeared in front of Garen, and blocked his right arm. The air suddenly let out a sigh.

Oddly enough, this white light which clashed with Garen’s palm was actually capable of bruising him and leave a mark, as though the light was very sharp.

Garen felt that his spirit was shaken, and his whole body and world tremored.

Expert!!

He immediately retreated to his original location in an instant, and warily stared at the white light that had just appeared.

It was a mental-type top-tier expert!!

Garen’s eyes finally turned serious for the first time.

The white light circled Tu Lan once and slowly landed on the floor, turning into a handsome man in white.

“Can you let this poor junior go? Master Garen.” the man had a hint of sadness in his eyes, which made this person felt like a damsel in distress.

“Leader Ashen!!” Tu Lan who was behind him suddenly shouted out of excitement.

Ashen?!!

Garen’s heart was stirred.

The world strongest Blood Breed! The First Death Apostle, Ashen Castine!?

Chapter 729: Ashen 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s gaze was fixed on that man. He rubbed his chin, and the edge of the mask there had actually cracked slightly when it was hit by the white light.

‘Be careful, it’s not going to be easy dealing with this guy,’ Black Sethe whispered in his ear. ‘He’s a top spiritual energy user, I did not expect a master level user to appear in this world.’

Garen slowly nodded his head and stared at that guy with his left eye.

From his clothes to his hair, even his skin was extremely pale, this was Ashen Castine, the world’s one and only strongest Blood Breed.

“So he’s the first Death Apostle, the Ashen Lord,” Garen slowly said. “As the leader of the light party, it’s truly unexpected that you will appear to rescue the Death Apostle of the Secret Party.”

Ashen stood silently on a tree branch, and Garen was below him. The two of them were seven or eight meters apart, but the area’s atmosphere felt as if it was being vaguely split into two halves.

He gently caressed Tu Lan’s hair with a complicated look on his face.

“In this world, there hasn’t been any new Death Apostle for many years, so every Death Apostle is my neo-humans’ greatest assets.”

He was the leader of the Light Party and he had always advocated that the blood breeds were leaders and evolved humans, whereas the Death Apostles of the Blood Breeds were the final evolution of humans.

Unlike the Secret Party, as they believed that the blood breeds were a higher ranked species than humans, while the Light Party considered themselves to be a member of the human race.

“That’s your own business,” Garen said calmly. “I have my own principles, and you have your own way of doing.”

Ashen was stunned, he did not think that Garen would not do him this favor, “If you insist on fighting…”

“Show me the strength of the first leader.”

The moment Garen spoke, he lifted his right arm, which had grown bigger and thicker, and swung it at Ashen.

Boom!!

More terrifyingly, a large group of black shadows had suddenly burst out of his right arm. It started stretching and morphed into a huge slender arm. Then, it swung at Ashen.

The arm was more than ten meters long and it was still stretching!

Bang-bang-bang-bang-bang!!!

A large area of the forest, about 10 meters wide, was directly cut down by the huge black shadow hand, and the whole forest became an open space with hand-shaped prints all around.

Strangely, he did not find any traces of Castine, and even Tu Lan seemed to have disappeared.

“This is a meaningless fight,” Castine’s voice came from all around Garen.

Garen sneered coldly and quickly tapped his shoulders around ten times with his left fingers.

Hooo!

A cache of black gas swelled up once again within him.

“Third star! Activate!!”

His entire body seemed to grow bigger and bigger, and the green-black blood vessels on his body looked like twisted wires. His muscles were bulging tightly, and each pec was like steel castings. At this point, he was more than two meters tall and he looked like a back metal giant.

At the same time, his overall attributes were once again raised by an average of seven points to achieve an average twenty-one points. With this terrifying increase in sense of perception, Garen finally caught a glimpse of subtle flaws in the surrounding space.

“Left!”

His left arm slammed like a cannonball to the left.

Boom!!!

The giant green-black hand fell like a hammer on the seemingly empty space.

Instantly, a slight muffling sound was heard, and it seemed like Ashen had been hit. A huge horrifying force suddenly created a high-frequency vibration which made the space somewhat unstable, and a small buzzing sound could be heard.

“Holy Technique – deactivate,” a clear voice was heard coming from the air.

As he heard that sound, Garen’s pupil suddenly shrank.

‘Be careful! It’s the nature of time ability!!’ Black Sethe warned. “Retreat!!”

Without hesitation, Garen retreated like a black lightning bolt, and in just a blink of an eye, he was ten meters away. The moment he retreated, there was a burst of white gas that seemed to be in pursuit. A strange looking white face appeared mid-air, which opened its mouth and appeared to be growling, although there was actually no sound.

“Fourth star!!” Garen’s body suddenly swelled and started growing once again. He put his hands together and held them high up above his head.

“Waterbird Fist Profound – White Jade!!”

At that moment, his tanned-skinned hands morphed into a black knife and made a slice. A similar looking white destroyed shadow was being drawn in mid-air. The black knife actually drew out a white destroyed shadow!

The difference between this and the other two profound techniques was that the White Jade was not as strong as the Flight and did not have the large-scale attack of the Dual Blade. The only ability it had was to increase the defense of both his hands to its limit and concentrate all his spiritual energy into his hands. It could forcefully increase the strength of his hands to a terrifying level in a short time, and together with Garen’s physical quality, if he were to activate the fifth star, the profound White Jade that he cast would be able to surpass the thirty points physical limit.

Not only did this surpass the limit of his body, it also strengthened the hardness of his exterior to an extremely high level, equivalent to turning his flesh and blood into iron and steel like a non-living thing for a short period of time. By abandoning his flesh and blood, he was able to obtain an extremely great strength. Because there was no living activity, his body would not be restricted by his physical limit.

This trick did not seem to be effective when he was against Nadia, therefore, this was his first time using it in an actual fight. Even so, without a doubt, White Jade’s effect was the strongest.

More terrifyingly, he was able to sustain this effect for about ten minutes at a time.

Garen’s hands turned into knives and it directly slashed the white face which was flying towards him.

Ahh!!!!

As if someone was screaming in pain, the moment they collided, Garen only felt a slight pain in his body, and he was pushed back by three steps!

When his palms came in contact with the white gas, there was an explosion and the white gas evacuated. Garen had to take a few steps to stabilize his body. He did not have any problems with his palms, but the upper part of his arms seemed to be slightly affected.

Right at this moment, Ashen Castine and Tu Lan appeared mid-air in front of the collision.

He covered his mouth and seemed to cough, and traces of blood could be seen between his fingers.

“So powerful…. I’ve heard about how powerful the Holy Fist Palace is but I thought they were just rumors… I didn’t expect… Cough-cough!” Castine coughed.

He stared at the young blond man in front of him. In nearly a million years, he had never met such a powerful human.

Every breath that he took created small holes on the ground. The heat emitted from his body was as hot as a furnace, and just by getting close to him, he could feel the huge radiation of heat from his body. Even by speaking casually, the vibration could cause an ordinary person to lose consciousness.

This level of power, he can no longer be called human…

The blonde man standing was wearing a mask on his face, one that had countless black tiny eyes carved onto the forehead, and he stood at almost three meters tall. With his horrifying green-black muscles, it gave people the impression that he was a giant monster truck that would block the cars behind.

Under his terrifying breathing sounds, he sucked in waves of air, and then spewed it out again, stirring up a small whirlwind around. Just by breathing, he was able to induce such a powerful air current.

Even Castine was slightly shocked.

Compared to his neo-human Blood Breeds, he was less like a human!

“I thought that there weren’t any worthy strong opponents in this world,” Garen slowly opened his mouth and spoke in a low voice that sounded like thunder, and his body began to expand again.

He could actually continue to get stronger!?!

The look on Castine’s face finally changed, and he took a few steps back from the air flow made by Garen’s speech.

He was not the only one who was astonished; Tu Lan who was standing behind him was stunned and could not get any words out. When Garen spoke, she felt the ground tremble and the vibrations from the huge sound wave.

A human being able to train to this level, he could no longer be considered human! Compared to Garen, she suddenly felt that the Blood Breeds were so much more ordinary….

Hooo!!!

A gigantic airstream started spreading in all directions with Garen as the center point, and trees were being uprooted and falling all around.

All this was just from Garen taking a step forward, yet such a ground shacking impact had been caused.

“Ashen Castine….” Garen stared at him quietly with his remaining left eye. “You are eligible to witness my strongest form.”

“You….!” just as Castine wanted to say something, he suddenly felt the earth shaking for a moment, as though there was an earthquake.

“Let’s have a showdown!”

His roar was like a thunderstorm which growled right in front of him, and even though Castine was horrifyingly strong, he was still shaken by the impact.

At that moment, Castine saw a giant figure suddenly appearing in front of him. The giant was more than three meters tall and the shadow of his terrifying physique overshadowed him and Tu Lan.

Armor-like bulging muscles formed on Garen’s shoulders, and the muscles on his whole body were like a horrifying ferocious heavy armor, complete with an obvious metallic sheen on them.

His right and left palms were coming together in their direction as if he wanted to directly squash Castine to death. The palms of his hands were larger than his head and looked like two giant iron bricks, and as they closed in, they were creating a terrifying, whistling sound.

Without having much time to think, Castine hurriedly took a few steps back.

“Holy Technique – Light!!”

An unknown ancient language was coming from his mouth, and his words were articulated, his speed was sharply raised and he streaked into a white light.

This was similar to what he had done just now. The speed of the white light was extremely fast, and he instantly broke free from Garen’s range.

But right at this moment.

Bang!!!

As Garen clapped his palms together, a horrifying sound wave erupted with an extremely strong vibration and explosion, which smashed into Castine and Tu Lan.

The two of them moaned in pain at the same time and tumbled onto the grassland not far away, as blood dripped out of their ears.

Garen moved his body forward and made a huge leap. It was actually a few meters long leap, but it seemed as though he’d teleported right in front of Castine and stepped on him!

A loud bang was heard, and a cloud of white gas which was more than 10 meters in length and width exploded and wrapped around Garen.

The air current swept away everything around Garen; the trees, dirt, rocks, living creatures, and even Tu Lan were blown away by the terrible explosion. Bang-bang-bang sounds were heard hundreds of meters away as huge trees were shattered. A figure slowly fell to the ground, covered in blood and on the verge of death.

“Holy Fist Garen….”

White gas had gathered during the explosion and formed into a white-haired man figure, which was Castine.

He covered his mouth and could no longer hold it in; his nose and ears were bleeding, and the drops of blood dripped onto his white clothes and stained them red. The blood could no longer return to his body, which indicated that he’d completely lost his vitality.

Chapter 730: Ashen 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

One had to know that when an Upper-Level Blood Breed was wounded, his blood would flow back into the wound to prevent him from losing strength due to blood loss.

However, as a Death Apostle, Castine didn’t manage to activate this regeneration trait at all. One could only imagine how overwhelmingly powerful Garen was. Not only did he have a ridiculously large attack range, he also had a very delicate technique to make his opponent felt hopeless.

Castine stared at the center of the explosion quietly as the white gas dissipated slowly to reveal a bulky humanoid monster at its core.

It was Garen!

Castine’s pupils contracted in disbelief, as he couldn’t see even the slightest trace of injury on Garen at all.

“You…” Castine tried to speak but he realized that his body was wracked with pain.

Boom!!!

He immediately exploded. His upper body turned into minced meat instantly and splattered everywhere on the empty field, staining the newly created crater with red bloody meat bits.

Castine’s lower body took a few steps forward before dropping down to the ground.

This was the horrifying part of the Waterbird Fist. One wouldn’t be safe even after completely blocking their opponent’s attack. What made it so lethal was the explosion after the contact.

Castine’s bloody mist swiftly dissipated and turned into white vapor as it diffused into the air. Then, the white vapor condensed into one location and formed into his body once more, including the white shirt he was wearing.

Castine regenerated back once more and now he had no visible injuries. Even so, he knew that if he couldn’t even injure his enemy while fighting to his death, then that death would be meaningless.

A Death Apostle too would experience a reduction in regeneration rate when he died too many times in a very short span.

There was a secret that was known only by the Death Apostles, one regarding the mystery of the Death Apostle’s immortality. It was true that a Death Apostle was immortal; as long as their dream world was not discovered, they could always resurrect.

However, one would require physical energy to resurrect in the material world. One would require some form of energy to restructure the blood and meat of their body.

If one was to die for more than ten times in a month, then one would wait for a certain amount of time before one resurrected once more. As one’s dying streak grew longer, the duration to be resurrected would grow longer as well.

In the beginning, it would require a few minutes and from then on, it would keep doubling up. For each death afterward, one would require twice the amount of time as the previous death.

Initially, one would require one minute to be resurrected. Then it would require two minutes and the next would be four minutes, eight minutes and it would keep going in such a trend. It would require very little iteration for the time to be extremely long.

In history, there were Death Apostles who had been dealt with in such a manner.

There were countless Death Apostles that were kept on the killing list by other Death Apostles. Eventually, the Death Apostle would spend all of his energy and be trapped inside the dream world, unable to return any more.

His resurrected point had been thrown into the core of a volcano, which had a great temperature. Furthermore, there was powerful witchcraft inscribed and witch weapons were used as well. At the moment he was about to resurrect, he would immediately be burned to death by the high temperature alone. Afterall, his body was extremely weak when he was just resurrected. Hence, no one had remembered the existence of that Death Apostle. Perhaps now, he would require a few thousands or ten thousand years to be resurrected. No one would know as he would be considered non-existent at that point.

Castine clearly understood the current situation he was in. His Blood Nucleus had been exhausted by the Secret Party and he had almost exhausted his blood essence as well. Even if it wasn’t spent, he was no match for that monstrous human before him.

The situation was very detrimental to him.

He stood inside the huge crater which spanned a few hundred meters long in radius. It was a smooth, white crater formed by the multiple explosions, and the surface at the bottom was completely flat.

Castine stared quietly at Garen. He knew that his opponent wouldn’t be able to last in this state for long, hence it was a battle to see who could last longer.

Garen stared back at Castine too.

The opponent was no match for him, but…

He couldn’t be in the fifth star’s state for too long. Although he had obtained the Demonic Book’s power and the blessing of the Holy Phoenix Scriptures, he could only be in this state for five hours. It would be troublesome for him if the opponent were to drag the battle for more than five hours. This was due to the fact that his body and aura would regress into a weak phase after activating the fifth star for five hours. If he were to not save some of his energy then, he would be in grave danger if he couldn’t activate his Seven Star Life’s Secret Point at all.

Although he was much stronger than the opponent when he was in the fourth-star state, the power that Castine had revealed thus far was powerful enough to injure him at the fourth star. While it may cause just a very small injury, it may pile up over time and become serious as well.

Afterall, he was not a Death Apostle and wouldn’t be able to resurrect indefinitely. If the opponent refused to give up and kept giving him these small injuries, it would accumulate to the point where it would be serious…

Garen started to feel frightened. While his opponent was not as powerful as him, the perseverant attitude was too much for him. If Castine were able to catch him off guard and injure him slowly, the injury would accumulate to the point that it would be troublesome.

“We really have no need to keep fighting,” Castine’s voice rang from afar.

While the two of them were hundreds of meter apart, they spoke as if they were right beside each other. This was technically true as this distance could be covered by them in the blink of an eye.

Garen changed his gaze slightly and stomped his leg out of the blue. With that stomp, a stone popped up and he sent the stone flying out with a punch.

Pew!!

The stone moved so fast that a streak of red sparks followed behind the stone. It was caused by the friction between the stone and the air. The stone was shot into a layer of dirt inside the crater the right behind him.

A cry came from the layer of dirt and it was the voice of Wellington. He wasn’t able to evade Garen’s senses and died once more at his hand.

“Stop it!!” Castine tried to stop him but it was too late. His face was filled with anger. “I’ve said it before. There’s not much hatred between us and this battle is completely unnecessary!”

Garen turned his head and stared at him.

“We can stop the battle but I need you people to reach an agreement. The Holy Fist Palace and the people from the Blood Breed shall never interfere with each other.”

“No problem,” Castine agreed without any hesitation.

“I have another additional request,” Garen lifted up his index finger.

“What is it? Speak up.” Castine didn’t like to battle and truly hated war deep down. From his perspective, it meant nothing to him if he had to sacrifice a little bit to stop the war.

“I can stop killing the Death Apostle, but I’ll bring her along with me!” Garen pointed to the left at a weak presence far outside the crater.

The owner of this presence was surprisingly Tu Lan!!

“No way!!” Castine rejected immediately. The aggressiveness showed by his opponent was a sign that he was a cruel and torturous man. If Tu Lan were to be under him, she wouldn’t be able to escape from his grasp anymore. Garen was a person whose strength had reached an overwhelmingly powerful level, so much so that Castine wouldn’t even judge him as a standard human being. Who could be sure of how long he will live? What if he was the same as the Blood Breed? Her entire life would be over if that were the case.

“You don’t have to worry that I will torture her. I’m just interested in the Death Apostle’s resurrection mechanism. I would not purposely torture her at all. In fact, I will treat her as a member of the Holy Fist Palace and you can observe for however long all you like,” Garen seemed to have predicted Castine’s thoughts. Although his opponent was a very old man who had lived for a long time, he too was no oil lamp as he had lived through three lifetimes. The things that he had experienced couldn’t be compared with others.

Castine pondered quietly for a while. In the past, he had also met a very powerful witch who had tried to research the Death Apostle’s immortality but to no avail. Against this overwhelmingly powerful enemy, this meant that he had been given a chance to infiltrate into the inner circle of his enemy’s base. This way, he would able to learn the secret of him being so powerful.

If he could determine the source of his overwhelmingly powerful strength, then it would be considered a huge victory for the Blood Breeds.

Castine started to feel excited as he thought of this.

“It depends entirely on her whether she wants to become your underling,” he purposely diverted his voice towards Tu Lan who was far away.

“I accept!! I accept!!” Tu Lan immediately replied loudly from afar and she seemed to be crying.

Tears were all over her face as she huddled on the ground. Her whole body would shiver whenever she saw Garen. It was obvious that she had been traumatized by his attacks. Garen’s cruelty had shed a new light on her as she died a few times.

She was currently placed in the same mindset as Dahm, in which Garen was a person they could never hope to win in their mind. Even if there came a day where they surpassed Garen in terms of force, the mindset would cause them to unable to perform fully in front of Garen. Hence they would be defeated easily.

It had taken a lot of effort for her to be promoted to a Death Apostle. Never had she expected that she would experience such a tragedy the moment she became a Death Apostle. Garen had indeed carved a deep impression on her.

It wasn’t just her that was afraid of Garen, even the Dream Creature that had merged with her was afraid as well the moment it saw Garen. Their fusion was never stable to begin with, and after she’d been defeated a few times, she was at death’s door. If not for Castine’s timely arrival, history might have been made where a Death Apostle would die for the very first time.

“I accept!!!” she cried loudly as if she was afraid that Garen would punch a hole through her hand again.

She had originally been a normal woman from a noble household. She had been turned into a Blood Breed when a dying Blood Breed injected his Blood Nucleus into her. After entering the household, she’d slowly gathered her strength to become an Upper-Level Blood Breed and now a Death Apostle.

Tu Lan always had a sense of insecurity with her deep down in her heart. This strange insecurity was kept her from improving her battle strength and persevering in practicing the Holy Technique. She could only suppress this insecurity deep in her heart by constantly improving herself.

She’d thought that she could simply kill anyone when she had become a Death Apostle, as she would be one of the strongest beings in the world no matter how one looked at it. However, never did she expect that she would meet this freak, Garen. After she realized that it was futile to defend against him, the insecurity deep inside her was out of the bag. This was especially true when she saw Ashen Castine, the first Apostle helpless against that man. She gave in to her fear and fell into despair.

“I’m glad you accepted the offer!” Garen smiled satisfactorily as he cancelled his fifth-star state. His body starting shrinking and returned to normal in a few moments, no longer looking like a monster.

He jumped out of the crater and stood beside Tu Lan. He then gently grabbed her by the neck as if he was picking up a kitten.

“First Apostle, we shall meet if we have the chance.”

After that, Garen picked up Tu Lan and sprinted swiftly into the sea of forests, disappearing into it.

Updated by

Castine stood still and gave off a long sigh as he looked at Garen’s shrinking figure.

He knew that after this battle, the Holy Fist Palace would become a powerful force that could rival the Blood Breeds!

Chapter 731: Post-Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Word of this battle between the Holy Fist and the Death Apostles spread like wildfire. There were people who claimed they had felt the ripples of shockwaves from the battle from afar. Certain countries’ military satellite monitoring system also picked up strong signals from the area of the battle. Of course, all of these details were confidential and sealed away.

Only the highest ranked personnel had the security clearance to access this information.

Garen started pursuing Tu Lan Wellington from the Holy Fist Palace. On the way, Tu Lan had managed to evolve into a death apostle and successfully surrounded Garen with the help of the head of the Wellington household, but the two were easily defeated. If it weren’t for the interference of the Number One Apostle, the two would have been utterly annihilated by Garen.

This piece of information was obtained from the internal messages of the Blood Breeds.

Ashen had managed to escape. This was a truth admitted by the Number One Apostle himself. As the strongest Death Apostle, if he hadn’t personally interfered in this, the results of this battle would have been unpredictable.

As the message spread, it caused tremors throughout the world.

This shook up the entire Blood Breed civilization, both the Light Party and the Secret Party. Various investigations on the Holy Fist Palace immediately started, with countless resources and manpower all siphoned towards the tasks of finding the truth behind how a group could manage to become so strong in just a short timespan.

Various technological or even secret means were used in attempts to investigate deeper.

Word of the top tier martial arts from the Holy Fist Palace started to leak out, spreading throughout the world. Rumor has it that if you managed to complete the martial arts training at the Holy Fist Palace, you would attain a monstrous combat prowess similar to the Blood Breeds.

These rumors and legends started spreading more and more, painting an even more concrete image.

Since the Secret Party had failed to repress Ashen, after the former strongest Number One Apostle had escaped, the two factions were once again forced to return to the negotiating table, with the resources of both sides drastically diminished. Due to the immense pressure from the Holy Fist Palace and the witches, they were finally willing to talk.

Although there’s still a sense of hostility and rivalry between the two factions, it was now far less intense.

On the other hand, Garen and his men had escorted Tu Lan to the Bailey Group headquarters, only to find the building completely abandoned. Just as they were prepared to move to the headquarters of the Primary Colours, they received an invitation, stating that the people who targeted the Holy Fist Palace had been removed and that they would send the appropriate reparations to the Combat Club soon.

Facing the Holy Fist Palace that was strong enough to suppress the Blood Breeds, even a group like the Primary Colours had to be cautious not to step on their tail.

At this moment, the Combat Club’s networking circle has also been rapidly increasing. After the second batch of students left, this network started to spread throughout the globe, connecting them with influential people all over the world.

After the battle with the Death Apostle, as the representative of the Holy Fist Palace, Garen’s fame seemed to have been raised to unparalleled heights.

Although most people only knew about the most minute of details, to be able to defeat two allied death apostles and almost being forced to retreat with Ashen’s presence showcased Garen’s ridiculous strength.

******

Holy Fist Palace

A thick layer of snow blanketed the entire palace.

It was late at night, and in the empty meeting hall, the smooth black marble flooring could almost reflect a person’s appearance.

Garen sat at the highest point of the hall, while his captive, Tu Lan, stood behind him.

On both sides stood the top-ranked members in the Combat Club and the Nighthawks, in two orderly lines.

Dahm, Hochman, Quentin, Xander, Ninox, Baldy of the Nighthawks, and Caesar from the second batch.

These people all stood there giving off an imposing air, giving out their reports when instructed by their master.

The one speaking now was Xander.

“We’ve recently captured 423 people who attempted to acquire intel about our Holy Fist Style, most of them were from the intelligence and recon agencies from various countries. Most likely, under the orders of the Blood Breed or overambitious parties. After your battle with the Death Apostles, our name has been solidified in this world. Although our numbers are nowhere near the witches or the Blood Breed, from the standpoint of high-level combat, we have master sitting here. There’s no way anyone would dare to take us lightly. Under this condition, everything is progressing rapidly as part of the plan.”

Xander bowed and moved back in line.

Quentin, who was on his left, stood out to give her report.

“Regarding the internal movements of the Blood Breed. According to the spies we’ve manipulated and planted within the ranks of the Blood Breed, the situation between the two factions is slowly dying down. Although there were still a few violent clashes and confrontations, the number of casualties have drastically decreased. This is most likely the effect of our threat. On the witches’ side, AG has just declared Mount Enredour to be closed. However, on the same day, a witch from the Dark Colours was ambushed, severing 3 of her limbs. This is likely an attack by the extremists from the Blood Breeds as a revenge from the battle of Wellington. I suggest that we also set up some defenses in case they decide to attack.”

“That’s natural,” Garen said. “Dahm, have you finished arranging the schedule to get the Sleepless Face Mask I want?”

Dahm hastily stood out.

“Everything is set, we will be heading to Memphis Forest tomorrow. I’ve already sent my men to scout out the Moon River over there, preliminary investigations have narrowed it down to a few possible locations.”

“Update me with the good news then.”

“Understood.”

“Oh, I also heard that you joined the National Security Agency and got a new position,” Garen usually didn’t care much about the affairs of the nation, but Dahm was from one of the most influential households in politics, hence becoming a civil servant or government official was only natural.

“It’s a special forces department, newly founded specifically for Spec-Ops. Officially, I am the director general of this department,” Dahm politely answered. As he dived deeper into the realm of the martial arts, he and Hochman had started to feel even more deeply that their absurd growth rate was completely abnormal. It wasn’t just him, everyone who had trained with Garen had the same amazing progress.

Obviously, that was the only explanation for it. The source always led back to Garen. He must have used some method to allow them to grow alongside him.

After learning about this and undergoing various investigations and experimentation, he and Hochman came to the understanding that their growth was based on Garen’s strength. Most of it wasn’t due to their own hard work.

After learning about this, any thoughts of malice towards the Holy Fist Palace were completely abandoned by the two.

Of course, that was also the reason why Garen completely did not care about the actions of those under him and gave complete control to the people under him. Except during his personal training sessions and the occasional confrontations, he completely relinquished his control on them, not caring about the internal disputes between his students.

This lead to the two shifting their focus back towards each other. Their mutual fighting styles were similar to Yin and Yang; they were the two polar extremes of the Waterbird Fist so naturally, they weren’t on friendly terms.

Recently Hochman had finally managed to capture his beloved cousin once again. After he found out that it was all Dahm’s doing, he was even more pissed.

The two’s confrontations once again escalated to a new height.

“What about the 7th mask? Hochman, have you found any leads?” Garen turned his head towards Hochman.

“We’ve already found some clues on it,” Hochman nodded. “According to our sources, the 7th mask is most likely in the hands of the Bailey Group Chairman. I’ve already sent out a command, ordering my forces to pour all their resources towards hunting Kabb and his accomplice Medis. However, even before this, the two seemed to have disappeared off our radar. They might’ve heard about our movements and went into hiding.”

“You can ask the witches from the Dark Colours for some assistance if needed. Their representative they sent to request aid should almost be here,” Garen answered. “As for the amount of aid from both sides, I’ll leave the negotiations to you.”

“Alright,” Hochman was now one of the heads of the largest conglomerates in the world. Unlike Dahm, he’d chose to take the path of economics and finance, but he had also achieved a similar level of influence in the world.

For these Monthly meetings at the Holy Fist Palace, he had no choice but to squeeze out some time from his regularly packed schedule.

Next, Caesar headed up to report on the progress of the Combat Club and its connections, some of their requests and the corresponding advantages it granted the Holy Fist Palace.

As for the progress of the Combat Club, they now own 3 of the biggest hotel chains throughout various countries, 5 private banks, and 1 media corporation. These were only the direct affiliations. Other intermediaries include various influences the members have throughout over 30 countries, with enough influence to affect the domestic economy and politics of numerous small and medium-sized nations. However, their influences on major countries are severely limited, as those are within the control of the blood breed and the witches.”

However, with this, the effective direct income of the Holy Fist Palace was more than 30 billion per annum, and this was only the first year of their growth.

The assets recorded under Garen’s name was valued at more than 100 billion, an unimaginable amount.

Even Garen himself was shocked when he heard this amount. He’d never expected his wealth to increase at such a rapid rate. Only after the detailed explanation by Caesar did he understand what was going on. A large amount of these assets were mainly from the gifts or discounts given by other forces in the world, trying to get on the good side of the Combat Club. In addition, with the support of the connections of the members themselves, the growth was boosted even further.

It had almost been a month since the battle with the apostles.

In actuality, it hadn’t even been a year since this palace had finished its construction. However, within such a short time, this place managed to become such an influential monster.

Tu Lan, who was standing behind Garen this whole time, was completely shell-shocked

Listening to the reports from below her, even she could not hide her shock.

These people giving reports all had supernatural abilities, and even the weakest amongst the bunch was at the level of a Middle-level Blood Breed. There were even 3 who have reached the level of Upper-level Blood Breeds. This level of strength has already far surpassed the old Blood Breed households. They had reached the level of a household of death apostles.

This was only the growth of a few years.

Garen was completely unworried about her leaking out the reports she heard, as he had no intention of hiding anything from her. He just allowed her to listen in freely on this entire session.

Was it because he could confidently suppress her completely?

Tu Lan started to bite her lip in frustration.

“Lord, Ms. Vivian has a message for you. She says that Mr. Emmer and Mrs. Trish wish to see you,” suddenly, a subject was brought up from below.

Suddenly the entire hall fell silent.

Garen, still sitting on his throne, paused briefly.

“Reply to her that I’ll return tomorrow.”

“Understood,” the subordinate below him bowed and swiftly departed.

“That’s all for today’s meeting. Cece, please stay back for a moment,” Garen calmly said.

Chapter 732: Post-Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Immediately, the people at the bottom bowed and silently left the hall, and only Ninox remained. She had the same style as back in her student days; she was in a pair of white skinny jeans and a knotted white T-shirt that flaunted her curves. However, her face was a bit pale, as she was still recovering from her injuries.

She looked over at Tu Lan who was standing behind Garen. Recognizing her, she had a displeased expression. However, since Garen was there, she didn’t say anything and quietly stood there awaiting her orders.

She was the most loyal person to Garen out of all the members of the Combat Club. Regarding the manipulation via the Soul Seed, she didn’t mind at all. On the contrary, she was extremely grateful for what Garen did for her, as it turned her life around.

Although she would have to face a lot of dark and gory predicaments, the Fantasy Fist wasn’t as bloody as Waterbird Fist. By using Waterbird Fist as a support for Fantasy Fist, she could easily render the opponent helpless. This also meant that she had also killed a lot of people, but most of the time blood wouldn’t be spilled.

Garen had never forced her to do anything though. Just like Dahm and Hochman, she’d started off merely as a martial arts hobbyist who had some basic training in the East. If not for her gratitude towards Garen and the influence of the soul seed primer, there was no way Ninox could’ve adapted to her current job and lifestyle at the Holy Fist Palace.

Garen stood up from his throne. After everyone else had exited the hall, he finally walked down, with Cece and Tu Lan following closely behind him. The trio headed to the palace, towards the common resting facilities used by Garen and the members of the palace.

Ninox had the utmost admiration towards Garen, and so she eagerly followed behind him. Tu Lan hesitated for a brief moment but reluctantly followed the two.

“How is the training going for your Fantasy Fist?” Garen asked while he continued to walk.

Cece politely answered.

“I’m only one more level away from reaching the maximum level.”

“Oh?” Garen was somewhat surprised. “That’s fast progress. Looks like your innate abilities are great after all.”

The three walked to a darker corner. Garen suddenly stopped and turned around.

“I have a task for you.”

“I await your orders, master,” Ninox immediately lowered her head.

“I want you to protect someone in secret back in my hometown of Grano,” Garen calmly said. He opened up his mouth, a name immediately rang in Cece’s ears.

She was stunned for a moment, and her eyes held a hint of disappointment. However, she quickly composed herself once more.

“I will complete your orders.”

“Out of my apprentices, I’m most worried about you,” Garen let out a sigh, “Relax your whole body.”

Ninox was once again stunned, not understanding what her master meant.

In an instant, she saw Garen’s palm fly towards her chest. Her face immediately flushed red, and she forcefully suppressing her urge to dodge his hand, closing her eyes.

Poke!

Almost as if numerous sounds merged together, it created a loud sound.

Garen’s index finger lightly poked a pressure point in between Cece’s breasts. He then slowly pulled back his hand.

At that moment, Ninox’s chest started to boil up, almost as if her entire body was being entirely enveloped by the warmth of a hot spring. This feeling only lasted for a brief moment and it faded away almost immediately.

“I left something inside your body that in the case of emergencies, such as when you face a life-or-death situation, it will automatically activate,” Garen’s calm voice could be heard once again.

“Apprentice…” Ninox suddenly realized that it was all her dirty imagination, and she immediately blushed. She slightly lowered her head, her heart beating rapidly.

“Alright, I’m counting on you!” he patted her shoulders, “Don’t let me down.”

“Yes!” Cece frantically nodded and turned around to escape from this situation. With a few huge leaps, she even used her secret techniques to escape this embarrassing situation.

“She likes you,” Tu Lan said in a soft voice.

“Is that so?” Garen didn’t seem surprised; Cece’s reactions were easy to read even for a normal person.

Tu Lan could also understand Garen. After all, his existence was on a whole new level.

An unparalleled position, monstrous strength, a handsome appearance comparable to Apollo, the God of Sun himself, he had every masculine trait that one could ever want. It would be even weirder if someone didn’t like him.

Garen also understood how Cece felt, but a young girl’s emotions were constantly changing. She was still young and might not understand what she was feeling yet, might not know what she actually liked yet. She would only find out more when she matured, and it was still too early to tell.

This mission he gave was also a form of training for Ninox. In the end, she still didn’t have much experience in killing and so she was still very naive.

What Garen left inside her was the aura to unlock the first star of his Seven Star Life’s Secret Point Secret Method. That small amount of aura could allow Ninox to obtain the burst potential of the first star in emergencies. That would allow her to double all of her stats, at the cost of collapsing in exhaustion for one entire day after.

This was his protection for her. Out of all his apprentices, Ninox had the purest intentions towards the Holy Fist Palace.

“You can go back and rest,” Garen looked Tu Lan in the eye. “Remember, you are not allowed to leave the Holy Fist Palace.”

“Yeah yeah,” Tu Lan made a dejected face. “It’s not like I could leave even if I wanted to, right?”

Her body was planted with Garen’s soul seed primer, as she’d given in to the temptation and started learning the Fantasy Fist. Even if it was the Blood Breed, after learning Garen’s secret techniques and demonic techniques, they would expectedly start to get engrossed in it. It wasn’t because the training brought them pleasure, but it was mostly because they had to find Garen every so often for him to personally refill the energy of the soul seed primer.

Without Garen’s soul primer to suppress the effects of learning the Fantasy Fist, even if she was a death apostle, there would still be numerous side effects of migraines and even memory loss.

However, with the pleasure getting stronger from learning the Fantasy Fist, Tu Lan, who had been bored for thousands of years, couldn’t help but delve deeper and deeper. She started taking the initiative in her training even without the orders of Garen.

Garen also found it strange, as the Fantasy Fist didn’t always have this type of effect. Ever since it had been written into the Demonic Book, it started to have the same effects of the Waterbird Fist, a weird pleasure in learning the technique and soul resistance. Similar to the other secret techniques, it became a demonic technique with rapid progression rates.

He guessed that this had something to do with the Demonic Book.

After Tu Lan left, he headed towards his reading room alone.

After closing the door, he saw the boiling hot glass of green tea freshly made from the kitchen. Inside the glass wasn’t just normal green tea leaves, there were also countless valuable herbs, all for the purpose of replenishing one’s vitality, qi and blood. The water had turned a bright shade of green due to an excessive amount of a certain ingredient used. However, if a normal person were to ingest this, it would undoubtedly have the same effects of drinking a poisonous tonic. Its frightening concentration could easily be made out from the intense aroma slowly enveloping the entire room. If a normal person were to drink this, they would definitely collapse immediately.

However, Garen was completely used to this, he just grabbed the glass and chugged its contents down.

“Is there any way for my right eye to recover?” Garen asked as if talking to another person.

At that moment, Black Sethe’s voice softly rang in his ears.

‘I’ve checked, the wounds left by Nadia has a special ability to cause permanent damage. To put it simply, after you get wounded and certain parts of your body completely stop functioning, there will be no chance of recovery. In other words, I can’t do anything else to help your eye.”

Garen lightly touched his right eye.

“As a Void Pursuer, can’t I use the core of void creatures to repair my wounds?”

‘That is the case, but those only apply to average wounds from normal void creatures. This ability of Nadia is something more like gene erasing. It looked as if she only attacked your right eye, but in reality, she attacked your body’s cells, removing all genes linked to your right eye in the cells, making it seem as if you never had a right eye in the first place. Naturally, there is no way of recovering from that,’ Black Sethe explained.

‘A better plan would be to get a transplant, attaching another creature’s eyes to your body, using it on your own. However, that requires major alterations in the brain, making it risky and troublesome.’

“Speaking of which, Nadia hasn’t appeared for a while now. Has she given up?” Garen frowned.

‘Impossible. After being silent for such a long time, there’s a high chance she has developed a strong attack tactic. You’d better prepare yourself,’ Black Sethe flatly denied Garen’s hypothesis. ‘As for your right eye, if you plan on hiding it from your parents, your best bet is to use your Fantasy Fist.’

Garen also understood that. He just sighed and moved on.

He shifted his sights to his own attribute pane.

‘Garen Thomas.

Strength 7. Agility 7. Vitality 10. Intelligence 11. Potential 7989%. Soul Limit 30.’

The attributes with more than 10 points now required more than 100 potential points just to increase them by one point. This frightening point requirement made Garen give up on raising the other attributes. He thought it would be better to save up his points to get to 12 points of Intelligence, gaining the double hit ability.

On the other hand, he had not met his family in a very long time, which was very weird for a child. Since his right eye couldn’t be repaired, he had no choice but to use his Fantasy Fist.

The information on the Fantasy Fist flashed in his mind.

His vision swiftly shifted towards his skill pane, in the panel filled with different abilities and skills, he found the Fantasy Fist.

‘Fantasy Fist: Level 1 — Memory Loss (Total of 4 levels)’

‘A mysterious and scary ancient form of martial arts. Uses sound and air flow to damage or vibrate the opponents’ brains, creating a confusion effect on the opponents. Once hailed as the most feared secret martial arts.’

The Fantasy Fist, as a top-tier martial arts technique, naturally required quite a lot of potential points to level. The system behind learning this technique was absurdly complex. Every level was as tedious as decrypting a code, and it wasn’t something a normal person could achieve.

However, Garen was different; even his lowest attributes were at 7 points and as his Intelligence was at 11 points, his memory and comprehension level had reached an inhuman level. Furthermore, he was once a researcher back in the Totem World and had a good understanding of advanced neurology. Naturally, this made learning Fantasy Fist a simple task for him. A lot of the theories and principles behind it were nothing but just a refresher course for him.

For a top tier martial arts technique, the first level should require 5 points…

Garen’s vision was focussed on the icon. After 3 seconds, the icon flashed, then once again turning clear, the text displayed also changed.

‘Fantasy Fist: Level 2– Delirium (Total of 4 levels)’

‘An increased effect duration, causing confusion on all 5 senses.’

Glancing at his potential points, he’d used up 5 points. That didn’t faze Garen, and he continued to focus on the Fantasy Fist.

Except for his Flight of the Waterbird’s Profound, there weren’t any moves from the Waterbird’s Profound that required his full potential. Even Flight of the Phoenix was the result of combining Flight with West Phoenix Fist, or else it would merely be a third-rate secret technique. It could never reach that level on its own.

If he leveled Fantasy Fist now, he would be able to widen his arsenal. After all, Fantasy Fist was a top-class technique.

Chapter 733: Fusion and Masks 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Shortly after, he reached the 3rd level.

‘Level 3 –Memory Alter.’

‘Changes memories, creates illusions and disrupts the opponents’ senses of their surroundings. At this level, one will obtain the prerequisite to learn the first Profound for this technique — Radiant World.’

This was the exact move that Ninox used against Tu Lan last time, forcing her opponent into an illusory world. However, because she didn’t have enough energy, she was countered by Tu Lan’s Blood Breed ability Illusive Counter, who then managed to break out of her world.

If it managed to succeed, Tu Lan would be stuck in an illusory world fighting against an undying Ninox. No matter how many times she killed her, Ninox would just revive again at full strength.

This would continue until Tu Lan exhausted all her energy. However, even though the Ninox in that world was just an illusion, if she got hit, it would still damage her physical body. This was the textbook case of how one’s mental state could affect one’s physical condition.

Lastly, there was the 4th level.

Garen once again focused for 3 seconds. The icon for Fantasy Fist blurred briefly once again, then immediately cleared up. There seemed to be slight changes to the icon as well.

‘Fantasy Fist: Level 4 –Vanish.’

‘All enemies being suppressed by this aura will momentarily lose their consciousness, falling under the control of the user. This effect will be automatically applied. Any opponent that comes into physical contact with the user lose partial control over parts of their body. Against weak-willed opponents, it may cause them to enter an eternal slumber, causing brain damage, and more.’

‘Final Profound –Reincarnate (Eternal control over a weak-willed opponent, forcing them to unconsciously obey your commands) – Not Learned. The user requires 1 or more Pearl Flowers.’

Looking at the effects of the final Profound, even Garen was in utter shock.

The strength of Fantasy Fist had already reached such a frightening degree. However, the last material required was a Pearl Flower. Garen knew about this flower, but unfortunately, it did not seem to exist in this world; he’d read about it in a botany book back in the Totem World under the category ‘Special Plants”.

At this moment, he suddenly realized that all the moves he usually used worked with the Waterbird Fist as their base. This third-rate fist technique, when combined with the West Phoenix Fist, could achieve a whole new height. Adding to the effects of the Demonic Book, its progress rate was drastically increased, its final strength largely increased and training period shortened, making it an advanced-level technique.

He also understood that the things he learned at this point were getting more and more diverse. The four big killer moves he created in the Secret Technique World were no longer enough to meet the requirements of the current level of combat, causing him to be unable to activate the full potential of the fifth star of the skills.

Having an excessively diverse arsenal was a troublesome thing for normal people. However, for Garen, he sorted out every single ability and technique he had, and only had to care about which secret technique he should select.

Now that Fantasy Fist had reached level 4, its strength could also be considered to be a level higher, and so his choices have also increased.

Reincarnate was undoubtedly strong, being able to forever alter a person’s consciousness. However, to Garen, this skill could not reach its full potential in a battle scenario. Furthermore, it even required a rare material.

His fighting style was largely based on brute force, fitting his strong and fearless personality. However, the combat style that best utilized Fantasy Fists was a more stealthy style. Unlike his other secret techniques, it did not enhance the user’s physical abilities and was purely a control technique used to gain an advantage over opponents. It was the polar opposite of his brute force style.

“Well… I still need to fuse the Fantasy Fist into my fighting style somehow,” Garen started to brainstorm. He went back to the table he usually used to write the Demonic Book and pulled out a pen, slowly twirling it between his fingers.

‘The Fantasy Fist’s effectivity relies on the mental and spiritual strength of the user. Except for Nadia and other void creatures, who do you think has a stronger mental and spiritual strength than you?’ Black Sethe said.

“That’s true,” Garen nodded, “but the two are still different secret techniques. One can only use one secret technique at any point in time because of the multiple overlapping variables within the meridian system. When I use Waterbird Fist, I won’t be able to use Fantasy Fist. Being able to learn both Secret Techniques was only because of my current strength, and because the parts of the meridian system for Fantasy Fist and Waterbird Fist don’t overlap too much. If it was an average person, they would’ve already suffered internal damage when they started to train.”

Garen frowned.

‘Then, how about you try fusing them?’ Black Sethe hinted.

“Fusion?” Garen suddenly remembered the days back when he’d first arrived in the Secret Technique World, where he kept trying to combined different martial arts. Those fusions created terrifyingly strong results. “That’s worth a shot.”

His vision returned to his Skill Pane.

Waterbird Fist had already reached Level 4, and there weren’t any requirements displayed for its Profounds.

Garen’s vision moved repeatedly from the two secret techniques with the intent of fusing the two. Suddenly, the two icons started to slightly vibrate, creating a miraculous result.

The two icons started glowing red and started to beat like a heart, one stronger than the other. This seemed to insinuate which technique would become the main and which the sub. After a while, contrary to Garen’s expectations, the far superior Fantasy Fist’s red glow started to fade, whilst the third rate Waterbird Fist started to glow even brighter.

The icon for Fantasy Fist slowly started to blur out. Together with the text detailing the technique, it slowly disappeared. On the other hand, the icon for Waterbird Fist started glowing even brighter. The icon almost looked like it was stained with bright red blood.

Pak! A soft sound could be heard, something like a steel wire being cut in half. Garen could now see that Fantasy Fist had completely disappeared.

Waterbird Fist also had some new changes.

‘Mirage Waterbird Fist: Level 4 (Total 4 levels)

A top class technique created by fusing the Fantasy Fist into the Waterbird Fist. The user can affect an opponent’s state of mind through his movements. It has 4 Profounds. The final Profound –Joyous Reincarnate.’

This new secret technique wasn’t like his previous results, where the fusion had led to the strengthening of one of the techniques. This time, it merged the effects of both techniques.

As Fantasy Fist and Waterbird Fist didn’t have too many overlapping variables in the Meridian system, this allowed them to support each other. The two secret techniques managed to merge and become a completely new technique.

However, when Garen attempted to follow the blood and qi circulation of the new technique, he felt that the blood flow used by this technique was similar to what both Fantasy Fist and Waterbird Fist used. There was one trouble that he noticed.

The areas with overlapping blood flows.

Even though there was very little overlapping, two of the overlapped areas have already started to hurt.

The first area was at the center of his left inner wrist, while the other was right in the middle of his lower back.

These two areas were coincidentally the areas that require the most blood flow for this new technique.

Hypothetically, if both the original techniques will require blood flow in a certain area, by merging the two techniques it will require blood flow to the same areas twice. This indirectly doubled the burden on the user’s body.

“If even a body like mine would feel discomfort, looks like this new technique can’t be taught to others, I have to train it myself…” Garen frowned.

‘Can you tweak it in any way?’ Black Sethe suggested.

“Sadly I can’t…” Garen shook his head, “These two overlapping areas are key areas, they can’t be replaced.”

‘Well you win some you lose some,’ Garen lightly chuckled, comforting him. ‘Let’s find a place to test out its strength.’

Garen nodded and walked out of the reading room. He walked down the corridor slowly but swiftly, he moved more than 10 meters just with a couple of steps.

Passing through the student training hall, he saw a few silhouettes engrossed in their training. Upon closer inspection, it was the students who had slower progress, and the sight made Garen happy and satisfied.

After the 2nd batch of students, this 3rd batch of new students was no longer directly under his control as he felt no need to control this batch of students. He left it up to his 3 best pupils, Hochman, Dahm, and Cece to choose who to guide. The remaining would then be left to Quentin, Xander, and the others to deal with.

All of his students from the 1st batch of students in the Combat Club now had the ability to release their own soul seed primer, as they have all reached a certain level of proficiency in their Secret Techniques. Although it was much weaker than Garen’s, it still managed to establish control to a certain extent.

This also helped further develop their own strengths.

Silently passing through the training hall, Garen walked past a few more areas to finally arrive at the pet feeding area of the palace.

This was a circular empty atrium area, with cages of different sizes placed all around. Some of the cages had an animal, and some were empty. Occasionally, you could hear the sounds of dogs and cats.

The air conditioner was set to a higher temperature here, unlike other areas where the temperature was lowered to train the students.

Garen looked through the cages one by one. He stopped at a cage with white cats with an unknown owner. Inside the cage was a nest of 3 kittens, all of them pure white. They looked like 3 cute little furballs from afar. As Garen went closer, the 3 palm-sized kittens all started mewing softly and snuggled close to each other, as if they were cowering in fear.

Garen reached his finger out with a smile, lightly poking the cage.

Ting…

A shapeless wave started rippling from the part of the steel cage that Garen touched.

The wave rapidly covered the three kittens, then quickly disappeared.

The steel cage cracked; the Waterbird Fist’s monstrous power had somehow managed to break through the steel bar, creating a small gap just enough for the kittens to wriggle out. However, the three kittens completely did not notice the newly created gap and remained motionless in the cage.

Garen stood up with a satisfied smile on his face.

“Mirage Waterbird Fist seems to be able to affect animals, though it’s not very strong,” he looked at the gaze of the kittens, they completely did not notice that the cage was broken, almost like they felt that they were still locked in the cage.

“What’s sad about this is that the effects weren’t completely intentional. As the illusions induced were natural, this cannot be used against void creatures.”

‘You can take the initiative and try it out on Nadia, it’s also a good opportunity to go check on her movements,’ Black Sethe suggested.

“Good idea.”

Garen agreed. Nadia hadn’t made any moves for such a long time that it almost felt like the calm before a storm.

He stood up and left the pet area, heading straight to the secret room in the palace.

After he left, the three kittens still did not move. In the reflection in their eyes, the cage was still completely intact…

Chapter 734: Fusion and Masks 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the same empty hall, a silhouette was stuck to the center of the wall, tightly bound by countless strands of green webbing, unable to escape. He seemed to be struggling in pain.

On both sides of the hall were rows of tall white statues, all depicting a humanoid being holding a huge sword up high, creating a solemn atmosphere.

Garen once again stood in this hall, before the wall shrouded in green webbing. He reached his arm out to touch the green webs, but there was a sturdy glass layer preventing him from touching it. He had attempted to break it in the past, but his efforts were futile; this glass was far stronger than any material he could’ve imagined.

Garen scanned the surroundings, the floor, and the walls, they were all covered in a layer of dust. It seemed that no one had been here for a long time.

“Nadia?” Garen called in a low voice.

There was no reply.

His voice only continuously echoed through the hall.

Garen frowned, as this was not his first time coming to this dream realm. This was his eighth time entering this place. In the past, he would come every so often to have a lethal duel with Nadia.

Similarly, every time he entered this place, Nadia would immediately appear.

However, this time Nadia didn’t appear.

‘She didn’t show up? That’s impossible,’ Black Sethe’s voice rang.

“Maybe she got wrapped up with some other stuff?” Garen guessed.

‘Maybe.’

Garen frowned even more. He had a bad feeling about this.

******

Bottom of the Holy Fist Palace Mountain

In a small town

A white car slowly stopped in front of a small building. It was Garen’s house. In the warm sunshine, the car door opened, and out from the driver’s seat came a handsome young man, with hair as bright as gold.

The man was in a white suit, and his lean figure gave off a fully balanced impression. He gently smiled at the cute young girl running out of the building.

“Lil’ Vivien…”

“Brother, welcome home!”

The young girl’s slim youthful body dived straight into Garen’s embrace. He swung her around in a circle.

“Mom and Dad are waiting for you inside!” Vivien seemed extremely happy.

Garen raised his head and saw his father Emmer looking down with a strict expression from the 2nd-floor window.

He smiled, then walked into the building.

Behind him, more and more cars slowly stopped near the same building. A few men emerged from the cars and patrolled its vicinity.

Walking through the doorway, Garen saw a big table at the center of the room, with something covered by a black cloth.

Bang!!

A frightening explosion sound rang from behind him. Just as he had let his guard down, his body was covered with countless party streamers.

His younger sister Vivien, his older brother Jason, Alicia, and even his mother Trish had blasted party poppers at Garen.

With the chaotic party poppers, Garen was completely covered with streamers, looking like a weird rainbow-colored creature.

“Happy Birthday!!”

They shouted in unison, their voices echoing in the room.

The black cloth was pulled away, revealing a giant birthday cake at a shocking half-meter height. On it, “Happy 21st Birthday Garen” was written in pastel buttercream.

Garen’s expression couldn’t be seen as he was covered completely by streamers, however, his eyes gave off an indescribable feeling. He always had birthday celebrations even back in the secret technique world and the totem world, but this was the first time he had such a grand and amazing celebration…

“You guys shouldn’t have…” he softly said, but his voice was overshadowed by their giggling. In the midst of this chaotic and joyous celebration, everyone was just popping party poppers left and right.

Garen helplessly shook his head, then walked over to the sofa at the side while brushing off the streamers draped all over him.

When everyone had their fun and started to feel tired, the room had already become a mess. Luckily, the cake had a huge glass lid covering it, otherwise it would’ve already been completely covered by streamers.

“Today is Garen’s birthday! Let’s sing him a celebratory song. Not just the normal birthday song, let’s sing this song I’ve written!” at this point, Trish didn’t even look like a mother, but more like a kid cheerfully shouting.

In their eyes, Garen’s eyes were fine, he wasn’t wearing a mask and he had his same old face.

Snap!

The sound of a camera shutter was heard.

Garen’s sight immediately shifted before he stood up and walked over to his little sister.

“I thought this camera was broken?”

Pointing at the camera, the internal components started to vibrate ever so slightly, causing some sort of change. On the surface it looked perfectly fine, though in actuality, the memory card had been damaged by his vibrations.

“Is it broken? Then I’ll use my phone to take a photo!” Vivien asked skeptically.

“There’s no need for the trouble,” Garen picked his sister up and tossed her onto the sofa as she screamed and giggled in a high-pitched voice.

At that moment everyone started to play around again.

No one had noticed that on the reflection of the black television screen, Garen was wearing that strange and mysterious mask.

*****

Memphis Forest — Moon River

As the largest tropical forest in the world, Memphis Forest had countless unexplored and unmapped areas.

Even the best research and exploration teams have not managed to completely unravel all the secrets of the various flora and fauna, swamps, crevices, unique natural terrain, strong geomagnetic disruptions, and even the existence of prehistoric beasts in this area.

Some authorities from the Blood Breeds once brought a team over here, boasting that they would fully explore the entire Memphis Forest and share the findings of his expedition to the world. However, expectedly, after losing more than half of his team, he was forced to retreat.

In addition to that, he himself had almost lost his own life in that expedition. Despite having sacrificed so much, he barely gained any reward.

He only managed to successfully explore barely one-third of Memphis Forest.

At this moment, Dahm, with his own team of elites that he’d personally chosen and trained, was trotting down the same path that that exact expedition team had used last time.

They were surrounded by dense tropical plant life and flying venomous insects. They could see a scourge of bloodthirsty mosquitoes buzzing about, circling above the team. Furthermore, every so often, there would be some sort of red insect that resembles a leech dropping down from above, trying to burrow into their necks.

Among the tall grass by their feet, there were countless spiderwebs tangled all over. Every few moments, there would be a team member accidentally stepping in a spiderweb, getting it stuck all over his legs.

Suddenly, the loud chaotic chirps of a flock of startled birds came from above; there was no doubt that there were ferocious beasts ahead.

“Be careful.”

One of the team members raised his arm up and grabbed something. Out of nowhere, he pulled out a green rope-like object.

It was a small green snake with dark green spots all over its body. Looking at the triangular shape of its head, it was definitely a venomous snake.

With a crack, he snapped the snake in half at the location of its heart [1]. The member who had been the targeted prey of the snake immediately thanked his teammate for saving his life.

In the 9 hours they had been in the forest, these types of occurrences had become commonplace. Hence, everyone was constantly on high alert, ready to counter against anything from their surroundings.

Dahm, while looking at the map in his hands, walked to the middle of the team. There was a large number of geomagnetic disruptions coming from this location, visibly affecting everything that was made of metal or used electricity.

“The second Moon River is right ahead. Everyone, be on your guard,” Dahm loudly ordered.

“Oh!”

Everyone loudly replied.

Overlooking the environmental disruptions, back when they’d first approached the first Moon River, they had encountered a spotted scorpion with venom that was extremely potent. This scorpion was only palm-sized, but it was extremely fast and darted around as fast as lightning. By the time one saw it, one would already have been stung by it.

Even Dahm could barely keep up with the frightening speed of this scorpion.

As someone who had top-class skills, for him to barely be able to keep up with a creature like this, he felt slightly ashamed, but he had also fully understood the fearsomeness of this forest.

After going around a few large trees that looked to be centuries old, they were suddenly greeted by a long flowing river that resembled a silver silk ribbon.

The river had a bit of curvature, was easily several hundred meters in length and almost 30 meters in width, forming a shape of a crescent moon. Sunlight glowing from above reflected in the flowing water, making the river glimmer with a tinge of gold. It was truly a mesmerizing scene.

“The second Moon River,” Garen let out a sigh of relief and raised his hand. “Proceed with caution! Everyone spread out and pay attention to gaps and crevices.”

The group started spreading out according to his orders, stationing themselves by the riverside.

“Something feels off?” Dahm’s instincts were telling him that there was something wrong with the current situation at the Moon River, but he just couldn’t think of what it was.

He continued to observe his men searching around by the riverside. The magnetic fields here were a lot weaker, allowing them to use their tools and apparatus. They were using plastic detectors, rapidly searching all around.

“M-Mr Dahm, you should tell them to be more careful. There… might be a lot of ferocious beasts over here, since there aren’t any animals drinking by the river…” the female guide he’d forcefully dragged along voiced out with a tremor in her voice. Along the way, she had borne witness to Dahm’s fearsome abilities.

“No animals drinking?” Dahm plainly said. “What’s there to be afraid of? It’s most likely just because the water is infested with alligators or something.”

He glanced over at the Moon River, still frowning; he felt that this wasn’t the source of his unease.

Judging by their pace, they were already quite deep within Memphis Forest, and they have already reached the area where the previous expedition had last reached. However, he still could not sense a hostile intent strong enough to threaten the someone from the Blood Breeds.

“Wait!! Threaten the Blood Breeds!?” Dahm suddenly realized something. If they didn’t encounter anything on their way here, then the only other possibility was a one-time-encounter of frightful levels!?

Sploosh!!

Emerging rapidly from the water, a gigantic creature appeared. Looking like a dark shadow, it attacked the members at the riverside with lightning fast speed.

“Careful!!” Dahm was facing another of the same terrifying creature, and the tremendous pressure coming from it was almost suffocating even for him.

Ahh!!!

In a flurry of screams, he saw his men all getting injured one by one. Even the female guide was swept into the river by the monster’s tail, immediately dyeing the water around her body red. There was undoubtedly no chance of her surviving that.

“Fucking lowlife!!” still hearing the screams of anguish from around him, Dahm’s face flushed with rage and ferocity, as his right hand morphed into a knife that he slashed furiously at the beast.

Chapter 735: Change 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Shing! Shing! Shing!

With three bloody flashes, three of the monsters were slashed open, causing a blood mist to spurt everywhere.

Dahm wiped off the blood on his face and dashed swiftly to his team. Only the elites of the team were left fending against the monsters; the rest had either been swept into the water or were heavily injured.

Bam! Bam! Bam! Bam!

With a chain of continuous explosions, the monsters were destroyed one by one, leaving behind only bloody mist.

As Dahm was attempting to save the guide and one of his team members who had just been dragged into the water, the sound of machine gunshots filled the air.

They finally managed to see what the huge beast lurking in the water looked like.

The black monster looked like a hippopotamus with two horns on their heads, resembling those of a buffalo. At a size of almost 3 meters in height, it seemed to be a species of the giant hippopotamus.

Additionally, on its back was a huge tail that resembled that of a crocodile’s, muscled and scaly. It was a terrifying sight.

However, under Dahm’s flurry of attacks, these monsters were like sitting ducks. With every strike, another one would be killed. In just a short moment, he killed more than 20 of them.

Roar!!!

Suddenly, the ground behind him split open as a 5 meter tall humongous black beast dug out furiously from the ground and lunged towards Dahm’s back. It was speeding in like a black wave, flinging black mud, wilted leaves, and branches into the airs, rousing a thick rotting smell.

Dahm immediately turned around, facing the lunging beast. His vision was completely filled with the monster’s size.

His pupils started to contract. He saw that there was a strange mask embedded in the monster’s abdomen. That mask seemed so familiar!!

******

Whoosh!!

With a gust of wind, Garen appeared at the top of the guest hall’s throne. He slowly sat down.

In the bottom right seat, an androgynous-looking Caucasian with a white veil was seated. There was a cinnabar gem embedded in the center of his brow, giving off an Indian vibe.

On the left seats were 2 of the underlings sent by AG. They were both young witches wearing tight skirts.

The mask Garen was wearing all this time had, for some unknown reason, turned completely silver. The eyes all over the head also started to seem much more active.

Through the eyeholes of the mask, he peered down at his guests.

“How is AG’s progress? It looks like it’s quite successful, right?” Garen asked softly.

“Lord Holy Fist, Lord AG’s progress have been successfully progressing. The motive for our visit was for us Dark Color witches to seek aid from the Holy Fist Palace,” the leading witch spoke earnestly.

“Regarding the aid, taking my friendship with AG into consideration, I will accept the proposition. I’ll leave the negotiation between you and Hochman. In exchange, we also require your help regarding some issues,” Garen nodded. He wasn’t actually on good terms with the Dark Colors leader Nasira, so naturally, he wouldn’t help her without any compensation.

“We are at a standstill against the Blood Breeds, and if we break the stalemate it may lead to unpredictable results,” Garen’s vision moved to the other party, the Caucasian representative from the witches’ main force.

“So, the self-proclaimed representative from the Witches Association, what is your motive for coming here?”

The veiled Caucasian smiled as he stood up, calmly bowing down before Garen, his hands in a praying hands pose.

“I bring forth a declaration of friendship from Lion Mother. Maybe Lord Holy Fist would want help from my master?”

“Oh?” Garen’s curiosity was piqued. “Tell me, what exactly would I need help in?”

The Caucasian did not reply, but he just lightly touched his own right eye.

Garen glared down.

“You have a way to recover my eyes?”

“I do not, but my master might be able to,” the Caucasian politely answered.

Garen paused for a moment as if he was thinking about some things.

“Is there any way for you to prove this?” he asked after pondering for a short moment.

If even Black Sethe was helpless, to the Lion Mother who was from this world, this kind of injury should be incomprehensible to her.

A wound from the Nine-Headed Dragon Queen Nadia was not so easily cured.

However, most importantly, for them to voluntarily offer to help repair his eyes, they must have done a lot of preparation. Thus, as compensation, they definitely desired something great.

In this world, Garen’s one and only fear was the First Apostle Ashen, and everyone else was merely ants in his eyes. Only Ashen stood as a threat to him. However, this was only on the Blood Breed forces side, and he had not pried into the witches side of things. He lacked an understanding of the types of tricks they used.

Listening to Garen’s doubt, the Caucasian smiled. He pulled out a pure white lily and tossed it into the air. It then naturally flew towards Garen.

Catching the incoming lily, Garen took a deep breath, he felt overwhelmed by the strong aroma, slightly mesmerized by it. More importantly, his right eye started to ache slightly, causing him to shiver.

“My lord wishes that if we manage to heal your wound, the Holy Fist Palace and the Blood Breeds will be able to coexist peacefully. This way, there would no longer be any bloodshed in this world…”

The Caucasian had a solemn look on his face, Garen could see that this was not an act, but rather a true desire to achieve peace.

“Ceasefire? I am not against it, but I fear the Blood Breed side would be against it,” Garen calmly said.

His overall strength was far weaker than the Blood Breeds and a ceasefire would definitely benefit him, so he definitely wouldn’t reject such a proposal.

“For the Blood Breed side, naturally, my master will try to change their minds,” the Caucasian nodded. “However, we have one more request before we can heal your eye.”

“Oh? What request is that? Tell me,” Garen remained calm. The Lion Mother was the only one from the witches side who had an existence at a Death Apostle level. For her to be able to influence and suppress the Blood Breed, she was definitely no random person. What’s more, her abilities could have some effect against a wound from Nadia, which largely exceeded his expectations.

“My master wishes that you would stop collecting the Sleepless Faces.” The Caucasian said with his head lowered.

The atmosphere suddenly sunk, as Garen’s body emitted a suppressing aura. This aura was so strong that the people below would feel as if their hearts were sealed behind a lock, and that they were suffocating.

The Caucasian continued on impassively with his head down, “The Sleepless Faces are the cause of all these troubles and will bring disaster to the world. My master hopes that Lord Holy Fist can give up on collecting them.”

With the atmosphere in the room getting more and more serious, Garen was still seated motionlessly on top of his throne, calmly glaring at this Caucasian. Despite clearly suppressing the aura at his heart, making it difficult for him to even breathe, the Caucasian was still standing motionlessly in the room, almost as if dismissing the effects of the suppression.

This seemed to be supported by the willpower of his belief.

“We’ll talk about this once you actually manage to repair my eye,” Garen finally answered. The strong suppressing pressure started to fade away as he started speaking.

“I will send your message to my master,” the Caucasian politely bowed.

After the representative from the Witches Association and Lion Mother left, the Holy Fist Palace guest hall was once again in silence.

Hochman and Quentin appeared from the corner.

“Master, the witch organization that the Lion Mother represents are the self-proclaimed protectors of world peace, and it’s filled with sad people. They have also come to warn me before. What an annoying bunch. This time I think it’s not just something as simple as trying to ask for a ceasefire,” Quentin frowned. She was in charge of recon and information collection, and she definitely had a certain amount of understanding of the strength of Lion Mother’s group.

“These people are using world peace as a pretense, but we don’t know what their true motives are. We shouldn’t trust them so easily,” Hochman chimed in.

Garen lightly tapped on the armrests of his throne, signaling that he was thinking.

“I know.”

The collection of the Sleepless Faces was not something that could be stopped. These masks were one of his main sources of potential points, and they could also block Nadia’s movement. No matter how you look at it, it was a precious treasure that he needed to have.

However, the Lion Mother’s mysterious abilities which could even affect the wound on his eye, this made Garen wary. He twirled the lily in his hands; the hint of aura it had had already dispersed, and this was now just a normal water lily.

The slight feeling in his right eye had also disappeared.

“Lion Mother…” Garen sniffed the lily once again, showing an amused expression on his face.

******

Outside the Holy Fist Palace

The Caucasian was slowly moving down the mountain path. Passing through the main gate of the Holy Fist Palace, he smiled at the two guards stationed over there. With light footsteps, he sped up his pace as he continued down.

After walking a short distance, he turned back, looking at the Holy Fist Palace.

The white palace was sitting on top of the peak of the snowy mountain, looking like a place from a legend. Outside the Palace, groups of cloaked figures kept entering the gate, showing their identification tags. These people were selected from all over the world to come over to the Holy Fist Palace for training. They were either chosen by the Combat Club or the Nighthawks, and all of them had stable blood and qi and light footsteps despite the freezing weather.

What the Caucasian found to be weirder was that on the way back from the Holy Fist Palace, he’d met with groups of Blood Breed and Vampires who had come to this place. The aurae they were emitting seemed to have been altered, appearing stronger than before but also slightly weird.

“Master was right, Holy Fist Palace… It’s the source of all this…” the Caucasian raised his head, looking at the grey sky. That unimaginable feeling of pressure and the roaring thunder, all of this managed to accentuate the strong force that this place was!

No matter if it was humans or the Blood Breed, the Holy Fist Palace’s arms were slowly spreading to every corner of the world. Furthermore, this force was expanding at a rapid pace.

The Caucasian started to feel a fear arise in his heart.

He thought back to the people he met on his way down here. Whether human or Blood Breed, all of these people had a sort of a passion as if they held absolute admiration and loyalty towards the Holy Fist Palace.

Chapter 736: Change 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He didn’t know how this ideal had spread out so quickly within such a short period of time. However, he knew that if this were to be left untouched, it could be very troublesome.

He wasn’t sure if his instincts were accurate though.

One of the main characteristics of the Holy Fist Palace was something that everyone would experience while practicing, the strange excitement induced by the Demonic Book.

Not only they could experience an excitement that was far superior to sex while practicing, they could become stronger as well. This path was so perfect that everyone would definitely choose it! It was the perfect choice for the modern people who wanted success within a short amount of time without any hardship.

They were able to enjoy this sensation while strengthening their bodies. Frankly, a lot of people completely didn’t care whether they had become stronger at all, as they were addicted to the adrenaline rush created during their practices.

This was the terrifying part of the Holy Fist Palace.

Everyone was very well informed about this as the models and practice methods were advertised during the International Combat Competition held by Dahm and Hochman.

The two major Marshalls of the Holy Fist Palace, who had created their own individual branches of fist styles. In addition to the three Secret Techniques from the Holy Fist Palace, there was a total of five fist techniques. These fist techniques were nicknamed the Five Major Fists by hobbyists.

It meant that these fist techniques ruled everything else and couldn’t be compared with other fist techniques!

An extreme sensation could be felt as one practiced one of these five fist techniques. Under Garen’s guidance, Dahm and Hochman were able to simplify their fist techniques even further and create a completed lower-tier fist technique structure.

There were at least ten middle-tier fist techniques from the Five Major Fists. Most of these fist techniques were able to achieve a certain overall effect, their practicing requirements were very simple and one could definitely feel the sensation of excitement as well. However, the downside was that they were not powerful enough.

With these middle and lower-tier fist techniques as a means to spread out to the beginners, those hobbyists who had experienced the addictive sensation would definitely turn into fanatics and spread praise of the Holy Fist Palace through word of mouth.

They could obtain happiness, a stronger body, and aura while training. Once they reached a certain level, they could obtain a tremendous amount of financial support from the Holy Fist Palace and get a well-paid salary.

The most important thing was that once one reached a certain height and showed some results, there was a possibility one would be noticed by a General Level. They then would be invited into the inner circle of the combat club and become an official member of the Holy Fist Palace. After that, they would qualify to learn a stronger and more advanced fist technique.

With this rewarding leveling system, it had attracted countless elites and talented people.

After learning the beginner lower tier fist techniques, some of the elites who had battle experience were able to understand the unreasonable power behind these fist techniques. With the influence of their own teachings, the Holy Fist Palace became even more powerful than before.

In a blink of an eye, a few months had passed.

The Holy Fist Palace’s influence snowballed as it expanded rapidly throughout America, where the simplified Five Major Fists had dominated the whole region.

There even were martial artist hobbyists from other countries that came to learn in America. After learning the fist technique for some time, the technique and skills had started a new trend of martial arts.

The world was into martial arts all of a sudden.

Within this period, the Secret Party of the Blood Breeds was in a temporary truce with the Light Party. After the major battle which had occurred recently, both parties had finally settled down and talk under the mediation of Lion Mother.

Both parties had put their grudges aside in the face of the threat from the Holy Fist Palace.

Within this period, Garen had isolated himself from the society and the Holy Fist Palace was practically managed by the two main Marshalls, Hochman and Dahm. Both of them had obtained their strength directly from Garen and they had no hope of getting out of Garen’s grasp, especially after they’d acknowledged that fact. On the contrary, they didn’t feel too conflicted being under control by him, as Garen didn’t really control them at all.

The Holy Fist Palace became stronger over time as both of them had gathered a lot of power under them. Under similar logic, the four people below them had expanded their authorities and influenced as well and had been stationed at different locations in America as representatives of the Holy Fist Palace. At the same time, Dahm had extended his influence to the military as he handed down the simplified version of Death Waterbird King’s Fist Technique to the military.

If not for the highly focused attacks from the heavy machine guns or the machine guns that had no blind spot, Dahm’s elite underling would be unstoppable.

Naturally, it would be impossible to defend against wide-scale bombing. However, practicing the fist technique would not only increase the battle power of every individual soldier, it would also improve their five senses together with the Shooting Shadow Secret Technique.

The simplified Shooting Shadow Secret Technique was considered a flawless technique to learn for the soldiers stationed on the outskirts, as they would be able to cover most distances.

Naturally, the will and aura of a normal civilian was no match for soldiers’. The most important thing was the mentality of war, which every soldier should have so that remote operations would not be inconsistent.

This had solved the issue of not having enough people for the Holy Fist Palace when they fought against the Witch and Blood Breeds.

After all, Garen’s Soul Primer could only control a very small amount of people. Similarly, Hochman and Dahm’s Soul Primer couldn’t be used on many people as well. Hence, the only people who were willing to fight to their deaths were the Nighthawks and the fugitives under the two Marshals. Even though the number of people who had died in the Wellington’s war was terrible, the supplements to replace them from the military had greatly lessened the Holy Fist Palace’s recklessness.

This was especially true when many young and energetic officers joined them, resulting in a massive expansion of the Holy Fist Palace’s power and influence.

Garen had already taken countermeasures against hypnosis from the Blood Breeds. By using the Fantasy Fist as its foundation, he had invented a way to suppress this hypnosis. After the experiment was a success, one would be immune to the effect of a lower-tier hypnosis. Those who had a very strong and firm will could directly ignore the hypnosis at such a level.

Under these circumstances, the humans who had been suppressed and enslaved by the Blood Breeds had finally found a way to retaliate and joined the Holy Fist Palace. As they had been suppressed for a long time, these people vented their frustration and the Holy Fist Palace started to fight against the Blood Breeds. As the two parties had suffered severe casualties through the war, the middle-level and lower-level blood breeds were defenseless against these former slaves.

Throughout this oppression period, excluding the two parties, a lot of secluded Blood Breeds who did not wish to be involved had suffered as well.

************

“Run!!!”

Multiple human figures were running swiftly while panting in a bamboo forest in the dark, with at least ten pursuers hot on their heels. These pursuers were very agile and their breathing was long and rhythmic. They were holding clear black assault rifles with sharp knives attached at the muzzle of the guns, which could be detached as melee weapons.

On a small hill nearby, there was a group of soldiers in black special ops uniform guarding two young military officers. These two officers were observing the situation inside the bamboo forest with their night-vision binoculars.

“These damn mixed blood bastards! How dare they reject Colonel Raven’s goodwill during the previous reception. It was very fortunate for her that the Colonel had taken a liking to her!”

A white officer scolded softly with a chilling gaze.

“Blood Breeds will always act like one. Although she is but a Lower-Level Blood Breed, she is still one of the beings with long lifespans so it’s normal for her to reject him,” the other man replied calmly. “However, Colonel Raven is one of the elites in my combat club who was able to obtain the teachings of an advanced level fist technique and become the direct disciple of General Crusoe. If everything goes well, the General himself may even pass down the Fist King to him, and he’ll become the third generation of the Fist King. She would be ignorant if she still rejects him then.”

The former officer went along with him and smiled.

The truth was that he knew the Blood Breed girl who was being pursued. He once tried to chase after her as well but had been rejected by her. This made him bitter, and he had been nursing this hatred within him all this while. It was mostly him who had manipulated the Colonel to chase after her and get rejected too.

He found a tremendous amount of sadistic pleasure in managing to pull down a princess from the very top and crushing her beneath his feet.

Suddenly, a guttural scream could be heard from the bamboo forest.

It sounded like the voice of one of the pursuing soldiers.

Two officer’s expressions changed all of the sudden.

They gestured with their hands and the special ops around them gathered and entered into the bamboo forest in a blink of an eye.

These people had undergone the simplified fist technique training at the Holy Fist Palace and each and every one of them possessed excellent physical characteristics. Soon, cursing and angry shouts could be heard ahead.

“Damned Monsters!!”

“Kill him!”

“Tom has been beaten! Quick, bring in the blood cleanser!!”

“Quick, quick!!”

Torchlight soon lit up in the darkness up front and a special ops soldier returned to report the situation to the two officers.

“Sir, we have discovered a hidden camp of the Blood Breeds about one hundred and fifty yards up front. There is a total of twenty-three Blood Breeds and Vampires hiding there.”

“That many?” the cold looking officer was slightly surprised.

“The target seems to be a pedigree member of this small household,” the soldier replied softly. “Sir, please give us a command!”

The officer hesitated for a moment as he looked at his partner by his side, who looked back at him as well as he waited for his suggestion.

He gritted his teeth and as he was about to order them to retreat when the image of the cold and arrogant girl flashed through his mind.

“Ah!!”

Another scream could be heard from the soldiers up front.

“Open fire! Open Fire!!” everyone started screaming as gunshots echoed through the bamboo forest.

“All members engage in battle! Kill every single one of them!!” the officer had made his decision. If they were not careful, all of them would die at the hands of twenty plus Lower-Level Blood Breeds even though they were the practitioners of the Fist Technique.

“Someone called the Wittsburg nearby for support!”

On that night in the west of America, a war between the military and Blood Breeds had emerged.

*************

Boom!!

A powerful punch by a pale fist was sent into the vampire’s chin and the vampire was sent flying away, crashing into a shop’s display window at the side of the road. The window was shattered and millions of shards scattered in all directions.

“You guys are the worst parasites!” the white muscular man stared down at the beaten black vampire with hatred and cursed as he spat on his opponent’s face.

He was the fifth generation practitioner of the White Cloud Secret Technique. He was in a rage as he’d found out that his cousin’s child had shown signs that his blood had been sucked by a vampire. In the past, he had not known much about the Blood Breeds, but after entering the combat club he’d obtained this information and managed to link everything up with the situations he’d encountered in his life.

When he asked the child of his situation, he instantly realized that it was the doing of a vampire. Without any hesitation, he brought a group of his friends and rushed over.

To fight against the vampires, those who practiced fist techniques derived from the King’s Fist would learn some tricks to counter the vampire’s skills in controlling humans.

“I’ve warned you before!” the muscular man walked forward. His muscles were moving about like little mice. He then held up the vampire single-handedly by his hair.

“But you turned a deaf ear to me. Now you’ll pay!!”

Boom!!

He punched once more. The punch was so strong, it shook the poor vampire’s brain so hard that he lost his sight temporarily.

Through trial and error by cooperating with Tu Lan, Garen had managed to simplify the White Cloud Secret Technique, which was highly effective against the Blood Breeds. Together with the white muscular man’s natural physical attributes, he was now like a beast with armor, undefeatable and overwhelmingly powerful.

Crowds started to gather as they looked upon the white muscular man punching the defenseless black man.

Occasionally, the black man would counter back with all of his might. Although his speed was fast, his knife wasn’t even able to pierce through the white man’s skin. In return, his leg was grabbed and slammed onto the ground like a hammer.

This made the crowd scream.

This kind of situation was very common on the street and could be seen everywhere.

Most of them were fist technique practitioners torturing the Blood Breeds and there were very few cases of Blood Breeds torturing the fist technique practitioners.

However, as there were much more people who practiced the Holy Fist… Compared to the minority of Blood Breeds, the fist technique practitioners would often come in pairs or groups. Hence most of the Blood Breeds would be beaten up and flee.

This world that they knew was getting chaotic…

Chapter 737: Clue 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Holy Fist Palace

“There is a wide scale conflict with the Blood Breeds in the western area. I’ve already sent people to handle the situation, but the situation is getting more severe by the second and we may not make it in time.”

Xander reported softly before Garen.

He wasn’t just reporting to Garen; Quentin was there as well. Both of them looked like they were having a dilemma as they frowned.

Inside the study room, Garen was busy reading the latest intel report. He was the only one in the room making noise as he flipped through the confidential report.

After a while, Garen closed the document, raised his head and looked at both of them.

“How far has the conflict with the Blood Breed spread in the region?”

“California. It is still expanding and through word of mouth, more and more citizens have acknowledged the existence of Blood Breeds. The notion of their world being controlled by the Blood Breeds have incited the majority’s dissatisfaction. There were people in some of the cities, who practiced the fist technique, that captured the vampires and paraded on the streets as they protested the Blood Breeds holding the upper hand,” Quentin explained.

“The spread of violence wouldn’t be this fast without people from the Witches Association and AG fanning the fire, right?” Garen said coldly.

“Yes,” Quentin confirmed, “their main objective is to incite fear and hatred normal citizens towards the Blood Breeds.”

“Then we will flow with the current for now. Conflicts are unavoidable and what we can do now is wait,” Garen decided calmly.

“Wait? Shouldn’t we send some people out?” Quentin questioned.

“There’s no point in doing so. If we can’t find the Death Apostle’s actual bodies, we cannot truly kill them. Take Tu Lan as an example,” Garen shook his head.

Speaking of Tu Lan, that person had truly fallen in love with the Holy Fist Palace. It was as if she was an addict as she hid in her room while she continuously trained the Fantasy Fist given to her. She had the Soul Primer transferred directly from Garen. She possessed the physical attributes of a Death Apostle, which could be the reason for her ridiculously fast progress.

This made Garen very relieved. If not for the restriction of the Soul Primer’s aura, resulting in the Blood Breeds being unable to learn the King’s Fist Fist Technique, the Blood Breed would easily surpass the humans.

She was barely under Garen’s control as of now. She was considered as one of the Holy Fist Palace’s strongest members, and below her was Dahm, Hochman, the Four Major Generals. They were no match for this Blood Breed.

However, all of them were still considered very powerful.

“We will leave this issue for now. We will talk about this later on when the conflict between the humans and Blood Breeds has reached a certain level. We’ll go to the meeting first,” Garen stood up.

Both disciples slightly nodded respectfully.

Three of them exited the room, walked across a corridor and entered a magnificent silver hall.

The hall was rectangular and there was a ten-meter-long black rectangular stone table placed in the middle of the room. Both sides of the table had been fully filled up.

The head of Rexott and other representatives from all sorts of major fist sects were there. Furthermore, a few General Level officers from the military and politicians from multiple nations were there as well. Within such a short timespan, the Holy Fist Palace had attracted many powerhouses due to their unique and mysterious fist techniques.

The authority they possessed in America was so powerful that no one could ignore them at all.

These connections were made possible by Dahm and Hochman, and one of the politicians was even a member of theirs.

The crowd had already lost their patience. This crowd had many big shots with political or finance backgrounds and they were all waiting for a youngster who was in his twenties. This notion itself made them very unhappy.

If not for the mysterious authorities of the Holy Fist Palace that had huge influences, and the fact that they were the only strength that could fight against the Blood Breeds, these people wouldn’t even bother attending this meeting.

Then, the main entrance of the hall was pushed open.

Three people walked into the hall slowly. The one leading at the front was Garen who was in white Taoist clothes and a black mysterious mask. One could faintly see that one of his eyes seemed blind as there was no expression in it. His golden hair flowed freely by his shoulders and would wave around behind as he walked.

As Garen entered the scene, the big shots by the table started discussing among themselves softly. Some of them even scoffed loudly to express their dissatisfaction, and there were some staring at Garen coldly in an attempt to mess with this youngster with tricks to gain control of the meeting.

This meeting was filled with individuals with great authority. If anyone were able to control this power, it would not influence just America, but even Europe and other regions. After all, the big shots could penetrate anywhere with their economic power.

Everyone started to feel greedy.

Garen brought Quentin and Xander pass the table as they walked towards the main seats and sat down.

“Alright, let’s commence the inner meeting of the Holy Fist Palace,” he said softly.

“Lord Holy Fist, the reason we requested this inner meeting is with regard to the increasing aggressiveness of the Blood Breeds towards the humans. We have to come up with a regulation and solution to this issue immediately. At the very least, emergency countermeasures are a must.”

A senator petitioned calmly.

“I believe that the main objective of this meeting was to select an individual as a conference leader who is able to oversee the whole operation and make the necessary decisions,” he proposed naturally. “Although Lord Garen has overwhelming power that could rival the Death Apostles, this individual requires more than just overall strength. He needs to oversee the situation and coordinate strategically.”

“When the Blood Breeds are cornered, they may ambush our weaknesses such as lord Garen’s family members or best friends. It would be very troublesome if they were to do so,” another senator nodded in agreement. “We definitely need a leader who is able to plan far ahead and oversee the situation.”

“No one has to worry about this. I’ve already placed my underling’s Blood Breed members all over the country to ensure the safety of the regions. Furthermore, we have also deployed the latest technology from the Rexott Group to survey the areas all day long,” Garen answered calmly.

He understood the feeling of these people who have been oppressed by the Blood Breeds. He didn’t care in the least about overseeing the situation and such, as these could be passed down to the experts to handle it. After all, these people hated the Blood Breeds more than he did, and the only way they could obtain authority as a human being was to destroy anything that threatened them.

“I have no comment regarding a personnel to oversee the operation. The Holy Fist Palace is a huge base and no Blood Breed outsiders can infiltrate this place, so everyone can discuss anything related to the Blood Breeds with ease,” Garen said calmly.

“Thank you, Lord Garen, for this is rather important. The powers of the Blood Breed know no bounds, and the only thing that is keeping us safe as of now is the Holy Fist Palace. It’s funny that Jackson thought that he was safe because they’d placed down safety measures around them, right?” an officer shook his head. The officer that he spoke off, Jackson, had been assassinated by a Blood Breed the previous night at two o’clock in the morning. It wasn’t just him; there were other reputable, racist senior officers of the resistance that had been killed or captured by the Blood Breeds as well. This shocked the world and was the reason why so many high ranking officers had gathered at the Holy Fist Palace today.

“We need to strike back with all our might!! We must show those Old Generation Blood Breeds what we’re capable of!”

“However, we first need to know how deeply the Old Generation Blood Breeds have infiltrated into our place.”

“The most important thing right now is to able to differentiate between a Blood Breed and a normal being. Our Group has developed a unique device that is able to differentiate between us and the Blood Breeds by analyzing heartbeats. We should be able to deploy this soon.”

“If the department of cardiology of the Holy Fist Palace is willing to cooperate with us, we can definitely make huge progress.”

Garen beckoned and Tu Lan immediately appeared behind him. After understanding Garen’s intention, she soon participated in the discussion. The Blood Breeds that were controlled by the Holy Fist Palace were called the New Generation Blood Breeds and they were all under the order of Tu Lan, and they formed their own branch of power. Their Soul Primer had been removed personally by Garen so that Tu Lan could inject the Soul Primer that she had created with her Secret Technique’s aura. This way, they would be directly under her.

With a hand by his head, Garen listened to the never-ending discussion of the crowd and soon a simple countermeasure against the Blood Breed had been formed.

Then the orders were transferred and spread out across America via wireless transmission, and everyone started moving.

Garen observed these people getting worked up while he remained unfazed.

Rexott Group and two other economic groups’ representatives kept giving out recommendations that were all adopted. It was no surprise, as they were the powerhouses that had been researching the Blood Breeds in the dark for countless of years. They finally had the opportunity to shine at this time.

This was especially true for Rod’s brother. Although he looked like a cool and handsome young man, his underling had developed a special virus that could be used against the Blood Breeds. It was a biological weapon that could weaken the Blood Breeds to the point where they couldn’t muster up any power. Their limbs would tremble and they would even lose their consciousness if it was serious.

The humans had been oppressed for far too long…

Garen sighed in his mind.

The moment he’d given them an opportunity, the power of their determination to resist had stunned even Garen.

A biological weapon, spirit explosive grenade, infrasonic wave oscillator, blood nucleus detector, et cetera. All sorts of countermeasures had been proposed one by one. At first, the group had felt that they had limited strength, but once everyone gathered their knowledge together, they realized that their strength was more powerful than they previously thought.

This hadn’t accounted for the senator’s super soldier programme. The super soldiers that they had trained were as strong as a Lower-Level Blood Breed. On the other hand, the Turing Group’s representative had revealed their latest research — high-speed neuro battle suits.

It was a suit that could enhance the human’s nervous system, running at fifty times faster than normal. A normal human would have the same reaction time as a Middle-Level or Lower-Level Blood Breed with this reaction speed. While this speed would harm the joints and muscles of the user, it was quickly resolved under the collective research from everyone.

With the high-speed battle suit, super soldiers and the elites of every fist sects gathered together, even Tu Lan was shocked by this development. They were able to gather an army that had the strength of Lower-Level Blood Breeds in such a short amount of time!

With these people gathered together, the strength that they were able to gather made even Garen rather surprised.

“This is the starting point where the humans will fight back!” a person stood up and shouted passionately.

“Today’s meeting will be engraved in history!!” there were people who started to pump their fists up in the air.

Garen had a hunch that the battle with the Blood Breeds would soon arrive after observing this passionate bunch.

Chapter 738: Clue 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The meeting lasted until nighttime before everyone was dismissed and went to their arranged rooms to rest. However, so much passion lingered in them that they couldn’t sleep due to the excitement.

After a series of instrumental experiments, it was shown that becoming a Blood Breed would lengthen their lifespan and practicing Secret Techniques possessed the same effect as well, though its effect was inferior as compared to the Blood Breed’s lifespan. A few of the group representatives were excited, as they were able to make contact with their respective chief scientists through long distance communication. After some inquiry, they’d found a clue on merging the Blood Breed’s gene in hopes of lengthening their own respective lifespans.

This was one of the very few topics that caught Garen’s interest.

After a more detailed discussion with the representative, he represented the Holy Fist Palace to purchase the high-speed neuro battle suits and its related research results, especially the Blood Breed’s genetic implantation which had piqued Garen’s interest the most.

About two hours later after the meeting ended.

Garen finally brought Tu Lan back to the hall in the inner region of the palace.

The moonlight shone through the glass window at their side and bathed the ground and their shoes.

“That meeting was an eye-opener,” Tu Lan was still in disbelief. “The humans’ accumulated oppression is about to explode.”

“Yeah, and I only gave them the chance to release everything at once,” Garen nodded.

“I wouldn’t have believed it if I didn’t witness it with my own eyes. I can’t believe that humans would ever be such a threat towards the Blood Breeds,” Tu Lan shook her head. “Luckily, I’m on your side.”

“Even you don’t believe that the Blood Breeds will win?” Garen frowned slightly.

“No. It’s not that. It’s just that there are too many humans and on the other hand… there’re too few Blood Breeds,” Tu Lan shook her head. “Laser weapons and high explosives are enough to threaten the Blood Breeds. The humans are no longer the same as compared to a few centuries ago. Even if you didn’t exist, this strength would accumulate and would explode sooner or later.”

“You’re right,” Garen nodded.

“Report!!” a black figure suddenly appeared behind Garen and Tu Lan. “Marshall Dahm has successfully obtained a mask and is currently waiting in the golden hall.” a Shooting Shadow Secret Technique practitioner reported loudly at the inner zone of the palace.

“Oh?” Garen revealed a smile. “Finally, he hasn’t disappointed me. Do you want to go and see it together with me?” he turned to Tu Lan.

“Of course.”

Tu Lan was very curious, as she didn’t know why this mask was so important to Garen.

Both of them turned around and walked into a corridor on their right. After passing through a few more corridors and a small garden, they entered a silver meeting room which was almost the same size as the golden hall.

The hall was empty inside and Dahm, who was in a black attire, was the only one standing inside with his head down. He was in a thick grey cloak which covered from his head to toe. He also had a white mask with red paint over the eyes, and one could only tell he was Dahm based on his aura.

“What happened to you?” Garen immediately frowned the moment he entered as he saw Dahm’s excessive coverage.

“Forgive me, teacher,” Dahm’s voice sounded from the cloak. “When I was searching for the mask near the Moon River, I encountered an unknown black monster that I’d never seen before. After pursuing it for more than a month, I finally took care of this beast’s leader on top of the cliff and obtained the mask. However, I was injured by the beast leader’s acid.”

“Take off the cloak and let me have a look,” Garen sat on the main seat of the living hall as he ordered impassively.

Without hesitation, Dahm took off the cloak.

He revealed the skin hidden under the cloak, and even though only the skin from his wrist to his neck could be seen, his skin was scarred and it looked like he had recovered from very bad blisters. His skin resembled a person aged between eight to ninety years old, and this made both Garen and Tu Lan grimace.

“A beast that can injure even you to this extent…” Garen stood up and a black streak was seen as he instantly appeared before Dahm.

Boom!!

He punched Dahm’s chest.

Although this punch wasn’t strong, it possessed a strange power, which was Garen’s own aura.

The aura circled Dahm’s body and immediately returned.

Ah!

Dahm immediately vomited out a mouthful of black water. It was very foul-smelling, and he vomited onto the ground between their legs. The cement on the ground started to sizzle, and white vapors formed upon contact with this black acidic water.

“The remaining poisonous water has been pushed out and with your current regenerative capability, it shouldn’t be difficult for you to heal your skin. Where’s the mask?” Garen asked coldly.

Dahm immediately took out the mask under his cloak. What made this mask different from others was that while it looked identical to the one Garen was wearing, there were some pieces of meat at the edge of the mask. It was as if it were alive as the meat bits wriggled about freely.

After receiving the mask, Garen suddenly felt a huge amount of potential aura entering into his body from the mask. At the same time, Tu Lan and Dahm who were at the scene could faintly hear a cry from the mask, as if it was afraid of Garen. The shredded meat at the edge of the mask wriggled wildly all of the sudden as if they were trying to escape from Garen’s grasp but to no avail. Soon the cry of the mask gradually became weaker and weaker, to the point where it could no longer be heard.

The shredded meat at the edge fell to the ground and formed into a pool of black ash or some sort of black powder. It was very strange indeed.

Garen stashed the mask and could still feel the huge amount of potential points flowing into his body.

“Thank you for the hard work. As a reward, I’ll give you this,” Garen extended his index finger and gently tapped Dahm on the shoulder.

Boom!

It was as if Dahm had been struck by lightning as he stood still and didn’t move at all. It was as though he was a device that had been put on idle mode.

Garen then turned around and left the hall with Tu Lan, the latter being very confused as she didn’t know what had just happened. This was applicable to both the strange mask and Dahm’s change in behavior.

That tap from Garen was the remaining level of Slaughtering Hand that had been retained. With that life force, Dahm would able to help to strengthen his inert life force and increased his physical attributes. For Garen, whose physical attribute was so strong, this was naturally negligible.

However, this was not the case for Dahm. He had become this powerful due to his fist techniques, and his body’s physical attributes had not reached their limits yet. This life force would help Dahm master his Secret Technique at a faster rate and bring his own technique to a higher level. He could also quickly recover from a serious wound so that it wouldn’t be detrimental to his vitality.

For Dahm, the greatest effect of this life force was an opportunity to surpass Hochman.

“Continue searching until you’ve found all twelve masks. Only then I will pass down the strongest secret method that will greatly improve your latent ability,” Garen told Dahm before he left.

The latter lowered his head down.

Garen believed that Dahm possessed quite a number of secret methods, and based on his understanding, it shouldn’t be hard for him to develop his own secret method, one similar to the Shooting Shadow Secret Method.

As he left the golden hall, Garen sent Tu Lan back to her room to rest and he went to his specially made secret chamber alone.

The secret chamber was completely dark. There was no light inside but Garen could see everything inside as if it was daytime.

He walked into the isolated round safe and grabbed onto a thick cylinder placed at the center of the safe. He picked it up and revealed a half-meter-thick cylindrical pillar.

The center of the cylinder was hollow, and there were masks stacked on top of one another, all on top of the Dragon Head Coin Nadia had left behind. What was strange was that the dragon-shaped aura that had always appeared on the coin had stopped flowing. There was nothing coming out of it.

Garen frowned as the cylindrical pillar weighed about a ton. With such a heavy item, the pillar itself was a countermeasure for the safe. If no one could lift it up, it meant that no one could even move the round safe that was placed on the floor as it was even heavier than the pillar.

‘Be careful, I have a bad feeling about this…” Black Sethe, who had been quiet for such a long time, finally spoke up.

“I understand,” Garen nodded. He felt a sense of crisis that wrapped around him like a spider web.

Garen stopped thinking about other stuff as he sat on his knees, preparing himself to absorb the potential points from the sixth mask.

***********

Inside a deep cave near the north pole.

Inside a pitch black cave.   ( Updated by .Com)

An ashen beautiful girl in a white sweater was sitting just beside the stone wall. Her hair was very long and it was as white as snow. Her hair was so long that it flowed and spread about on the ground.

Her white hair was at least ten meters long and was glowing faintly in white inside the cave, giving off a pure and clean vibe.

Her long hair had completely covered her body in such a manner that no one would know whether she was sitting beside the stone wall or merely leaning against it.

“Lion Mother, why have you invited us here?” suddenly, a red blood orb appeared beside the girl in mid-air. What came out from it was a clear male voice.

Soon two more blood orbs slowly appeared at two other spots in the air.

“Scarlet Moon, you’re still alive!” a girl’s voice came from another orb. She was the last one to speak among the blood orbs.

The white-haired girl’s face looked extremely sad.

“I even invited Lord Ashen, but it looks like he’s not joining.”

“The two parties have reconciled and it is his wish whether he wants to attend or not. You can voice out if you have any concern.” a deep male tone rang from the final blood orb.

The Lion Mother nodded her head.

“Have you guys heard of the legend of the Sleepless Faces?”

“The legendary mysterious mask that the mortals spread? I understood a little bit.” the first blood orb responded.

“I’ve heard of it as well.” the girl spoke through her orb.

“Realistically speaking, the Sleepless Faces is related to a secret known to very little being. It is related to the secret of immortality…”

Chapter 739: Clue 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“We Blood Breeds are immortal, to begin with. Why do we still need that mask?” a female Death Apostle grumbled through the blood orb impatiently.

“Naturally, as this is not noteworthy towards us Blood Breeds at all, no one goes out to collect these masks,” the Lion Mother said impassively. “However to the humans, obtaining immortality is definitely one of their greatest desires.”

“Are you suggesting that the Holy Fist Palace is currently collecting these masks?” the Death Apostle Scarlet Moon asked softly.

“The Holy Fist Palace…!” the sound of grinding teeth accompanied the first blood orb’s speech. Wellington was one of the victims that had suffered a defeat at Garen’s hands, which was why he had a very strong impression of him. If Ashen hadn’t arrived in the nick of time, he would have been killed repeatedly to the point where he would have to respawn on one of his bloodlines. The pain and torture that he experienced, the sensation and incredible pain each time he had been pulverized into minced meat by a single punch from this human had completely traumatized him.

“Are you saying that the legend of this mask is real?” Scarlet Moon asked.

“It’s real,” the Lion Mother nodded. “According to what I know, the Holy Fist Palace has already collected six masks. When they collect all twelve masks, they will be able to activate the last mask. Once Garen wears the Primal Mask, he will most likely turn into the Original Blood Breed that once roamed this world.”

“The Original Blood Breed?” a few Death Apostles didn’t really understand what it was.

“Legend has it that the Sleepless Faces masks are actually one mask that gave life to the Original Blood Breed. However, a legend is just a legend. I’ve done my research back in the days and it’s true that the mask does possess a mysterious power. The Sleepless Faces are able to allow people to be immune to all sorts of illusions and supernatural interference from the dream world. This is the origin of how it had gotten its name, the Sleepless Faces.”

“This means that once Garen has obtained this mask, his body may become that of a Blood Breed and also possesses the immunity to all of our dream interference and illusions. Does that mean we can only handle him in the normal material world!?” the female Death Apostle’s tone turned sharp.

“Damn it!! Fight him in the material world? Do you guys know how ridiculously strong that guy is in the material world?” Wellington shouted.

“Patience is a virtue. Actually, I still have another important thing to announce,” the Lion Mother shook her head.

“I believe that once Garen has become the Original Blood Breed, he will have the ability to track down the locations of the Death Apostle’s dreams.”

The moment it was announced, the whole cave was thrown into quietness.

No one spoke as these Death Apostles had realized that they were in grave danger.

After a while, Scarlet Moon started speaking once more.

“If it really has this capability, why had nobody attempted to search for it before?”

“Because I’m the only one left who knows of this secret…” the Lion Mother replied calmly. “I’ve been alive for so long and I’ve already forgotten where I’d learned this secret. Do you really think no one attempted to search for it before?”

“In 1871, a countess from Europe managed to collect five masks but passed away while she was on a search for the sixth mask. In 1544, the king of Greece Melsa once sent a huge army to search for the mask and managed to find six masks as well. I’ve been keeping an eye out for this mask and these are just examples.”

She said calmly as the history was just a small part of her life.

“Everyone who tried to collect the mask would usually halt their progress when they collected six masks. There are no exceptions. However…”

“What?” one of the Death Apostle raised a question but no one seemed to care as they poured all their attention onto the Lion Mother.

“However, the Holy Fist Palace may very well be the first one to exceed this amount.” the Lion Mother continued softly. “The seventh mask was in the hands of the moon river’s protector, which has been killed by someone.”

“According to what I know, Garen should have six masks including the one from the moon river, which does not exceed the amount you mentioned yet,” Scarlet Moon said calmly.

“Another mask is in the hand of someone else,” Lion Mother’s words made everyone quiet down.

“Are you really sure the Sleepless Faces is able to turn someone into the Original Blood Breed? Furthermore, that person will be able to locate where our dream worlds are?” the Death Apostle asked once more.

“The Blood Breed’s bloodline originates from one ancestor, which was created from a miracle of life via dark magic when the humans were in search of immortality. Perhaps I should say that it was an alteration, as I’ve done a detailed research regarding the origin. The Original Bloodline should be able to sense every descendants’ location. Perhaps there is an area of effect, but by no means, it is very small scale.” the Lion Mother responded.

“I need to go and read up the old database,” Scarlet Moon’s blood orb dispersed and he had left the area.

“I need to head back and do my research as well,” the female Death Apostle said softly. “My household’s Holy Weapon, the Original Eye has stored information that spanned several millennia back. I should be able to find some hints.”

“I’ll go with you,” Wellington voiced out.

“Sure.”

Two of the blood orbs dispersed as well.

The cave became quiet once more.

A flicker of unease could be seen in the Lion Mother’s eyes.

“The world is turning more chaotic… The Holy Fist Palace… the source of all chaos,” she muttered as her face was filled with sadness.

***********

Garen was sitting on his knees inside the secret chamber.

He looked at his attribute pane.

His potential point had increased from 64 points to 174 points. This mask had provided him a decent amount of hundred plus potential points. Although it wasn’t considered much among the other masks, it was enough for him to increase his last Intelligence point.

Without any hesitation, Garen focused his gaze on Intelligence in the pane.

Since his Intelligence already had eleven points, he would require just another point to revert back to his strength when he was at the Totem world. After achieving twelve points, he would be able to obtain the unique effects from his physical attribute, Doublecast.

In an instant, his potential points dropped by a hundred, leaving behind 74 points. His Intelligence then increased from eleven points to twelve points.

Garen, who was sitting on his knees, jolted his body suddenly. He could feel a very agile and light feeling swelling inside him. He felt that his body had given him the illusion of an agile body by merely increasing one Intelligence point.

He reached out his hand and punched straight with all his might.

Pew pew!!

The air in front of him boomed as two white puffs of air appeared out of thin air as his fist thrust forth, landing on the secret chamber’s wall. This resulted in two deep blade marks on the wall.  ( Updated by .Com)

“When I release my basic strength, the Doublecast will be activated and it will make me stronger.”

It was a weird sensation similar to one releasing all of their strength, only to realize that one still had enough strength to release it once more after that.

He stood up and took the mask off his face. He then changed into a new one as the former mask had been slightly damaged while he fought against Ashen.

“I’ve finally obtained the Doublecast. I should focus on obtaining the remaining masks next,” Garen’s goal was clear as day. “No matter what trick Nadia has up her sleeves, I will be able to isolate her trace as long as I am able to collect all the masks, evading all dangers from her.”

************

At the headquarter of the Bailey Group.

On the nineteenth floor of the Merlot building.

Boom!

The floor’s entrance was kicked open and a team of black-shirted police entered the place swiftly. A ‘safe’ secret signal was then broadcasted immediately from their communication device.

The nineteenth floor of this building was filled with office tables and chairs that have not been used for a long time. The leftover documents spread about everywhere and there were a few documents on the ground looked like they had been wetted before they opened the window.

The entire nineteenth floor, which was able to fit hundreds of people, was completely empty.

At least ten special police members positioned themselves strategically while they remained on full alert.

Xander, who was in a black cloak, entered the room with two of his best subordinates, a woman and a man, following behind.

He had an unlit cigarette hanging from his mouth as he scanned the whole floor.

“Looks like it’s been abandoned as well. The Bailey Group sure is something,” he took out his cigarette and said calmly.

“Boss, we will definitely be able to track the core members of the Bailey Group if we go to the airport’s train station,” the woman behind him spoke calmly.

“I’ve already told someone to do so and I believe I should be receiving the news any moment…” before Xander finished his sentence, he immediately aimed at the window with a silver gun that no one saw him take out.

Bam!

Bam Bam!!

Three gunshots were fired in a manner as if they had all been fired instantaneously.

Suddenly, two gunshots could be heard from the opposite building and two bullets were flying towards him.

The wall and the windows were shot through, leaving two clear holes. Two bullets went towards Xander at lightning speed from two different angles. He was under the impression that he couldn’t avoid it at all.

He then raised up his gun and shot as well. His aim was so amazingly accurate that he managed to hit one of the incoming bullets slightly on the right. This shifted the bullet’s projectile path and it ricocheted into the wall and vending machine beside him.

Xander moaned as he quickly held onto his left shoulder tightly. He didn’t manage to evade the other bullet and had taken a hit. His shoulder was immediately dripping with red blood.

His face turned pale instantly as the opponent had fired an armor-piercing bullet from an anti-material sniper rifle! With that shot, a hole instantly appeared on his shoulder and he was completely defenseless against it.

Chapter 740: Clue 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Take cover!!” Xander shouted at the top of his lungs, and two of his subordinates immediately moved; they rolled on the ground and hid behind a pillar to avoid being shot.

Although he was a very powerful Martial Adept, he was a non-defense martial adept type as he practiced the Waterbird Fist Technique. Hence it was only natural that he was defenseless against the threat of human weaponry.

On the other hand, it was completely different to those who practiced the White Cloud Secret Technique. Although they were not as fast, they were the best meat shield in this situation. There was a practitioner that practiced the White Cloud Secret Technique who, other than having natural talent, had a strange bodily characteristic as well. After reaching the second tier, he had a much higher defense than others in the same level.

They had once tried an experiment where they used a rather weak handgun and shot his stomach at point-blank range. The result was surprising as he barely even bled. If he were the one who had been shot by the anti-equipment rifle which had pierced through a layer of obstacles, the power of it hitting onto him would be almost the same as him being shot by a handgun at point-blank range.

The special police officers took cover but they didn’t know where the bullet was shot from.

Soon the special forces stationed just below the building started to surround the suspected buildings nearby.

With the support of the military and government, America was basically under the representation of the Holy Fist Palace. The majority of the Blood Breed’s strength had either moved out of America or were directly under the Holy Fist Palace. As the conflict between the Blood Breeds and normal humans kept increasing, both Blood Breeds and the neutral standing hidden Blood Breeds were all forced into the light. The majority of the neutral standing Blood Breeds joined the Holy Fist Palace and became a part of them in order to continue living their peaceful life.

Soon, the gunners sent by the Bailey Group had been captured by the Holy Fist Palace’s Blood Breeds and was sent directly to Xander for interrogation.

With the Blood Breed’s hypnosis on humans, the killer soon revealed his mission’s objective.

Never in Kabb’s mind would he have expected that the Blood Breeds would enter the Holy Fist Palace, as his killers had revealed everything under hypnosis.

Two hours later…

Kabb and Medis, who were hidden in a certain basement in Los Angeles, were personally captured by Hochman himself and soon on their way to the Holy Fist Palace for their impending punishment.

************

“Tell me, where’s the mask?” Garen stared calmly at the already kneeling Kabb and Medis. Both of them looked very drained and exhausted as if they’d experienced a lot of pain on their way there.

“I have a lot of ways to make you guys speak but I’ll be merciful since I’ve interacted with you people in the past.”

Garen said with a very straight face.

“The mask is indeed in my possession. Furthermore, I know where the remaining masks are too,” Kabb answered calmly. “However, I have a condition.”

“You do not have the right to negotiate any condition.”

Garen closed his eyes, stood up and walked to the small door on his right.

“Kill him.”

Hochman’s pupil immediately shrunk as he didn’t even notice that a blue figure had appeared beside Kabb and Medis, who were literally just beside him.

It was Tu Lan in a blue dress. Her hair was as red as blood as they flowed around her shoulders. Her eyes were giving off a rather mysterious and seducing beauty.

Kabb and Medis, who were half kneeling, had expected that Garen would try to make concessions in order to gain advantages for future negotiations. However, they only realized that he didn’t even care when Garen had left the room!

With the sudden appearance of a blue-dressed woman, both of them had started to panic for real.

His actions were completely illogical!

Didn’t negotiation mean that both parties should take a step back and reach a point of agreement? Why did he just flip everything right at the very beginning?

“Tell me everything you know about the Sleepless Faces,” it was as if Tu Lan’s eyes were filled with a lethal spell as she easily absorbed both of their consciousnesses.

In an instant, both of them immediately turned limp.

No matter how much times Hochman witnessed it, the admiration kept lingering in him. Tu Lan’s hypnosis far surpassed any typical Blood Breeds. He felt that this power was too much even though he wasn’t the target.

A few minutes later…

With a relieved look on her face, Tu Lan walked towards Garen, who was watering the plants in the greenhouse.

She then reported everything she had extracted from Kabb and Medis to Garen.

“The Sleepless Faces is able to grant immortality? It can create the Original Blood Breed?” Garen was stunned.

“This is what I found out according to Kabb. It is also the reason why he had been secretly trying to obtain the Sleepless Faces. Unfortunately, he doesn’t have the strength and confidence. It is very impressive that he, as a commoner, is able to get his hand on one mask,” Tu Lan sighed.

Garen pondered for a moment as he reached out his hand and gently picked a newly bloomed white rose. He then gently placed it under his nose as he admired the fragrance.

He glanced at Tu Lan and realized that she seemed hesitant, as though she wanted to ask something.

“You can speak what’s on your mind.”

Tu Lan hesitated for a moment but she eventually opened her mouth.

“Since you don’t know the purpose of this mask, why are you collecting them?”

“I have my own reason. You don’t need to know about this,” Garen smiled.

“Is it because of the mysterious energy it contains?” Tu Lan asked softly.

“Oh? You know about it?” Garen was surprised to hear that.

Only the founders of the Black Uniforms knew that antiques contained mysterious powers. As the higher-ups of the Black Uniforms had dispersed, it was no longer a secret and it wasn’t strange that Tu Lan knew about this.

Garen didn’t care if people knew about it, as his natural ability was something no one can replicate.

He was able to absorb this energy and channel it into himself to increase his abilities. This was indeed a very powerful skill. However, he wasn’t the only one who possessed this glitch-like ability, regardless of whether it was the Secret Technique world or the Totem world. For example, there was White Bird Holy Fist Palosa and his ridiculous 99 Acute Airholes. However, these were all unimportant, as what determined the victor of the battle was perseverance during the battle itself.

It didn’t matter if it was him, Sylphalan or Pasola. They represented the peak of their generations and was the representative of generation after generation.

They weren’t people who could be simply described as having natural talent.

Without the will to focus and achieve their goals, it would’ve been impossible for them to reach that far.

As Tu Lan stared at Garen from the side, she suddenly felt that this man was very mysterious, even more than a Death Apostle.

A mere human who lived for about twenty years had reached such height in terms of power. It was as if he knew everything since young and could master everything without any guidance. Furthermore, his gaze didn’t fit a twenty-year-old youngster at all but resembled that of a very experienced old man.

“If the Original Blood Breed story is real, the other Death Apostles will not allow you to live.”

The Death Apostles who were used to standing at the top would never allow Garen, who resembled dark clouds that would engulf all high ranking Blood Breeds and was a person who stood above everyone else just like Ashen, to live.

“The conflict between us and the Old Generations Blood Breed cannot be avoided,” Garen laughed as if he wasn’t worried at all. “But what about it? No one can stop me, including Ashen.”

He kept recalling the life he’d lived in this world. He wasn’t sure why, but he had been recollecting the days he had here.

However, he wasn’t rejecting his memories of being born and the life he had with Rafaelle in a small town when he was young.

“I may be out for a few days. You’ll be in charge of the Holy Fist Palace until then,” Garen said all of the sudden.

“Aren’t you afraid of the Death Apostles ambushing you?” Garen was stunned. “I won’t be able to stop them. Wellington probably hates you to the core and would strike at any given opportunity.”

“It’s not in Ashen’s personality to act like that, but you should take caution against the other two Death Apostles,” Garen started frowning as well. This was indeed a problem since the masks might force the Old Generation Blood Breed to stand against him. Excluding Ashen, the remaining two Death Apostles might team up and it would be very troublesome once they do. Tu Lan alone would be helpless against them as she had just become a Death Apostle not long ago.

The Holy Fist Palace had now become the mental icon of humans fighting against the Old Generation Blood Breeds. Hence, they couldn’t afford to be embroiled in trouble as a lot of important big shots from America had gathered in this place. Its influence was immense and strong. It would be unimaginable if the Old Generation Blood Breeds successfully attacked this place.

“Do you have any news from AG?” Garen changed the topic.

“No. However I heard that there was a rare glacier earthquake at the south pole where AG had locked himself away from the world. AG’s location is unknown after the large-scale glacier collapse, and we could only determine AG is still alive by using a weak positioning communication device,” Tu Lan was very determined in following Garen permanently. With her lazy personality, she didn’t want to leave at all as she got to learn Secret Techniques and become stronger.

Garen only planned to visit Raffaele. If possible, he wished to take her and her family members in so that the Blood Breeds would not take her in as a hostage after discovering their relationship.

However now that he looked at it, he was completely chained at the Holy Fist Palace.

*********

In the small Grano town.

Inside a black villa at the center of the small town.

The main hall was completely dark. There was no light but rows of lit candles had been placed on the ground in circles all around the whole main hall.

The yellow candlelight wobbled about as it lit up the situation inside the main hall.

There were three beautiful girls dressed in white dresses and had white wreaths upon their heads. Under the witness of a huge group of black-shirted witches, the three ladies carried triangular silver accessories as they quietly walked towards the grey sculpture in front of them.

The golden-haired woman who walked at the front was Grano’s youngest and most talented witch — Raffaele.

As she walked at the front, her expression was strict while she approached the female figure sculpture. She then stabbed her left index finger with the silver triangular accessories.

Pop!

Drops of fresh blood started to drip into the black basin in front of the sculpture. / .Com

“Great Lion Mother, please accept Grano’s most attractive corolla as the purest gift to you,” Rafaelle’s grandmother started singing loudly as she raised her wooden crutches high.

Chapter 741: Realm 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Along with the melody, the drop of blood in the basin had gradually gotten thicker and started spreading rapidly. From only a drop of blood, it had turned a washbasin-sized black basin with a red-stained interior.

Raffaele raised her head, looked at the statue in the eyes, and used her bleeding index finger to gently stroke in between her eyebrows, leaving a vermillion mark.

She closed her eyes. When the ceremony was just about to end and the witches were about to throw away the stuff, suddenly.

Buzz!!!!

A powerful, coarse yet gentle force suddenly befell.

This force focussed on the statue with a dazzling, hazy white light and strangely, the stone statue started moving. The statue stretched out her right arm and gently caressed Raffaele’s cheek.

“The Lion Mother has arrived!” the witches exclaimed in wonder.

“The great Lion Mother! Please bless the leader of Grano!”

“The Supreme Witch King!”

The witches were in a joyful commotion.

Raffaele’s grandmother had a happy look on her face while she stared at Raffaele and the statue without blinking an eye. The advent of the Lion Mother was so rare that one hand alone was enough to count the number of times it had happened. Previously, she only had the chance to communicate slightly with the Lion Mother during special holidays, but now, the will of the Witch King had appeared right before them and surprisingly came just to bless Raffaele.

“Bless you, Grano’s Raffaele, the beautiful sun witch, you will have a greater position and power in the future….” a majestic will spirit shrouded over Raffaele.

Raffaele had a sweet smile on her face. However, no one noticed that the liveliness in her eyes was gone, leaving only indescribable emptiness.

*****************

In a distant underground cave.

The Lion Mother slowly opened her eyes, and the look of sympathy in her eyes had gotten worse.

“Please do not put the blame on me…. In order to eliminate all sources of evil, any sacrifice will be worth it….”

***************

“The seventh mask is in an ancient tomb in Asia?”

“The Holy Fist Palace has definitely sent someone to look for it. As long as we send someone over, we will certainly be able to delay or even prevent him from getting the seventh mask.”

“Then who should we send?”

“Someone who’s at least an Upper-Level Blood Breed as the leader. Otherwise, it would be hard for them to deal with Hochman and Dahm.”

In the hall of the Blood Union.

The four Death Apostles of the Secret Party and Light Party were sitting in the top four seats. The Blood Breed representatives of each ancestral family surrounded the four of them, and they were all crowded into a large circle. This was the first time that both parties, the Secret Party and the Light Party, have peacefully co-existed in the Blood Alliance conference since the fight.

Although the members of both parties were still hostile towards one another, ever since the pressure from the humans was getting bigger and heavier, their actions towards the blood breeds have gotten extreme. The newly invented detector had sleuthed out many older generation Blood Breeds, who were executed on the spot.

Humans named the Blood Breeds who joined the Holy Fist Palace as the new generation Blood Breeds, the neo-humans, whereas the Blood Breeds that did not join the Holy Fist Palace were named as the old generation Blood Breeds. With such a distinctive classification, it greatly suppressed both the Light Party and the Secret Party, as well as the neutral Blood Breeds.

Under such circumstances, many furious humans were unable to control their emotions and as a result, their actions against the Blood Breeds were starting to get out of control.

At this point, the Blood Breed’s Blood Alliance had no choice but to hold an emergency meeting to discuss methods to deal with the problem they were facing.

Surprisingly, the four Death Apostles came to an agreement regarding the issue about the Holy Fist Palace’s search of the Sleepless Faces.

Wellington looked at the remaining two Death Apostles.

“I did some research and found that the Sleepless Faces do have the ability to change one’s physique and convert them into ancestral Blood Breeds. In addition to having a long life, the ancestral Blood Breeds were able to locate all Death Apostles, but other than that, they had no other special abilities. Even so, I cannot help but tremble in fear at the thought of Garen being able to continue putting pressure on us.”

“I have found records on the abilities of ancestral Blood Breeds,” the only female death apostle said calmly.

“Me too,” another unfamiliar looking blonde man dressed in a black robe answered curtly.

The three of them were the three key figures of the Secret Party, and that man was the most mysterious among them.

Scarlet Moon from the Light Party was sitting opposite to them.

He was a pale looking dark-haired young man with a cold look on his face, and only when his eyes moved slightly could people tell that he was alive and not merely a sculpture.

“Scarlet Moon, what do you think?” the female Death Apostle looked towards Scarlet Moon.

“We are not participating; joining the Holy Fist Palace might also be an option,” Scarlet Moon answered coldly. The two Death Apostles from the Secret Party had chased him from such a long time that even now, he has yet to regain his full strength, so he was simply unbothered about these things.

“Fortunately, it is obvious that we have the advantage of our large number of usable manpower as compared to the Holy Fist Palace. All he has is just one Death Apostle and two Upper-Level Blood Breeds. Hence, he himself has to be in the headquarters and will not be able to leave,” Wellington analyzed, “I think that we can directly launch a nuclear attack onto the Holy Fist Palace and destroy the hope of mankind with their own technology, hehe…” a glimpse of cruelty flashed through his eyes.

When he recalled the memories of Garen slaughtering him continuously, he could not suppress the anger in his heart; that had been how Garen had traumatized him. If Garen were to find a way to kill the Death Apostles, then killing them would be easier than slaughtering a chicken if he was also able to locate the Death Apostles.

“We clearly cannot let him find the last few masks. If possible, I suggest that we should also start looking for the last few masks, and keep them in the hands of the Blood Alliance,” he suggested.

“This could work too.”

“Since we need to stop him from getting the masks, why not just directly eliminate his organization?”

Although the few of them did not respond to Wellington’s nuclear attack idea, it did not mean that they would give up on that method. However, the nuclear strike would be their last resort, and they will not use it until the very last minute. Otherwise, they would need to sacrifice eight hundred of them in order to kill a thousand of them, and that would be an outrageous loss.

“Both Hochman and Dahm are only Upper-Leveled, so as long as we are careful, we can easily settle the both of them.”

“What if they are using this trick too?” the female Death Apostle frowned.

“We can lure him into a trap, since he’s so strong, right? Let us see if a large number of strong explosives will be able to kill him, or how many toxic bombs will be enough to infect him. We can also use a thousand degrees flamethrower and laser splicing. I doubt that he will be able to survive,” the blonde man in the black robe surprised Wellington by uttering those words with a calm look on his face. Furthermore, the methods that he mentioned were almost all humans’ methods. This man was obviously very familiar with the humans’ science and technology.

“It seems like your human economic group has deeply affected you,” Scarlet Moon sneered. “Once you’ve used this method, do you think that they won’t use the same method to deal with us? You should know that human beings are far greater than us in terms of numbers.”

“This is a war, and we’re supposed to resort to every possible method,” the blonde man in the black robe said.

“I agree,” Wellington raised his hand. “Let’s vote to decide.”

Two hands were raised; the female Death Apostle hesitated, but still raised her hand.

Scarlet Moon remained impassive.

“All of you can do what you want. The Light Party won’t be participating.” he hit on the armrest of his chair and gradually disappeared from his seat.

At the same time, the representatives from the Light Party got the signal and left one after another.

“Even without them, we can easily conquer the Holy Fist Palace,” the blonde man in the black robe shrugged, maintaining his calm expression.

*******************

Asia, Forwade Mountains.

The brown mountains looked like a brown giant serpent with a little white peak that lay between Asia and Europe, completely separating the two regions.

A dozen of small countries surrounded the mountain, and Cassarne was one of them.

Cassarne was a small Buddhist country with a population of not more than 20 million, with only five cities including the capital. The vast majority of them were Buddhists.

During the afternoon, when the sky was still slightly dim, the bell started ringing as usual on top of Cassarne’s capital, Mount Roland.

The heavy bronze bell was being hit repeatedly, accompanied by the temple’s distant chants.

Bustling crowds filled the streets of Mount Roland, and from time to time, gray elephants passed by in a line. Women were walking around, dressed in veils that could only cover their upper body, and most of them had a red mark in between their eyebrows, indicating that they were married.

On the other hand, unmarried young women kept a long braid and were without any marking in between their eyebrows. They were walking together in groups.

From time to time, skinny and dark-skinned ascetic monks could be seen on the streets. Some of them were bare from the waist up, and with their long hair and beards, they looked very sloppy.

Some ascetic monks were sitting cross-legged on the large piece of cement in the largest temple near Mount Roland, Garlot temple, with their eyes closed while they murmured their chants.

Many local children and young men and women surrounded them. There were also foreign tourists who constantly took pictures with their cameras.

There were blonde-haired and black-haired tourists. The special characteristics from different countries were gathered in this place, and even black people with skin as dark as charcoal were present.

A fashionable female tourist with luscious blonde hair and a curvy body was wearing a pair of dark brown sunglasses as well as a beautiful black dress. Two sturdy bodyguards with closely cropped hair were following behind her.

She saluted the ascetic monks by putting her palms together in front of them, then she started browsing the stuff from a small accessory stall. However, her eyes were inconspicuously focussed on Garlot Temple on top of the mountains.

“It has been confirmed that the seventh mask is just below the Buddha stupa located at the back of Garlot Temple. There should be an underground ancient tomb palace,” the woman heard a man’s mosquito-like thin voice in her ears.

She nodded slightly.

“Hold on, that place only allows devout Buddhists to enter, so you might start a large-scale riot by entering recklessly. Wait until it gets dark before entering. According to the order of Sir Caesar, it would be the best if we can retrieve the mask without alerting anyone.”

“Understood.”

The man’s voice slowly faded out.

Chapter 742: Realm 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As time passed, the woman and her bodyguards went to a small restaurant to eat, but as there were only vegetarian dishes available, they had an unsatisfied look on their faces.

The sky gradually got dark and the street lights began to switch on.

The woman brought along her two bodyguards and casually walked towards the alley behind the temple.

They entered a relatively narrow alley, and there was no one inside. The three of them instantly changed from leisure and carefree to quick and speedy.

In just the blink of an eye, they took off their robes and the woman was wearing a tight-fitting undercoat beneath.

“Let’s go!”

The three of them scaled the walls of the temple like geckos, and with a leap, they disappeared into the other side of the temple wall.

But just behind them, two men in black slowly walked out of the dark alley. Both of them had blood red eyes and emitted an indescribably weird feeling.

“That should be them. Let’s keep up with them.”

The two men were the guards sent by the Blood Breeds. Because the Blood Breeds had way more connections than the Holy Fist Palace, even though they were not interested in the Sleepless Faces, they were able to find this piece of information from a mass of information that was as vast as the skies and sea, so they followed the Holy Fist Palace’s research team everywhere they went.

After the two blood breeds entered the palace, two slender figures appeared in the alley once again.

A handsome and mature-looking young man who wore glasses was no other than Caesar, and a middle-aged woman with a respectful look on her face was standing beside him.

“The blood breeds have made a move,” Caesar looked in the direction the two blood breeds had gone towards. “Jean, we will follow the plan.”

“Yes, master,” the middle-aged woman bowed her head.

As the second heir to an ancient family in Europe, after Caesar had joined the Holy Fist Palace, he’d become the successor with the highest chance of inheriting his family’s power. He’d defeated the first heir using both direct and sneaky methods during this period of time, who was unable to retaliate. With the help of the Combat Club, Caesar gradually took control of the family’s hidden powers.

“It is said that the Sleepless Faces have some kind of mysterious power, and it can strengthen one’s physical qualities. Perhaps we can intercept it and investigate it,” the middle-aged woman proposed.

“There’s no need for that,” Caesar shook his head. As the heir of the family, he valued his responsibility as a member of the Holy Fist Palace, as it was the source of his power. “The mask is something that the Holy Fist master personally wants, so we cannot let anyone get it. As the master gets stronger, we, as the members of the Holy Fist Palace, will also be influenced to improve.”

In fact, he was a little tempted, but after taking into account the risk of being found out, it was not worth risking the benefits that he was getting. Even if he got stronger by using the mask, was it possible for him to be stronger than the Holy Fist Master, Garen? The answer was obvious, and he might raise suspicion in the palace with his abnormal improvements. Most importantly, after so many years, Kabb from the Bailey Group had not been able to study anything from the mask that he had gotten. Therefore, it was unrealistic for him to think that he was able to study the mask in such a short period of time.

“Okay, let’s follow the plan.”

“Yes.”

The middle-aged woman replied in a low voice and began to send out secret signals on her phone.

Soon, a large number of people who were ready to ambush the Cassarne, the capital of Mount Roland, started to gradually make a move.

Hundreds of tourists sneakily moved in the direction of the Garlot Temple and surreptitiously surrounded the whole temple.

Then, they stopped moving and slowly waited for the moment when the Blood Breeds would leave the temple.

These tourists were elites from Caesar’s family that were trained by the Holy Fist Palace. Although they were not as powerful as the formal members of the Holy Fist Palace, they were still able to fight one-on-one against a vampire. However, the training that these people underwent were focused primarily on the Blood Breeds’ control over humans, along with some special classes to deal with high-speed rivals and specially crafted venom bullets. These poisonous bullets were invented by humans to specifically target the Blood Breeds’ constitution after the Holy Fist Palace festival. After optimizing the raw material formula, it formed a cost-effective poison against the Blood Breeds. Blood Breeds who were shot would have symptoms of weakness, and although it was not life-threatening, even an ordinary human could kill a weakened blood breed in a single blow.

After who knew how long….

“There are here!!” suddenly, a deep voice was heard. It had an Austria German accent.

Cho cho cho cho…

In just a blink of an eye, there was a burst of raindrop-like silenced gunshots. Numerous poisonous bullets were fired into the night sky above the walls.

Right at this moment, two black shadows appeared, and they were the two Blood Breeds that had gone into the temple. Just as they appeared, countless bullets were fired in their direction and being unable to dodge the barrage, the duo fell to the ground from mid-air after being hit twice, as though they were deflated balloons.

Caesar waved his hand.

“Bring them along and leave this place immediately!”

The people who were previously hiding hurriedly rushed over to the two Blood Breeds, searched their bodies, put them into two sack bags and carried them away. They were extremely experienced.

Everyone including Caesar quickly left the place. The entire process had lasted less than a minute, showcasing their terrifying efficacy.

At the same time, at the main entrance of the temple, an old monk in a yellow robe slowly walked out of the main hall and walked towards the stupa behind from the side of the temple. He had a pious look on his face, and as he walked, he would put his palms together to greet the other resting monks.

Soon, he arrived before the stupa, then he put his palms together to greet the old monk guarding the stupa and walked into stupa as usual for inspection.

After walking quite a distance using the main route, there was no one around him. the old monk then gently reached his hands up and tore at his face, and he actually ripped off his whole face. A horrifying burnt face underneath was exposed, and shockingly, it was Dahm from the Holy Fist Palace, who should have been far away in the United States.

He looked at his surroundings, quickly locked onto a direction and walked towards the tarin. When he arrived in front of a seemingly deserted stupa, he groped and searched the ground. He opened a wooden cover and exposed a dark underground passage, and this was his reward for being in disguise for such a long period of time.

However, it seemed like someone had gotten here first as there were traces of people entering the passage.

However, Dahm did not panic. He took off his monk robe, put on a tight-fitting black suit and walked directly into the passage like a ghostly figure, pulling the wooden cover back, reverting it to how it used to look.

The seventh mask was definitely in this underground palace, and he knew that it would not be easy retrieving the mask.

*******************

Holy Fist Palace

“The seventh mask should be similar to the sixth mask, and there should be a guardian,” Garen gentle stroked the sixth mask in his hand. “No matter how well we prepare, the lack of strength is a fact that we cannot hide.”

“Caesar and Dahm both went there openly and secretly, maybe they might succeed,” Tu Lan replied. “According to what the clan leader of Wellington would usually do, he will definitely send someone in advance to grab the other masks, so you be prepared.”

“They know about the other masks?” Garen asked.

“Of course, the possibility is very high,” Tu Lan nodded.

The two of them were sitting face to face at the restaurant for dinner. Small meat patties covered in a black sauce were stacked together and a fragrant sauce had been poured on top. The dish emitted the savory aroma of minced meat, tender lamb chops, steak, mushroom soup, and sweet trout with truffle. A variety of dishes were placed in front of them, but only Tu Lan was eating happily; Garen did not have much appetite.

“Now that Dahm has managed to get into the underground palace, if things go without a hitch, he should be able to get the mask. He just needs to be alert about the Blood Breeds,” Garen said, frowning.

Recently, he’d practiced the Holy Phoenix Scriptures and his progress was quite good when combined with the Demonic Book. The Holy Phoenix Scriptures were actually a type of reality, divided into three layers and nine small realms, and each realm corresponded to a type of spiritual form. Or perhaps, it could be described as an imaginary platform that allows one’s spiritual energy to transform and form powerful images.

The true meaning of the Holy Phoenix had played a significant role in the formation of his soul seeds.

According to his estimation, as long as he reached the second layer of the Holy Phoenix Scriptures, he would be able to completely gather his soul seed. However, this way of practice was totally different from his previous secret techniques.

The most crucial part of the Holy Phoenix reality practice was to know the true meaning behind it. There would be an image of a strange living creature in each realm, and in order to proceed to the next realm, he needed to completely visualize it. After successfully visualizing it, he could then transform his spiritual energy into the same powerful creatures in a spiritual battle, and attack his opponents with a powerful force.

But as his visualization gradually deepened, Garen vaguely felt as though there was a line connected to his body, and this line had appeared due to practicing the Holy Phoenix Scriptures.

He had a feeling that the true meaning of the Holy Phoenix might be related to the Mother Stream.

And Black Sethe agreed.

It was obvious that the true meaning of the Holy Phoenix used a training method of separating one’s spirit from their physical body, which was a purely civilized spiritual method. Therefore, it was no surprise that they created a large machine such as the Buddha Mother because their physical qualities might be far weaker than their spiritual development.

In other words, they used foreign objects to make up for their own lack of physical and combat strength. This was purely a spiritual energy training.

As for the source of the Mother Stream, it was the greatest miracle stream that acted as a natural storage of spiritual energy. From what Black Sethe speculated, the Holy Phoenix Scriptures and the Buddha Mother might be the same as him. They were the survivors of the Mother Stream and entered into this world. Or perhaps they have lost their way and made it here.

‘In this world, you might never find enough resources to break through to the army level. Even if you reach the second level of the soul seed, without the full development of your body and unless you are spiritually strong enough to reach the level of true soul, you will never be able to withstand Nadia’s gradually improving brute strength,’ Black Sethe said softly in Garen’s ear.

“There are three levels to the soul seed. I have gone through the ordinary soul stage, and now I’m at the second soul seed level. How can it become a true soul?” Garen asked.

Chapter 743: Undercurrent 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

‘True Soul? Are you kidding? Even during our peak demon lord class period, we were not True Souls. That was just a dream. Only ancient warlocks with great achievements were able to reach that level, as their spiritual energy alone was able to distort reality, and just by saying their names, magical powers could be drawn out. The horror of True Souls is out of this world. You’re just in the second Soul Seed level and you still need to go through many small stages,’ Black Sethe explained.

‘We call the Soul Seed levels the Soul Breeding Phase, which is divided into seven colored soul levels according to the colors of the rainbow. These correspond to the colors of the souls, and they are red, orange, yellow, green, blue, purple and indigo. Each level has a seed quantity requirement, and you’ll need to gather at least five soul species and merge them together to get to the next colored level. As for you, it is still way too early now; you’ve not even collected enough souls for the basic colorless second Soul Seed. When you’ve gathered more than five colorless Soul Seeds, the five Soul Seeds will start resonating and repulsing one another. This is to get rid of uncoordinated impurities and unwanted stuff, then they will finally merge together and you’ll enter into the actual seven-colored phase.’

‘As the number of seeds increases, because each seed is a condensation of your life’s major insights, as you accumulate more seeds, unwanted stuff will be rid of and what’s left will ultimately be similar. That is the purity rule of the soul. You need to merge your seeds together under such circumstances in order to enter the next stage.’

“It is… so far away…” Garen finally understood why Black Sethe kept repeating that it was still too early. Now he knew that it was indeed too early for him. Who knew that it would be so difficult to reach the True Soul stage, it was no wonder that even though there were so many powerful beings in the Ancient Endor, none of the demon lords climbed to a True Soul level.

“Actually, our demon lord class is just up to the green soul realm, and at that level, our spiritual energy alone was able to crush someone of an army level. You must also understand that only this level of soul realm, after being highly concentrated, will allow you to move through space without getting hurt. One’s physical body might be adjusted because of the rules of the universe space, but the souls which are highly concentrated would hardly suffer any major damage. And this is the one true eternity pursuit.”

Garen was caught deep in his thoughts.

He did not even notice Tu Lan leaving after the meal.

According to what Black Sethe described, he had only gathered one soul seed so far, which he’d gathered coincidentally in the Totem world.

‘You don’t have to overthink it, insights are the source of soul gathering, and the reason why it’s taking so long is mainly that you did not develop in this direction specifically. Only when your insights deepen to a certain level will it will start condensing, though most of the time, you might get inspired just by looking at a painting or hearing a song. When you have found out about the laws of knowledge, then your soul seed might start condensing, but there are also times when it will not condense no matter what.’

“Indeed, I don’t really need to think too much, there’s still a long way to go,” Garen nodded.

He stood up and left the restaurant, it was already evening. He walked towards his thermostatic tub in the Holy Fist Palace. The whole area was very big, and the entire palace was as big as a small town. Initially, it had a few big buildings, but later, because of its importance, it started expanding, and now the Holy Fist Palace occupied almost the entire peak of this mountain. Garen had his own private warm water supply tub, and similarly, some other important figures also had similar warm water tubs.

He passed through several halls and entered the bathing area, from which the sound of students’ giggles could be heard from the public bathing area on the other side.

With the help of a young female servant, Garen put on a bathrobe and went into his private bathtub. Every day at this time, he would choose to take a warm bath here to relax.

After about ten minutes, his cell phone rang; it was the routine report call.

Garen picked up the phone placed on the white stone stand.

It was a call from Ninox.

He answered the call.

“Master? There have been blood breeds around recently. Do you want me to bring sister Raffaele away?” Cece’s voice came from the other side of the phone.

Garen had sent Ninox to Grano to protect Raffaele, and once in a while, she would update Garen on the situation.

“If she wants to,” Garen replied with a low voice. Raffaele did have people who were important to her, and it was impossible for him to bring all of them here together. Even the important figures who lived in the Holy Fist Palace have reached double digits. If everyone were to bring people they cared for with them, it would not fit no matter how big this place was.

Grano

Ninox smiled bitterly while she looked at the witches’ gathering around her. Under the dark night, these witches were holding something like a glow stick in their hands and were coming from all sides of the forest.

They’d mistook her protection for monitoring, and it had almost led to a conflict.

Raffaele stood in front of her and stared at the phone in her hand.

Cece was a little frustrated, and she still did not understand the means of the witches. Therefore, although she was almost as strong as an upper-level human, she was careful so that she will not be discovered by them.

Having gotten Garen to pick up her call, Ninox looked at the blonde woman standing in front of her.

“Do you want to talk to the Master?” she put the phone down and handed it over.

Raffaele looked at the phone in her hand, remained silent for a moment and shook her head.

“I’m going to meet him.”

Her golden long hair was sparkling even under the moonlight as if it was molten spun gold.

“Are you really from the Holy Fist Palace?” she still had doubts.

“Of course,” Ninox answered helplessly.

Raffaele looked a little lost.

All this while, she knew about the strong human warrior in the Holy Fist Palace who had suddenly risen to fame, who was known as the Fist Saint. He was a human who was able to stand up against the top Death Apostle of the blood breed families. Although she knew that the Fist Saint was named Garen, she did not relate him to her ex-boyfriend, Garen.

What she did not expect was that both Garens were the same person.

When she got Ninox to admit that, the witches around her looked slightly surprised. They knew that their leader once had a wonderful first love, and that person was just an ordinary boy. But now it seemed like that person was actually as powerful as the Death Apostles, this made the witches who were already jealous of Raffaele, even more jealous.

Raffaele was born as the granddaughter of the leader of the witches and she was very talented, now even her boyfriend was someone who was as strong as the Death Apostles.

How was it fair for her to get all the benefits?

Raffaele suppressed the shock in her heart, turned around and said something to a trusted witch beside her. She told her to inform her grandmother about this as this issue might trigger something unpredictable.

“Now the Holy Fist Palace and the Blood Breeds are on bad terms, and Master is worried that the Blood Breeds might go up to extreme lengths and even try to harm you. Therefore, he sent me to protect you secretly and bring you back to the Holy Fist Palace if necessary.” Ninox could tell that Raffaele was not against the idea of leaving Grano, and she could not help but to feel relieved.

She calmed down and began to carefully analyze Raffaele, master’s ex-girlfriend.

She had exquisite features and a confident and beautiful appearance. She had golden, tassel-like long hair hanging down past her shoulders, which looked as if it was able to emit warmth like the sun, and it gave people a dazzling yet intense impression. Her strength was almost close to the level of a middle-level witch.

Ninox sighed slightly in her heart when she thought about the possibility of Raffaele getting back together with her master. With this thought in mind, she was a little uncomfortable, and she started looking at Raffaele with a slightly annoyed look.

“Get ready, when should we go?” she asked directly.

“As soon as possible.” Raffaele thought about it and answered immediately. Although she did not know why Cece’s gaze was a little hostile, she understood that something troublesome might have happened. “I don’t need to bring anything with me, so I can leave anytime.”

“Okay then. We will leave now!” Ninox nodded.

*********************

A peninsula beach in Asia

After the night fell, the surface of the sea was dark and deep, with sounds of waves hitting on the riffs occasionally.

The deserted seashore was filled with black steep reefs of various sizes, and the larger ones were stacked together with large gaps in between them. Seawater would seep through these gaps and cause a large number of sea creatures to get stuck in it.

Right at that moment, a group of men in black quickly changed in the gaps between the big reefs. They took off their black clothing and changed into a frogman outfit with a large-capacity oxygen tank on their back.

There were about eight to nine of them, each one of them was agile and quick, and they had all kinds of tools with them. It was obvious that they were prepared.

“We will start searching this area today, then group four’s mission will be completed,” One of the shadows whispered.

“Are you sure that the thing that we are looking for is near the sea? Why did we not find anything after so long? There are a dozen groups looking for it and it has almost been half a month, but there is still no sign of it,” another shadow asked casually.

“Who knows? We just need to follow the orders.”

“Let’s go, Brother Xu, Henry,” one of them had already put on the frogman outfit and threw a face mask to each of the two.

All of them donned a facemask and quietly plunged into the sea along the reef’s gaps, then rapidly disappeared into the sea like swimming fishes.

On the surface of the sea roughly ten sea miles away from the reef coast.

Multiple small warships and fishing boats with illuminated lighting poles constantly cruised on the sea. It seemed like they were patrolling, but also seemed like they were passing by slowly.

When their backs were facing the light, these boats would stop occasionally and a few frogmen would get up, and soon afterward, a few more frogmen would get into the water. As time went by, waves after waves of people went up and down the boats.

On a shore further away, there were groups of frogmen who constantly carried oxygen tanks into the sea.

A large amount of manpower was spent continuously searching this area of the sea.

About a hundred nautical miles away from the seashore of the search team, towards the left, there was a cruise-like luxurious white ship.

Hochman and two young women dressed in red and black dresses laughed and talked over at the ship’s rail, and he occasionally teased the two women to the point where they covered their mouths laughing.

The cruise was filled with well-dressed men and women conversing with one another politely; it seemed like a luxurious gathering for the upper-class society.

The sound of music played continuously in the hall of the cruise. There were beautiful and fashionable women walking around, and also waiters dressed in neat white suits who constantly delivered delicious food to the guests.

Chapter 744: Undercurrent 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Hochman had been invited to the after-party of the Asia Financial Summit. The cruise was sponsored by a financial tycoon in Asia. Hochman had always participated various financial gatherings on behalf of his family. As the first heir to his family’s properties, he was very famous among the beautiful young ladies in the party. He was handsome, talented and rich, so he could be considered as the model example of a bachelor.

Many ladies were willing to get to know him, and there were also quite a number of business tycoons who wanted to get on good terms with him. Even though this was a business gathering in Asia, Hochman did not need to reveal his identity as a member of the Holy Fist Palace; the status of his family alone could already be counted as the very best. Only a handful of people were able to compare their status with him.

While he casually chatted with the two ladies, Hochman slightly diverted part of his attention to the news coming from his earphone.

Asia was not only the place where the seventh mask is located; according to the news, it was also where the eighth and ninth masks were located. After putting in a lot of hard work and using all sorts of connections, Hochman found a sea which might be where the two masks were located. He quickly made use of the manpower in his family and began a large-scale search in the seashore vicinity.

In the world of ordinary people, Hochman was just the first heir to the American business family and the top student of a famous university. Even though he did well in the supernatural world and had a reputation of an upper-class member of the Holy Fist Palace, to ordinary people, even some powerful business tycoons were unlikely to reach the same level as him.

After all, there were too few supernatural beings. There were not more than ten thousand of them in the United States, including witches. It was worse in Europe since there were only a small number of blood breeds to begin with, and witches were restricted regionally as they could not leave their ancestral homes without their powers being greatly reduced.

As for those hidden top martial arts experts, if they weren’t madmen who pursued martial arts to an extreme, it would be impossible for them to surpass the limits of the human body, and there was an even lower chance of them wasting time on fighting.

This resulted from the fact that only less than 90 percent of the world’s population knew about the supernatural circle. It could be because most people felt that it was too complicated, but they mostly avoided it out of fear. Only upper-class humans with great influences could truly enter the circle.

Usually, most of the mysterious incidents around the world were started by this circle. But since most people were too afraid to face it, with the witches’ memory-erasing abilities and the blood breeds’ human-control abilities, after erasing their memories, the blood breeds and humans had even fewer interactions.

Whenever Hochman thought about it, he would have a sense of being isolated from the world. Just a moment ago, he had still been running errands for the Holy Fist Palace and had been worried about being attacked by the blood breeds. But now, it seemed as though he had returned to his carefree life as an ordinary human.

Beauty women, wine, good food, gambling, drugs, orgies, surfing, bungee jumping, illegal boxing, keeping various extremely dangerous pets just for show, et cetera, there were all sorts of exciting events that he got to do whatever he wanted.

This was the life that he’d once lived. It was a meaningless and corrupted life; all he did was enjoy.

But now.

Hochman stretched out his right hand and gently gripped it. He felt a truly rich and strong force circulating continuously within his body.

“This is what I wanted….”

He continued chatting with the two ladies with a straight face as though nothing happened. Occasionally, he could feel the envious gazes of the people around him, and also people pointing at him to introduce him to their children.

“I heard that Mr. Hochman has visited the Kato Businesses, can I know what do you think about my father’s company?” a girl in a red dress said while she walked towards him from the other side. The girl had a cool look on her face with a hint of arrogance. Her black curly hair was scattered around her shoulders, and she wore an exquisite diamond necklace around her fair neck.

Hochman looked at her carefully and immediately recognized her identity.

The elder daughter of Kato Businesses. Kato Businesses was a world-class financial group, and it was a highly-ranked company, not just in Asia but around the world, which could be compared to the huge companies such as the Primary Colors and Rexott. They had many crossover industrial businesses and countless properties.

He did not expect that someone of such high rank would participate in the Asia Summit Gathering, and he was a little surprised. Muneteru Riko’s identity was even more dazzling than his family’s. He did not see her just now, so she might have just boarded the cruise, or she stayed in her room all this time.

Hochman pondered on how to answer her question.

“Oh, it’s Ms. Muneteru Riko. Kato Businesses did leave a great impression; specifically, how distinct the hierarchy management was. There was a lot for me to learn from the visit.”

When the other two women heard the girl’s identity, they were surprised and sensibly left, leaving the two of them to talk at the side of the cruise.

“It seems like Mr. Hochman has a good impression of my father’s company. Maybe we will have the opportunity to work together,” Muneteru Riko smiled and said.

“What do you mean?” Hochman frowned slightly.

Muneteru Riko looked at the man standing in front of her, handsome, confident, and strong yet dangerous. Even though she was a black belt in karate, before this man, she still felt a strange sense of danger, as though she was standing before a fierce beast.

Rumors had it that Hochman had once killed a polar bear with his bare hands. It seemed like the information was indeed true.

After she calmed down, Muneteru Riko admired Hochman even more, if she could choose her marriage partner, she was willing to choose the man standing before her who was stronger than her.

“I heard that you are looking for an ancient mask that was lost in this area?” Riko asked softly. “About the search, my family might be able to help you in with the marine ships, and of course, manpower will not a problem.”

“Oh?” Hochman raised an eyebrow. Everyone in the Holy Fist Palace knew that Garen was looking for the Sleepless Faces mask, and everyone was using their connections to look for the mask. Under such situation, he could only rely on his own strength to search for it, since it is said that whoever found the mask would be rewarded personally by the Holy Fist Palace. At the very least, the reward would be an increase in lifespan and strengthening of physique.

He heard that Dahm had been rewarded previously, and his originally wounded skin had recovered in a very short period of time. His skin became even more delicate and fair, and after examining his skin with medical devices, he discovered that his physical function was much stronger than before. Also, he estimated that his maximum lifespan had been extended by ten years, which meant that he got to live ten years longer.

Many people who suffered from a chronic disease were interested, as their illnesses would be healed and their bodies would be strengthened. In addition to that, they got to be trained personally by the Holy Fist Palace, which was why many people who seek power were interested too.

Therefore, there were a lot more people searching for the masks.

“What do you mean?” Hochman knew that it was impossible for her to ask nothing in return.

“We hope to get your support in the North American businesses,” Muneteru Riko answered very honestly.

Hochman understood what she meant, as he’d heard that Kato Businesses was being attacked by a secret group in North America and so they were unable to successfully establish their business there.

“I can think about it, but my family…” before he could finish his sentence, there was an abrupt report coming from his earphone.

“We found it!! The two masks!! Hahaha! The twenty million bonus is ours!! Ah!!!” before they could finish cheering, he heard rounds of panicked screams.

“What monster is that!!?”

“Shoot! Shoot!! No!!”

Along with a ‘crack’ sound, he heard cracking sounds coming from the other side of the phone; apparently, their communication equipment was being crushed.

Hochman had a heavy look on his face. The blood breeds have made a move…

“Mr. Hochman?” Muneteru Riko who was standing in front of him reached out her hand and waved.

“Marshall, we were attacked by the blood breeds, and they coming after you! Be careful!!” an anxious voice from another channel was heard.  U.p..dated by .Com

“Understood, do you know how strong they are?” Hochman raised his hand and give Muneteru Riko a sign to wait.

“The detector indicates upper-class Blood Breeds! There are at least two of them!!” the one who was on the other side of the phone suddenly lowered his voice, probably because he was afraid that the Blood Breeds might hear him.

“Quick! Get on the boat!”

Hochman had a gloomy look on his face, and there were traces of extremely dangerous vibes radiating from his body.

“It seems like the Blood Breeds were fully prepared…. Don’t worry about me, retreat first. I will come later.”

“Understood!” then he disconnected.

Hochman worked out a kink in his neck as he looked at Ms. Muneteru Riko, who had a puzzled look on her face. He had spoken in German just now instead of standard international conversational English, therefore, she could not understand at all.

“Are you in a hurry?” Muneteru Riko asked curiously. “Do you need my help?”

“Hochman, you will not be able to escape today…”

Suddenly, a loud male voice reverberated on top of the cruise.

A fiery red shadow suddenly appeared on top of the cruise ship. It was a red-haired man with strong muscles all over his body. He was wearing a red leather coat, sunglasses even though it was at night, and had his hair styled into a flashy mohawk.

He jumped down from tens of meters of height.

Thump!!

The deck of the cruise was very sturdy; surprisingly, there was no indentation at all.

The man stood up, waved with his right hand and gathered crimson-colored flames into a long red sword. There were numerous mystical symbols on the sword.

“Sword of Daybreak!” he whispered.

In an instant, under the stunned gazes of the guests and their bodyguards, the red sword suddenly burst into a large red flame. Then, it morphed into a curvaceous flame woman figure and was launched towards Hochman at lightning speed.

At the same time, in the shadows behind Hochman, a black female shadow slowly appeared.

“Blood breeds’ holy weapon….?” Hochman took a step back, stretched his right hand out and gathered invisible air-currents in his palm. As his hair moved around constantly, his eyes vaguely turned black.

Under the illumination of the flame, the shadow behind Hochman suddenly became distorted and turned into a giant black shadow dragon which surrounded him silently.

Muneteru Riko took a few steps back from the suffocating air-current and fiery flames, frightened, and sat down on the ground. She raised her hands and covered herself while she stared blankly at what was happening right before her eyes. Everything had happened in a way that she was unable to understand, and she had goose bumps all over her body. She was feeling dangerous cold-induced tremors; despite the intense heat from the flames, all she felt were chills.

Chapter 745: Fierce Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Profound – War cry!”

Hochman looked at the flame figure launching towards him at a lightning speed and swept his right hand forward. He cut through the air with his hand and shot a few transparent air blades.

The half-moon-shaped air blades swirled towards the flame figure.

Boom!!

The air blades collided with the flame figure, creating a violent explosion. The crimson flames swept over the whole area like a tide that drowned the deck.

Some of the bodyguards were caught in the fire as they did not avoid it in time and screamed pitifully as they burned.

Some of them were blown away by the violent explosion and collided into the cabin. They were bleeding out, screaming in pain, wailing and panicking. Whether adults or children, the crowd broke out into a riot.

As the flames dispersed, Hochman held his shoulder with one hand; a black arrow had pierced through the back of his right shoulder. There was no bleeding or wounds, and even the black arrow was starting to slowly disappear.

But what bothered him was that he’d lost all sensation in that area of muscle that had been pierced by the arrow, as though he’d completely lost his shoulder. He could not even raise his right hand.

“Two Blood Breeds’ Holy Weapons…” he felt a sense of danger in his heart. If it was just one Holy Weapon, it will not have been a problem facing it head-on. However, his opponents were two combat type upper-class Blood Breeds, and they were armed with two extremely horrifying Holy Weapons. This was supposed to be a fight where two men fought with their bare hands, but suddenly, his opponent had a sharp sword in his hand, and the sword was something that belonged in a god-tier level.

***********************

Stupa underground palace

Dahm moved forward quickly, took a few turns at lightning speed and moved around the underground tunnel like a gust of wind. The air was rancid and the light was dim, and only the torchlight that he brought with him formed a beam of light.

Not long afterward, he quickly found a worshipping urn with a statue of God and stopped right in front of it.

The worshipping urn was located in a pitch black underground hall surrounded by bizarre Buddhist mural paintings on the wall. There were celestial nymphs of unidentified gender flying everywhere, their bodies were red in color but their eyes were green. Their eyes reflected like shiny green spots of light in the dark.

The statue of God was a bald-headed three-eyed man with his right palm placed in an upright position. He had a smile on his face and his eyes were slightly open. Inexplicably, it gave off an eerie feeling.

“This is not just any Buddha statue!” Dahm frowned slightly; they were worshipping an unknown statue instead of the almighty Buddha statue in the underground palace of a Buddhist stupa tarin…

He had hidden in this place for quite some time and he’d roughly studied Buddhism, but he did not recall any branch of Buddhism with a god that resembled the statue right in front of him.

However, all his doubts disappeared when he saw a black mask in front of the statue.

He quickly walked towards the mask, picked it up, stuffed it into the black bag that he had prepared, and tied it tightly. He glanced at his surroundings and swiftly retreated along the route that he used previously.

Suddenly, a red light flashed through the darkness and headed right at him.

The red light was as fast as lightning, but Dahm caught a glimpse of its face. The sharp and cold look on his face caused the pores on Dahm’s face to shrink instantly, and he even started to feel a slight pain.

He instinctively took a step back while he put his palms together against the red light.

He saw clearly that it was a long red sword, but under the illumination of the flashlight, it reflected a striking red light in the darkness.

Clang!!!

His palms came into contact with the red sword as he precisely caught the red sword in between his hands. At this instant, a red light started shining from the edge of the sword and hit on Dahm’s face heavily.

Bang!!

He released his hands and staggered back several steps. Blood dribbled down his hands as he covered his face with his hands.

AHH!!!

He screamed.

“My face…. my beauty….” Dahm covered his face with his hand, but blood did not stop trickling through his fingers.

It had not been easy for him to recover his beauty from his Master, but now, someone had ruined his face again!!!

“I’ll tear you apart!” Dahm immediately put down his hands. His eyes turned blood red and he was filled with a burst of murderous rage. Bits of black threads were moving all around him.

In a flash, the ground started to collapse silently, and he disappeared from where he was standing. Then, he turned into a bloody red shadow and ran straight in the direction of the red sword.

Instantly, a sudden burst of airflow rushed into the dark and narrow hall. The overwhelming atmosphere shook the hall and immediately occupied all the available space in the hall.

A series of continuous explosions were heard as Dahm constantly used his blood red hands to hit the red sword. He laughed fanatically and horrifyingly as he created countless shadows with his hands to throw it against his opponent who was in the darkness. He did not worry about his palms being cut open by the sword.

The owner of the red sword slowly appeared out of the darkness. He was a middle-aged man with whiskers all over his face. He was dressed in a black trench coat with a white shirt and jeans. The red long sword in his hand accurately blocked all of Dahm’s disorderly attacks.

The man had an indifferent look on his face as if he was completely unaffected by Dahm’s madness. No matter how swift and fierce Dahm’s crazy attacks were, his red longsword was able to fly up and down and accurately block all of Dahm’s attacks, as though he was blocking bullet shots.

Thump!!

With a ‘thump’ sound, Dahm was hit by a sudden huge counterattack.

“The bloody marshal, Dahm,” the man with whiskers raised the sword single-handedly and embedded the sword into the ground of the underground palace. Then, he took a lighter and cigarette from the pocket of his trousers. He lit the cigarette and inhaled deeply. “As I expected. Although your power output is strong, your endurance is too weak.”

His eagle-like eyes were fixed on Dahm, and even the darkness was unable to impede his gaze. He clearly saw Dahm’s chest heaving violently.

Previously, the two of them had been constantly attacking and defending; they did their utmost best and did not hold back at all. Therefore, although their power output was horrifying, the amount of energy they consumed was absolutely shocking.

“Are you mocking me by putting your weapon down right in front of me?” Dahm’s face was hidden in the dark, it seemed like he finally finished venting and calmed down.

“What do you think?” the man with whiskers reached for his cigarette, inhaled and exhaled the smoke through his nostrils.

“After I kill you and break through as a Death Apostle, I will kill the guy named Garen. Then I will light a big firework there. Boom!” he mimicked the action of an explosion. “And everything will quiet down at last…”

“You have a death wish!!”

Dahm’s figure instantly turned into a red shadow and rushed forward. In the next moment, all the blood on his body had gathered on his hands.

‘Chi-chi-chi’! a number of transparent fine threads flew out and shrouded the entire hall as if there had been an explosion. A large number of silk threads burst outward and cut through every corner of the hall.

Dahm elongated all of the silk threads. As long as one came into contact with a body, it would instantly cause one’s blood to explode. This was Dahm’s scariest area-wide attack!

An all-direction, encompassing shroud of countless silk threads.

The man with whiskers inhaled deeply from his cigarette and the cigarette suddenly lit up.

Clang!!

He suddenly pulled the long sword from the ground with his right hand and rushed forward!

As the sword was being pulled out of the ground, Dahm could not see any continuity in his movement, it was as though the sword had suddenly appeared in his hand, or he did not put down his weapon since the very beginning.

The red sword was shining as it slashed down towards the countless silk threads.

***********************

With a ‘clang’ sound, the air blades cut through the flame figure.

“The blood breeds has been planning for a long time, I need to leave immediately!!” Hochman finally understood. It was impossible for the Blood Breeds to simply send the two of them here, they must’ve concocted an entire plan. If it were up to him, he would surround three out of four exits, leaving just one exit open. From there, his prey would get hurt while they tried to escape while a faint hope was dangled before them. As they escaped, it would consume their energy, and he would easily get the final victory.

The red-haired man standing in front of him giggled and waved his long flame sword once again.

Whoosh-whoosh!!

Several flame clusters were spilled from the sword. The flame clusters that fell onto the ground started burning. While it burnt, it started to deform like a like plastic clay and turned into petite female flame figures, which looked exactly the same as his initial attack.

In a blink of an eye, there were three more female flame figures on the deck. They opened their mouth and roared, but only the sound of flame crackling can be heard.

As the red light flashed, the three flame figures rushed towards Hochman. On the other hand, the red-haired man who was standing a distance away slowly moved backward, swung his longsword again and created a few more human-figured flame clusters.

Hochman had a gloomy look on his face and quickly dodged towards his left. A black light was coming after him from behind and went through the clothes on his waist; he was almost shot.

He did not have too much time to think, activated Double Fist and immediately launched a punch forward!!

Bang!!

There was a shallow indentation on the deck. The impact was like a thunderclap which made everyone’s feet numb.

A huge dark shadow burst forward on top of Hochman’s punches and the very air was being stirred. There were fluctuations and vibrations just like the Profound – War Cry previously.

As expected, along with three ‘chi’ sounds, three air blades were fired from Hochman’s fist and respectively split through the three flame figures.

Hochman fiercely rushed towards the red-haired man and slammed his foot towards him.

Boom!!

As the deck started shaking, Hochman’s speed increased rapidly, with a huge impact like a tank.

At the same time, the three flame figures were being split apart. Even the flames that spilled out were being shaken up, and the time it took to recreate a human figure was delayed.

The red-haired man’s face changed slightly. He tried to dodge, but he had not expected Hochman’s speed to increase rapidly once again. Along with a muffled sound, another shallow indentation appeared on the deck once again.

Hochman abruptly appeared right before him, and his strong arm was like a sharp blade that was swung down towards him.

His hand-blade cut through the air and made a harsh screeching sound, similar to the screeching sound made by combat jets midflight, and a faint white line of smoke trailed the back of his palm.

Thump!!!

The red-haired man and Hochman slammed into each other, as though a tank had collided with an elephant. The two of them was taken aback and rolled onto the ground. By chance, Hochman dodged the two black arrows launching towards him from behind.

Instantly, the two of them started grappling with each other on the deck. The red-haired man was completely suppressed as four arms overlapped. Every few seconds, he would be punched in the chest which caused him to continuously cough up blood. All he could do was use his red longsword to shield his body.

Thump!

Hochman punched a hole through his chest, but since he was able to heal rapidly, his flesh and blood wrapped around Hochman’s hand and trapped it tightly.

“Fire!!”

He finally shouted. He took the opportunity while Hochman was trapped, and his whole body started burning in flame. He made a flame ring and hit it straight into Hochman.

Bang!!

The two of them were finally separated. The red light shone brightly as the huge impact threw Hochman away. However, the direction that he flew to was a little strange; as though he was a bat, he turned around in mid-air and headed towards the direction of the sea.

“Don’t let him escape!” the red-haired man shouted.

Chapter 746: Fierce Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A black shadow quickly caught up. Impressively, it was that black-shirt girl who shot that cold arrow, but her speed was slightly slower. When she heard the sound of water while waiting beside the boat, she rushed towards the flange of the boat, and looked down on the floating Black Water Flower.

“Damn it!” The black-shirt girl slapped the side of the boat, smashing the edge of the boat-sides. For a moment, a deep dent appeared.

Boom!

Suddenly, a fist smashed the sides of the boat underneath her. The fist opened up into a palm, and it fiercely caught something with one grab.

Thump!

The black-shirt girl looked mad, as her right thigh was caught. She violently tried to pull away, but she lost her balance and fell to the ground with a thump.

“Profound – Disordered Flow!” Hochman said in a low voice, from the outer side of the boat.

In a split second, the edge of the boat-side lit up with a bunch of golden sparks. Then, a tearing and piercing metal friction sound rang out.

In the huge spark, the boat side started ripping apart, revealing the situation inside. Both of Hochman’s arms wildly chopped forwards. With every chop, the strength of his speed hit a terrifying level. Although it is not as violent as before, where it gave out a white whistle, each karate chop he did was as if it was a real blade instead, violently chopping up the Blood Breed woman’s body. Suddenly, fresh blood shot out.

In a short second, Hochman had chopped out a dozen knives towards the front. All of them were on the Blood Breed woman’s body. Especially her chest, it was chopped until it was bloody and all caved in. With one violent kick, the Blood Breed woman flew out. Then, Hochman creased his brows; if his right shoulder wasn’t attacked, causing a loss of force in his right arm, he could have ripped the Blood Breed woman apart just now.

Stepping onto the edge of the wrecked boat, he borrowed that strength and like a bat, he flapped the sleeves of his robe and flew away. He drifted on the surface of the water, not falling into the sea yet. An explosive sound could be heard coming from both of Hochman’s legs.

Under his feet, water splashes burst out. It was shocking to find that both his feet were fiercely stamping on the water surface. Borrowing this strength, again, he stepped on the water like a water spider, traveling a far distance. In the blink of an eye, he had exceeded more than two hundred meters.

“The most important thing now is not the battle with two of the Blood Breeds. Instead, it is about finding the masks that Master needs, and then we leave!” Hochman’s aim was very clear. He immediately stepped into the water and left, creating a huge thrust with every terrifying explosive power. It allowed him to travel at a much higher speed compared to the fastest motorboat.

The cruise ship behind him quickly became smaller, darker, and more blurry in the evening.

*******************

Holy Fist Palace.

“Both Marshalls were attacked?”

Garen picked up a chess piece for a moment, then gently put in down in front of the board.

He was playing chess with Tu Lan, sitting in a small and quiet room that was not more than a few square meters wide. On the side, a huge letter “quiet” written with a black ink on a white paper, in a Sina character.

The Sina text was very similar to the ones on the Earth were Garen lived. However, the size Sina was far less than China, where the size of it was more than a million square kilometers. Instead, it was a combined series of smaller countries like Sina. Asia and Europe were very similar too — there were dozens of large and small countries. Some of them were strong, and some of them were weak. Furthermore, invaded countries that participated in second world war were also included. Those that once had the world’s first Air Force, and wanted to conquer the world with force.

“Do you need me to take a look at it?” Tu Lan looked at Garen, and put down his chess piece.

“No need.” Garen shook his head slightly, “everyone has their own things to do.”

As he put the chess piece down lightly, he removed Tu Lan’s dragon piece immediately. He saw Tu Lan’s face turned green. Even though this old-school Blood Breed had been alive for many years, all he could feel was his IQ being crushed whenever he was with Garen.

There was no bigger picture, nor was there any tricks, but just some partial battling involved. With every partial battle, Garen would win nine battles out of ten of them.

His calculation and deducing skills made people boil with anger. Using such simple calculation skills to crush people gave them no chance to resist. So much that seeing the chess board now gave Tu Lan a bit of a trauma since she had never won before.

Or maybe my chess skills are too weak; if I was replaced by chess player who was strong at overlooking the bigger picture, they would definitely win, Tu Lan comforted herself.

“Are you men in position?” Garen suddenly asked a no-brainer question.

Tu Lan nodded.

“They have been in their position since ten minutes ago,” the both of them packed the chess pieces and put them into the chess basket.

“Let’s wait awhile longer.” After Garen kept the chess pieces, he reclined on the chair and began to repose by closing his eyes.

He was really calm.

Tu Lan could not help but look at him. The Older Generation Blood Breeds were attacking two of his strongest and most important men. Yet, he was no the least bit affected by it.

Garen’s expression was calm. In his mind, the black-covered Demonic Book slowly floated and rotated around slowly. It was as if his whole body was spreading out a dull golden light. Ever since he had grasped the true meaning of Holy Phoenix, the Demonic Book became like that.

In reality, more and more martial arts steps were recorded in the Demonic Book. Even Dahm’s and Hochman’s two new Waterbird Fists were recorded by Garen. Along with this recording, the Demonic Book was becoming stranger and stranger. Originally, it was just a simple notebook, but it slowly turned into something that had some magical effect that linked Garen’s brain with the Demonic Book.

Most times, Garen could feel the Demonic Book, as if he was pregnant with the Soul Seed. Sometimes, he could even feel it’s beating, just like a beating heart.

As time passed, Garen sat as still as a monk — he did not move at all. There wasn’t even a single change in his expression, just as if he was sleeping.

**********************

Boom!

In the Underground Palace, it was densely packed with red long knives and countless wired strings fighting against each other. There was no crisp sound coming from the metal, but only a combination of countless sounds, forming a muffled explosion.

The wired strings retreated. However, Beard pushed forwards, charging towards Dahm.

“Profound – Bloody Night!” Dahm shouted violently. Countless wired strings suddenly emerged in a pale-red color indicating a large number of spirits that were flowing along the wired string. It was as if a fluid-like liquid covered the whole strong, forming a huge red net, rushing towards Beard.

Chi chi chi chi chi!

A large number of wired strings carried a horrifying cutting-air sound rushed towards Beard. Some of the stone sculpture decorations that stuck out in some of the halls were cut off with just a silent and gentle graze. However, before the broken pieces fell into the floor, it was cut through once more with the flying wired strings and they all turned into countless tiny debris. With a bang, the debris exploded immediately.

That was Dahm’s explosive power. After going through the improvement of Waterbird Fist, he used a huge amount of resources to collect and organize the martial arts information. Then, the most scientific method of deduction was used to calculate the most suitable and strongest battle method for himself.

“Holy Technique – Faded.”

The knife in Beard’s hand was as red as blood. The front of it faced the red net, like a lightning in the night sky, or a laser. Only when it lit up did it cut through the big red net. The moment the red knife met the string, a bright light reflection from the top of the knife lit up with a clang. Unexpectedly, it cut the wired net into half.

For the first time, Dahm’s face revealed a grave expression.

He waved both his arms, and once again shot out many wired strings. Among three of them continuously replenished the wired strings that were broken. The rest were silently hiding in the dark, quietly creeping behind Beard.

Chi chi!

Right above Beard’s head, a huge chunk of heavy stone was cut through with a string.

Boom! Just as the huge stone fell down, Beard’s sword shattered it into tiny pieces that eventually fell onto the floor, like raindrops.

“I can’t remember clearly how many years it has been, but other than the Death Apostles, there weren’t many Blood Breeds who survived until their fifth move in front of me.” Beard removed his cigarette bud and blew out a mouthful of smoke, “let’s see if you can break the record today.”

“The fourth move!” As Beard’s pupils narrowed, his whole body gave out an extremely dangerous atmosphere, “red lotus!”

The moment the sound rang, Beard flew forwards, moving towards Dahm’s direction.

In mid-air, with a clang that rang out beside him, four blood-red sword reflection lit up. The reflection of the sword continued to light up to a point where it kept spinning, as if it was a windmill, turning in the wind. The speed of the spin became quicker and quicker. From a distance, it looked like a red lotus flower that did not stop spinning.

Bang bang bang!

The red lotus immediately broke open countless wired strings, as he was getting closer to Dahm.

In a split second, this was the first time Dahm felt a life-threatening situation where his nerves were constantly agitated. It was not the same as his past experiences. The true strength of this enemy in front of him far exceeded his. Since when did Blood Breed has such scary Upper-level Blood Breed? Even if it was a Death Apostle, it was not estimated as such.

Seeing as the red lotus was closing in fast, Dahm’s brain could not help but flash across different solutions. However, there was nothing he could use that would truly defeat the enemy in front of him. Against his enemy, his tough metal strings were like weak ropes; once hit, then it breaks. If he directly slashed forwards, Dahm would still be able to sneak an attack on Beard’s back. But with the speed that it’s spinning in now, there would be no flaws all around him.

This was the first time — the first time he was faced with a single opponent, and Dahm wanted to retreat. Suddenly, he thought about the information he saw not long ago. There were five families in Blood Breed, and every family had a unique Holy Technique.

However, it was weird that among five families, only four were Death Apostle families. Whereas when he linked up all the information he had seen, the last one was an Upper-level Blood Breed that acted as Landlord.

Dahm’s expression finally changed. In the information, the only non-Death Apostle family’s Landlord was suddenly in the shape of Beard. It was also said that he used a long knife as a weapon. He was known as the world’s famous top-level knife master.

The red lotus became closer, and now he was close at hand. Dahm wanted to get out, but it was as if his body was immobilized. There was an unknown attraction that locked him onto the ground so that he could not move.

“Damn it!” Dahm wildly raised both his hands. In this life and death situation, he did not care much. If he did not retaliate, he would be chopped into minced meat!

“Profound… First Star,” a low, yet familiar voice appeared in his consciousness.

Suddenly, Dahm’s eyes were wide open. He could feel something that did not belong to him in his body. However, it was also an oddly familiar violent strength surging outwards.

Whiz…

In the blink of an eye, countless wired strings gathered in his hand and turned into one blood-colored spear that slowly suspended beside his face.

“Flight of the Evil Phoenix…”

At this moment, Dahm finally realized that the original Waterbird Fist was the final secret of the terrifyingly brutal Profound technique.

The subtle wind flew past as the warmth brushed his face, like there was a voice reverberating in the wind.

Could you hear it? It was the sound of the wind…

Unconsciously, Dahm closed his eyes.

Then, the sound of birds chirping rang out.

The red lotus froze in mid-air, stopping less than one meter away from Dahm. In the red light, his pupils shrank quickly. An overwhelming sense of crisis was suddenly all over his body, giving him goosebumps. In the reflection of his red pupils, a huge transparent pair of airflow wings slowly appeared on his back.

Retreat!

As this had just idea risen, an overwhelming wind blew from the front. Something in the wind seemed to be mixed with something inexplicable.

Chapter 747: Fierce Battle 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Holy Fist Palace.

Garen suddenly opened his eyes.

“It’s time.”

He looked towards Tu Lan, who was sitting in the same position beside him.

“Go. I will compensate you for what you’re worth.”

“Are you sure?” Tu Lan let out a breath, shook his head in annoyance, and stood up, “Forget it, I’ll be generous this time.”

She slowly walked out of the quiet room and towards the direction of her residence.

Garen sat alone in the quiet room. His expression was indifferent. His gently stroked the chessboard, thinking.

“It’s getting closer, and closer now,” BlacK Sethe’s voice was low. His voice seldom came up lately. He was not like before, where he was very chatty. Instead, he had become more and more silent, as if his every word was like gold.

“The Old Generation Blood Breed have joined forces to attack you, and they are sending out men with strengths who aren’t those with typical power. Are you sure that you’re not worried at all? The five big Holy Technique Family at least have around ten Upper-level Blood Breed. At first, the Wellington Family only had three Upper levels. But if they add the Holy Weapon, your people will suffer heavy losses.”

Garen shook his head.

“Everything has been arranged. If there’s a problem, there is nothing else I can do. Just as I’ve said before, for Holy First Palace to battle against the entire Old Generation Blood Breed, our strengths are still considered very weak. That is why we cannot leave this place even if they ambush us.”

“I have this sixth sense lately that it’s best if you and your men don’t attack,” Black Sethe reminded.

“Oh? Why?” Garen was slightly taken aback.

“There’s no reason why, because I have no idea too. It’s just a feeling,” Black Sethe’s voice slowly faded into the air, and it no longer rang.

Garen stood alone in the quiet room, with a flash of doubt in his eyes.

*********************

The strong winds blew against the inner walls of the Underground Palace’s Hall. The whole Underground Palace trembled and swayed violently.

Buss!

Dahm’s eyes looked lost. His whole body couldn’t help but be carried upwards by his wings. The transparent wings continuously fluttered. Beside him, the red spear that was like a red rifle floated beside him and he caught it in his hands. The rifle opened up circles and circles of transparent ripples — that was the powerful effect from the vibration in the air.

However, Beard was immediately held in mid-air by the violent surge of air. He could not move at all, and in the blink of an eye, it was as if his whole body was tied around with an invisible rope.

“What… Is this move…?” All of a sudden, Beard’s expression calmed down, as he looked downwards at Dahm.

Chi!

The red rifle impressively shot out a red line.

Chi chi! Chi chi chi chi chi!”

Within seconds, a big piece of red wire burst out from the rifle and aimed towards Beard from all directions.

With one puff, and just with a blink of an eye, Beard was suspended in mid-air. His body was penetrated into a bloody mess by countless of wires.

“This time, you win,” Beard said in a deep voice.   U.p..dated b.y Box novel. com

With a thump, he turned into a cloud of blood mist, disappearing completely. Countless bloody wires also fell to the ground, returning to its original invisible, yet transparent color.

All the dust settled.

Only then did the hazy look in Dahm’s eyes slowly cleared. He absentmindedly looked at both his hands and then at the broken wires that had fallen everywhere on the hall’s floor. He took a deep breath in.

“This was the strength that master has hid in my body…” He muttered. Suddenly, he felt his whole body weakened. The energy he felt in his body just now suddenly faded away.

He struggled his way to the location in which Beard exploded, but he could not find any of the things he left behind; only found some shreds of his shirt.

“Didn’t I kill him? But at least he is heavily injured.” Holding the mask tightly in his hand, he could suddenly feel the fine sand falling from above his head.

“This place is going to collapse soon. I must leave quickly.”

He clenched his teeth and mustered the last strength in his body. Dahm quickly formed an afterimage and rushed out towards the direction of the exit.

Not long after he left, on the left side of where Beard disappeared and in one of the dark corners, Beard’s shadow appeared once again. His whole body was covered in holes from the penetration of the wires. Only his brain was not pierced through but other parts, including his heart, was no exception.

At this moment, he seemed unusually weak. He was using the red spear to hold his body up.

“I miscalculated… That burst of strength was completely different from that of Dahm before. That is definitely not him. Holy Fist Palace…” He felt slight chills in his heart. To be able to influence his disciple even through such long distance, and made him much stronger in an instant, this method was unimaginable.

This time, before he could use his strongest Holy Technique move, he was defeated by that powerful and terrifying move.

“Next time… Next time, I will win, Dahm of Holy Fist Palace. Next time, you will not be so lucky…” His low voice echoed the hall but he instantly disappeared on the spot.

*********************

On the coastline.

Hochman was like a gigantic black lizard, speeding in a zig-zag manner along the reefs by the sea. He was extremely fast. His body was as light as the waterbird. By the looks of it, it seemed like he was as light and effortless as if he was weightless.

Suddenly, he raised his head, looking far away at a distant beach that was cluttered with dead bodies. The blood was flowing into the sea, faintly dying the sea water red. He did not know how much blood there was.

“It should be here…” Hochman tried to adjust his earpiece. “Group five, is anyone there? Answer me! Group six, and group seven to group twelve, if you’re alive, say something!”

His earpiece gave out a fizzle sound. After a while, there was a faint sound coming from beside his ears.

“Marshall, we are here.”

Hochman was slightly stunned because the sound did not come from his earpiece but from the waters on his left.

He quickly got closer to the sea surface and saw the shallow part of the sea. In the sea water between the reefs and the bloodied bodies, the water was stained red. The people here were all covered in injuries of an infant’s bite mark. Their faces looked pale and weak, as if they did not have the energy to move.

“You’re the team leader for group nine?” Hochman frowned as he walked over. Suddenly, he stopped, “How did you end up here alone? What about the mask?”

“The mask… It’s with me, Marshall. I have a heavy injury… on my back. I can’t move…” The man had no expression in his eyes. It looked like he was moments from dying. He forcefully lifted his hand up, as if wanting Hochman to save him. “Save me, Marshall… Save…”

He trembled as he used his other hand to take out the mask from his arms. Surprisingly, it was two masks; the densely packed eyes on the forehead was the biggest prove.

As Hochman looked at it, his eyes moved around left and right, alert of his surroundings. Unconsciously, his palm gently grazed a piece of gravel on the reefs at the side.

Only then, he slowly walked towards that wounded person.

Roar!

In a flash, a cloud of violent flames exploded and spread outwards without indication, taking that wounded person as the center. The red flames were like the most beautiful fireworks. Instantly, it wounded person was covered by the sea and then, it rolled towards Hochman’s direction.

Hochman did not react in time and was quickly swept in by the flames. He only managed to raise both his hands in front to block his body.

Bang!

He could feel himself being violently tossed outwards by a huge impact. Immediately after, he had hit the corners of the sharp reefs that were behind him.

With a low humph, he opened his palms. With the notion that the rock was on the right side, he hit the rock behind him. Then, he rolled onto the ground.

Clank!

Bullet-like stones hit the right side of the air where it originally looked empty — there wasn’t a single person. But after the stone hit, a transparent invisible figure emerged out of nowhere.

“You can’t run, Hochman!” The figure laughed grimly as he flew towards Hochman, who rolled away. The silver flashes in his hand seemed like some metal weapon.

However, when he saw Hochman, the invisible figure was suddenly shocked. He had now returned to the center of the explosion and found the two masks. There were slight damages on the marks, but it wasn’t destroyed in the explosion. Only the sharp edges that bulged out were blown off.

“I am sick of using these explosive traps.” Hochman got up from the water in slight dismay. He looked to the left and right of his surroundings but no one else appeared, “more than ten of my teams are lost… I will note down this fight.”

He looked intensely at the invisible figure who was standing in front of him. Out of the blue, a fish dived into the crashing waves of the sea. With a plop, he quickly jumped into the sea. After a few strokes, he was nowhere to be found.

The invisible figure did not go after him. He or she only looked at the direction in which Hochman left at and frowned slightly.

Minutes after, two of them who attacked Hochman before this appeared beside him — one female and one male Upper-level Blood Breed. The red-haired man held a red longsword in his hands, as always; the girl was dressed in black, like ink, from head to toe.

“Should we go after him?” The red-haired man asked. It seemed like the both of them who rushed forwards took this invisible figure as their leader.

“No need.” The invisible figure raised his hand, ‘Hochman… He is very cautious and cunning. If he had hesitated for a while more, he would have been walking any more. This bastard is quite something.”

“How should we explain this to the Chief?” The black-shirt girl asked quietly.

“I’ll go and explain it myself. This was not our original purpose this time, it’s just a cover-up. Where are the real masks?” The invisible figure asked.

“They are already aboard Halda’s ship. I believe no one will know it’s there?” The red-haired man laughed, “I don’t think that Hochman would know that he brought back the fake version. But since that thing looked like it survived the explosion, he might think that it’s real.”

“If it was the real masks, forget the explosion, even the lightly force could ruin it.” The invisible figure shook his head, “once Hochman brings those things back, we would have more or less achieved our aim. I think the items have arrived at Blood Union’s HQ.”

“Thank goodness for Lord’s arrangements. If not, how else would the fifth Holy Technique Chief obey your arrangements?” The black-shirt girl praised her leader.

The invisible man smiled and said nothing more.

“Let’s go. Everything has been arranged. Now, let’s just wait for Chief’s news.”

“Understood.” They slowly walked away from where they stood, and towards the deep coastal land. There were already people waiting for them there.

Chapter 748: Fierce Battle 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On the sea not far from this territorial waters, a cargo ship was slowly moving into the deeper ends of the water. The ringing of the ship’s whistle was mixed with the sounds of seagulls. The crew members wore a blend of blue and white clothes, walking back and forth on the deck.

“There are a little more goods this time… And, the price has been doubled. Has peak session been brought forwards?”

On the side of the boat, a few of the shipment’s businessmen stood together. They were all old customers who often operate the ships under the same sea transportation group, but this time was different than the rest. The amount of money needed to be paid this time had doubled. And, their attitude this time was intransigent. There was no way they could have bargained. If it wasn’t for the unexplainable loss of cargo ships used for shipment, it would be unlikely that why have been so reluctant to promise a price rise.

“I heard some information saying that a lot of ships nearby has been looking for something lately, like a treasure,” another businessman said in a low voice.

At this moment, a cold color suddenly flashed under one of the few women’s eyes. When she turned around, she did not know when a younger girl with black-shirt appeared.

“Excuse me, my niece is here,” she said with a smile to a few people.

“Let’s go. Let’s talk more inside. The wind here is strong.” Several businessmen smiled back with sincerity.

The businesswoman walked towards her niece’s direction.

“What’s wrong?” Her eyes suddenly turned red. Impressively, she was a Blood Breed hidden into a human.

“Upper level Grina, it seems like a Holy First Palace’s Blood Breed has followed us on board.” The appearance of this girl looked young. But in fact, she was already more than hundred years of age. Her expression looked serious, “I was observing her, but just now, I didn’t think that she would disappear. That’s why I wanted to report this to you immediately.”

Grina was the Castine Family’s Upper-level Blood Breed. Although the Chief did not declare that he wanted to start a war with the Holy Fist Palace, as an Older Generation Blood Breed member, her family approved of the perspective as per the people in the secret party. Holy Fist Palace was the root of causing this chaos. Only by removing Holy Fist Palace and the behind-the-scenes manipulator, Garen, can they restore the order of the world.

“This time, we’ve joined five other Upper levels. More than half of the Blood Union’s combat Upper levels are here. We are all gathered here from all over the world, and these are the top elites of the Blood Breed. Even if we lost our enemy, what is there to fear?” Grina frowned as she said.

“I have a feeling that something is not right,” the young girl said worriedly. “I have a feeling that this Blood Breed has been following us from the start, and we’ve only noticed her now.”

“You say it’s her? That female Blood Breed?” Grina asked in return. “Which level?”  U.p.dated by Box n o v e l. com

“Should be Lower level…”

“Why are you scared of a mere Lower level person?” Grina was frustrated. Looking at that complaint female Blood Breed, she did not fight it in her heart.

“But… But I have a feeling that there is something fishy about that female Blood Breed!” The young girl argued.

“Alright, I’ll go take a look at it personally, and I’ll catch this bastard.” Grina said plainly, “Bring some men to patrol the area. It’s just a fish that escaped the net.”

“Well… Alright,” the young girl could only nod her head.

After her subordinate left, she started wandering around alone on the cargo ship. It looked like she was taking a stroll, but in reality, her senses had been magnified. She was constantly paying attention to her surrounding situations.

The cargo ship was huge. Ninety out of a hundred person were container cargos that each divided into a dark storage warehouse.

Bang!

She slowly pushed open a metal warehouse door. Some of the darker spaces inside suddenly appeared before her eyes.

Grina walked in confidently. She had casually walked around and inspected several warehouses. This was now the fifth area.

The worker who opened the door gave it a pat.

“You can take a look yourself. When you need to lock the door, just give me a shout.”

“Great, thank you.” Grina smiled as she slipped him some cash. At once, the worker beamed with delight and walked away.

Walking into the warehouse area, Grina looked left and right. There was no one in here, but she did not relax. This warehouse area was the most important place because the core items this time were hidden in this huge warehouse area.

Hence, Grina looked unusually serious.

“Is there something wrong here?”

“Nothing is wrong. My main items are all there. I won’t be able to relax if I don’t take a look first.” Grina was aware of her reply. Though it did not feel right, and so, she turned around. She saw a girl dressed in black windbreaker was slowly closing the warehouse’s door. One click, and it was locked.

The person’s eyes glowed red. In fact, she was also one of the Blood Breeds on the ship. It was just that Grina could not remember such person on her team.

“Which group are you from? Didn’t you guys go to the Eastern District?” Grina said with some dissatisfaction.

The female Blood Breed suddenly revealed a strange smile. That smile was just like a human, as if there was no self-consciousness – a smile in which she was not aware of.

“Grina, long time no see. You don’t even recognize me now…”

She slowly said, with a light, yet lazy tone.

Hearing this familiar tone, Grina’s heart suddenly jumped. In a second, her expression turned dignified. Her eyes were staring at the female Blood Breed opposite of her. She is merely just a Lower level Blood Breed, she should not have been able to resist the suppression of her Upper-level position.

However, this person completely ignored this suppression, and slowly walked towards her.

********************

Holy Fist Palace.

Tu Lan’s naked body was lying in a boiling hot blood pool. The blood-red pool water gave out a strong smell. For the Blood Breeds, this was the highest quality of enjoyment. But she could not feel a single thing. Instead, she slightly frowned as more than half her body was soaked in blood.

If anyone could go into this secret room and saw her current face, they could see it from her lifeless eyes that she had lost all consciousness.

Hiss…

The room’s stone door was slowly pushed open. Garen’s shadow appeared by the side of the blood pool, and he used his backhand to shut the stone door.

As he looked at Tu Lan who was in the blood pool, he gave a slight frown. He then walked to the side and pressed some buttons. Suddenly, the boiling of the blood pool became much smaller. It also revealed Tu Lan’s naked upper body.

There was no trace of lust in Garen’s eyes. He only walked to the back of Tu Lan. While he stood there, he looked down.

The view from his angle was great. On the back of Tu Lan’s vest, a white-raised spike by the side of the pool had deeply penetrated her skin.

“This such a wonderful ability…” Garen sighed.

“Using the bloodline would create the ability to space jump. The Death Apostles in this world also have a powerful side.” Black Sethe also sighed, “We just don’t know how long Tu Lan would need over there. First, suicide; then, use her own Blood Breed’s bloodline to resuscitate her body. Thanks to you, for figuring something like that out. I don’t know how long the Death Apostles of the Blood Breed take to train their bodies. But once they give up, it will be a huge loss. Have you thought about how you’re going to repay her?”

Garen shook his head slightly.

“She, herself has died. If her body dies here, Blood Nuclear will have fragmentation. Originally, she should have turned into black ashes immediately because the Blood Nucleus isn’t providing the blood essence. But since she’s using the Blood Breed’s blood pool, it can keep her body activated and maintain its original shape.”

“But if there isn’t any Blood Nucleus, and instead, we use other Blood Breed’s blood essence to sustain her, won’t this body lose Tu Lan’s bloodline? Then what use will she have? I think this blood essence would only sustain this body for another two hours only,” Black Sethe couldn’t solve it.

“We also did think of this,” Garen took out a thick blood that emitted a crystal-red color. It looked just like human blood, or if not, the same. Garen gently and carefully held it in his hands, as if resisting from breaking it.

“This is the blood essence that Tu Lan left with me before. No matter how the situations go, whether win or lose, I will inject this into her body in the last phase of the two hours. Then, I will welcome her back on her return.”

“You bunch of Death Apostles are using the Resuscitation Ability at its ultimate level,” Black Sethe exclaimed.

Garen gave a slight smile.

If this technology couldn’t be studied, then won’t that be a waste of his experience on high-precision technology in the Totem world, as well as his own transplanted heart? Anyhow, he was once the top biologist and biochemist.

Furthermore, he would not worry about the reproduction of Blood Breeds with this method because these blood essences were obtained from the Older Generation Blood Breeds, who were captured in the previous war and drained alive. With such a small pool of blood, he had killed hundreds of Lower level Blood Breeds. Yet with this sacrifice, this would only sustain a Death Apostle’s body for two hours. Even in the two hours, if she faces a life-threatening situation in the middle of it, her body would be ruined. After thousands of years of refining this body, it would be destroyed, once and for all. This was also one of the first reasons of Death Apostle Wellington’s hatred towards Garen. He had taken many years to refine his body, and just because he wasn’t careful, it was destroyed by Garen. Hence, he seemed so weak from the back.

Regarding this method, even if the Older Generation Blood Breed’s Death Apostles had studied this method, they could not use it nor, would they dare to use it. The number of Blood Breeds would be decreasing as the war went on. No matter if it’s the Leader of Blood Breed, they would still need their men to get their hands on the resources and forces for them to provide themselves the information and resources. Else, even if the Death Apostles are stronger, when they are against human’s top weapon, they would be destroyed once the attack is focused on them. Then, they would resuscitate. Another point would be that this questions one’s moral belief. Just as in the human world, some people would bathe in human blood, and hence kill hundreds of people. However, once they were exposed, then these people would immediately be treated as the public’s enemy. It would be the same with the Blood Breed, especially when Castine, the soft-hearted, and peace-loving First Leader would be around.

More so, the most important point would be that there weren’t any other Death Apostles who would entrust their body to someone else. And even so, only Holy Fist Palace could do it. Tu Lan was originally convinced by Garen. At first, she was almost killed by Garen. But after always being under his despotic power, and since she had never enjoyed the power and authority of a Death Apostle, she simply treated herself as a subordinate of the Holy Fist Palace who was just slightly above the Upper levels.

Anyway, if Garen wanted to kill her, he would have already done so. He would not have left it till now. Even she did not think about it when she had figured it out, which fit in quite well with Garen’s experiment.

“Too bad this method can only be used once, before the alternative of the Blood Breed’s blood essence is found,” Garen felt slightly sorry. If he could master this method, then he could use Tu Lan’s ability as a Death Apostle and spread her Blood Breed’s bloodline to every part of the world. If anything happens, she could instantly provide support.

“How are there so many good things in this world, and how is it that only you get the benefit of it all?” Black Sethe smiled.

“That’s true too,” Garen smiled. He just kneeled on his knees. From his arms, he took out a small white alarm clock and put it down on the floor, as it quietly guards Tu Lan’s body.

Chapter 749: Advancing 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the cargo ship storehouse

Grina stared at the female Blood Breed who was walking towards her. The other person was clearly just a lower level blood Breed, but that strange feeling, that inexplicable familiarity, seemed to make her think of something.

“What, don’t tell me you can’t recognize me anymore?” The other female Blood Breed stopped, standing ten feet away from her. To an upper level, that distance could be closed in an instant.

“Then what about this?” The female Blood Breed smiled slightly, and her face actually began to melt like wax, automatically forming a new face as though it had a life of its own.

This face was so very familiar, such that before it was even complete, Grina had already taken a slight step back, her expression full of shock.

“You… You’re Tu Lan!!?” Her voice was even slightly shrill.

“Give me the mask.” Tu Lan reached out her hand, maintaining the smile on her face.

“What are you talking about? What mask?” Grina narrowed her eyes slightly, a cold sweat seeping out of her back. Behind her back, her hands were clasped together tightly.

“Why ask the obvious?” Tu Lan looked around her. “It should be in this warehouse, right? Hurry, I don’t want to fight a former friend.”

“If you don’t want to fight, then go back. With your current power and level, why do you have to serve the Holy Fist Palace any longer?” Grina quietly observed her surroundings with the corner of her eyes, just in case anyone else showed up, or perhaps she was looking for a way to escape.

“Serve?” Tu Lan’s smile grew sweeter. “Right now I’m doing this of my own will, where else can I get such joy if not the Holy Fist Palace?”

Tsk…!

Just then, the ship tilted to one side, thrown off balance by the large waves.

Grina instinctively steadied her footing, and abruptly lost sight of Tu Lan. She noticed it suddenly, and retreated backward, holding her arms in front of her to block.

Bam!!!

A round and slender long leg crashed into her arms, coming from above and headed down, just like a war axe.

The collision between the long leg and the two arms created a deep but powerful thud.

Tu Lan jumped a little and spun rapidly, stomping down again.

Bam! It was the sound of another block.

Side kick, downward swing, downward chop. Using completely different combinations and sequences, Tu Lan’s legs took turns, attacking Grina like a storm.

“It’s just like when we were young…” While Tu Lan launched her assault, her gaze was nostalgic.

Grina kept getting pushed back, until she knocked into the crate behind her, then she ducked quickly.

Ker-chak!

The crate was instantly decimated, and many glass cans of beans exploded everywhere, scattering all over the floor.

“Tu Lan…” Grina stared at her, her complexion pale. “Why do you… Why do you obey the Holy Fist Palace when you’re so strong!!”

The two of them split apart abruptly, standing steady a few meters away from each other.

“Why?” Tu Lan stretched out a finger and touched her chin, looking thoughtful. “Ask me again when you can beat me,” she laughed. “Ever since we were young, we grew up together, so let’s settle this with our old rules.”

Grina did not say any more, she just curved her body slightly.

She did not understand why Tu Lan, as strong as she was, actually decided to join an organization founded by a human.

They had been together since ancient times, they joined martial arts and sword fighting classes together, but she had never beaten her. All her life, Tu Lan had been a marker of the ultimate fighter in her heart, someone who could never fail. Perhaps it was not just her, but the same applied to all of the girls they had grown up with back then.

Tu Lan always represented the ultimate power!

Even though so many years had passed since then, and maybe more than half of those girls from back then had already vanished, but that glow from the past was unforgettable.

Powerful, beautiful, lazy. As untouchable as a goddess.

Grina had always been chasing Tu Lan’s back, ever since she became a Blood Breed, she never stopped once.

And now, Tu Lan had even become a Death Apostle, crossing a life-or-death hurdle. No matter when, she was always that powerful and beautiful. Looking at the old friend in front of her, Tu Lan could only sigh inwardly.

They had grown up together over several thousand years, experiencing wars, living several decades in Ancient Greek cities, surviving with each other through the Blood Breeds’ chaotic times. That was the most unforgettable time of her life.

She took care of them, ever since they were young. Whenever they faced a challenge, she would always step up to the task, so that all the girls only saw her strongest, most perfect side. She was always smiling, always dazzling, always fearless…

But no one knew that even she would feel fear, she had also been scared… What they saw, had always only been her perfect facade.

“Grina, give up… Hand over the mask, and I’ll go easy on you.”

Tu Lan’s right leg drew an arch through the air, still at speeds so high that it left an after-image, so that it looked like there were countless legs stacked on top of each other.

Her response was a fierce knee jab.

Grina rushed at her abruptly, lifting her right knee and grabbing Tu Lan’s shoulders with her hands.

Bam!

Her knee was blocked, and the two of them were tangled up, a mess of arms and legs crashing into each other, emitting a series of explosive sounds.

Thwok!

Tu Lan’s fist landed on Grina, but the sound of contact was like hitting wood. The place where Grina was hit in the abdomen rapidly turned to wood, and then it regenerated the places that were destroyed, growing out new flesh and blood that looked like wood, so that she looked completely healed in a second.

“Wood Petrification? Grina, you are still as innocent as ever…” Tu Lan licked her lips.

Psst!

Her body suddenly left a long after-image behind her, as though she had instantaneously become three or four people. They spun around Grina once, and then the three or four figures crashed into the center simultaneously.

Grina’s body flew into the air, just managing to avoid the surround attack. She whipped out a silver chain with a whoosh, and tossed it around her, but all of a sudden her head hurt for a moment, and her movements paused.

Pff!

An intense pain erupted from her chest, and spread all over her body.

Grina was instantly in the chest by Tu Lan’s foot, and she shot out as though from a cannon, crashing hard into the metal cover over the top of the warehouse, sinking into it.

With the crisp sound of leather footsteps, Tu Lan walked up to the wall beneath her, and looked up.

“Pure speed and power, is that the power of your Blood Breed Holy Technique? Looks like we truly are sisters, even the paths we take are so similar. Or perhaps I should say, were so similar.”

Seeing the disappointment in Grina’s eyes, Tu Lan suddenly felt impatient and frustrated. She was no perfect standard, she was also a normal person. She could be happy, scared, furious, jealous. Why did these people always glorify her, why did they always try to force their false ideals onto her, and then look disappointed at her?

That sister from back then was like that, and now Grina as well!!

“Don’t look at me like that…” Her smile vanished.

But Grina did not seem to hear her at all, she had just entered the upper level after all, and she was not very strong in real combat anyway, that was why she was only in charge of espionage this time and not battle. Faced with the oppressive power of the level difference that Tu Lan emitted unknowingly, she could not even move her body, her movements sluggish.

But she did not seem to hear anything, and continued staring at Tu Lan quietly with disappointed eyes.

“I said, don’t look at me like that!!” Tu Lan suddenly lost her temper, her body creating after-images as she appeared in front of Grina, and hit her with her forearm.

Pff!

Blood sprayed everywhere from that hit, spraying out of Grina’s mouth and splattering all over Tu Lan. With that difference in level, even the blood of upper level Blood Breeds lost their activeness, and could no longer return to her body automatically. She could only bleed out like a normal human.

“Grina…” The spray of blood seemed to wake Tu Lan up, and pain flashed through her eyes.

She reached out her hand to caress Grina’s face lightly.

“Why are you so stubborn?”

Grina still said nothing, staring at her quietly, wisps of disappointment and sorrow in her eyes.

“Such… a disgusting gaze!” Rrrip!

Tu Lan tore off Grina’s clothes, revealing her entire upper body. Violently, she reached out to grab Grina’s breasts.

“Where’s the mask?”

“…”

Ssssk!!

Blood splattered everywhere.

Tu Lan actually ripped Grina’s left breast right off.

There was no pity in her eyes, no hesitation, just cruelty.

“Tell me, where’s the mask?”

A sheen of sweat had broken on Grina’s forehead out of sheer pain. She panted a few times, clenched her teeth, and turned away.

“If only it was Rosna, if it were her, she would have told me obediently a long time ago…” Tu Lan said calmly. Looking at Grina’s stubborn face, she began to reminisce.

“The Sleepless Faces will push the Blood Breeds into a bottomless abyss! As a Blood Breed, you actually serve the humans of your own will, you traitor!!” Grina spat at her, but Tu Lan dodged it.

“Whichever side makes me happy, that’s the side I’ll join. Whichever side can give me power, that’s where I belong. Isn’t that very simple?” Tu Lan replied matter-of-factly.

The two were suspended on one of the warehouse’s metal walls, in mid-air. Tu Lan had one hand pierced through the wall to keep her suspended there, whereas Grina was simply embedded into the wall, and kept from moving by the level difference oppression.

“Looks like I’ll just have to do it this way…” Tu Lan calmed her heart, and black whirlpools began to appear slowly in her eyes, meeting Grina’s gaze.

Blood Breed Hypnosis, a special oppression ability only upper level Blood Breeds could use against lower level Blood Breeds. It was a natural talent, like Human Hypnosis.

But strangely, Grina’s gaze only had mild contempt, she did not seem to be controlled at all.

“Give up, all the upper levels who have organization secrets have accepted the Death Apostle chief’s power, so that we won’t be controlled by Hypnosis.”

Tu Lan harrumphed coldly, and pulled back her Hypnosis.

The problem now was that she did not have enough time, if she could not find the mask as soon as possible, her real body would begin to deteriorate after two hours, so she needed to rush back.

Bam!

She knocked Grina out with one fist, dragged her down and tossed her over her shoulder, floating to the ground lightly.

She had already completely controlled the surrounding guards here with her illusions, and anyone further out would not be able to hear the sounds coming from here anyway, that was why no other Blood Breeds from elsewhere had discovered her after so long.

Of course she was not afraid of being discovered, she could even just forcefully control this ship.

But that would take too long.

Brutality flashed through her eyes, Tu Lan glanced at the mountains of crates, and made a cruel decision.

She took out her phone, checked quickly if it was being watched, and then immediately rang a complicated number.

The dial only beeped once, and then the call was picked up.

“Lady Tu Lan?”

“Track the location of this phone of mine, and send ships over immediately,” Tu Lan said in a low voice.

There was a silence on the other side, probably to track her, and a moment later.

“Understood, we will immediately mobilize the navy, and arrive in one hour.”

“Remember to bring some navy soldiers to take over this cargo ship.”

“Understood.”

The call ended, and Tu Lan opened the warehouse door slowly, carrying Grina over her shoulder as they disappeared rapidly down the cargo ship’s corridors.

Chapter 750: Advancing 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Half an hour later…

The whole cargo ship turned around suddenly, heading for a navy port somewhere in America at full speed.

There was the occasional gunshot or scream coming from the ship. It was the Blood Breeds that Tu Lan had controlled with Hypnosis killing their companions.

Tu Lan was sitting in the control room, looking exhausted. The Hypnotized Blood Breed captain was changing the direction of the ship obediently, accelerating as they went.

But even with her Death Apostle level and power, it was still unbearably exhausting to temporarily control so many Blood Breeds at once.

After all, Death Apostles were just Blood Breeds who were slightly stronger than upper levels, their biggest advantage was their immortality. For everything else, they were not nearly as far away from upper level Blood Breeds than others thought. At the very most, one Death Apostle was equal in combat power to four or five upper levels working together, with Ashen being the obvious exception.

So the Death Apostles’ biggest strength was their immortality, their own bodies were not overly powerful. Temporarily controlling so many Blood Breeds at once was a heavy burden even to Death Apostles. Thankfully, Tu Lan practiced the Fantasy Fist, so she could use the Fantasy Fist Fist Technique to influence the humans on the ship. However, this fist technique was only effective for a short while, or it could cause memory loss, it was just that effective in altering memories. That required concise changes to the brain, so she had no choice but to rely on her Blood Breed Hypnosis first, and use the Fantasy Fist as support. The effect was not bad, she could more or less control the whole gigantic cargo ship into changing direction.

And by now, an hour had passed.

********************

Dusk

“The mask is fake?” Hochman hid behind a large black rock by the sea, holding his phone to his hear and listening to the voice coming from the other side.

“Tu Lan has succeeded, return here now,” Garen said calmly through the phone.

Hochman took out his two masks slightly reluctantly, and checked them carefully. Upon closer inspection, he vaguely noticed that this mask did not seem as old as he thought. It was not noticeable at first glance, but when he looked closely, he could see markings to make it look older. Normal people may not have noticed it, but with his upper level senses, he could still notice some little things were amiss.

Bam!!

He smashed the mask onto the stone hard, and it shattered into countless pieces, while a large crater appeared on the rock as well.

Hochman’s expression was cold, those Blood Breeds played him! Ever since he started off, he had never suffered quite so heavy a loss.

Pressing the injury on his shoulder, his expression grew even colder.

“I understand,” he replied on the phone quietly. On the other side, Garen seemed to have noticed that he was pissed off as well, and hung up immediately after a soft ‘Mm’.

Tu Lan was at the level of a Death Apostle, he could not do anything to her. But there should still be one mask with Dahm…

A hint of cold flashed across Hochman’s face. Picking up the phone again and trying to dial it, he went through all his powerful personal connections in his heart. Looking at the incoming call on his phone, however, he quickly decided on the best person for the job.

After dialing the number.

“Hello, I’m Hochman, is this Miss Muneteru Riko? I need your help for a little favor here.”

********************

On a luxury cruise ship

Muneteru Riko had just sat down in her room, still shell-shocked, when her phone rang.

Glancing at the caller, joy flashed through her eyes, and she hurriedly picked up the call.

“Hello, this is Riko. Is this Mr. Hochman? What do you need my help with?”

“Yes… Yes, yes… I understand.” Hanging up the call, Muneteru Riko heaved a long sigh.

There were too many things she wanted to ask, but after picking up the call just now, her brain had gone completely blank, so she could not ask anything.

Hochman and those two people who look like they were filming a movie, what on earth were they?

She had heard of rumors in her supernatural circles, but she had always assumed they were only rumors. Everyone repeated them baselessly, they were merely exaggerated fiction, but she never thought that she would have the chance today to witness such a phenomenon herself.

She quickly dialed a few numbers and made some arrangements as Hochman requested, then she hesitated, and called her father’s number after all. But after the call went through, she hesitated, and only told her father about her plans, without mentioning anything about the cruise ship.

She got up and walked out of the cabin, but found a pale young woman standing guard in front of her door.

She recognized her, the woman was one of the bodyguards who followed Hochman around.

“It’s still very dangerous on the ship, it would be better if you don’t leave your room.”

“Alright.” Muneteru Riko nodded and retreated back into her room.

Judging from that, the assailants must have been chased off the ship, or rather, the assailants had left. It was temporarily safe, then. She released a long breath.

Returning to her room, she suddenly remembered seeing some records about the Sleepless Faces in the books back home. Her family had once purchased a large collection of books from a European family after they weakened and fell, plus she liked reading since young, so she had snuck in and read a lot of them before. She also had a certain level of understanding towards the Sleepless Faces Hochman was looking for, those books had this bit of detailed information about that mask.

When the twelve masks were gathered, one needed to go to a certain spot to find a clue about the Final Mask. And according to the theories of that old family, there were two possibilities for that spot. All of it was recorded in that book, these things were only meant to be a record of ancient history for archeological purposes, and had no value but in collections. When Muneteru Riko thought about it now, however, she vaguely felt her chest beat fiercely.

She realized, that this might be her chance to really delve deep into the supernatural world!

*********************

Dahm crawled out of the underground palace, exhausted. The moonlight shone down from outside, landing on his body and reflecting a shade of deathly white.

Psst!

Thin threads of blood shot out of his arms and thighs suddenly.

Quickly tapping some acupoints to stop the bleeding, Dahm propped his body up and barely ran towards the meeting spot.

This was the result of his activating the First Star and then using the Final Profound, he was completely burned out.

The communicator hidden on his body had already been destroyed in the intense battle just now, so now he could not contact Caesar and the others who were outside, and could only rush out by himself.

Stumbling out of the temple’s forest of stupas, he used the dark corners to sneak his way out of the temple, arriving in a dark alley next to it.

“Where’s the item?” Caesar appeared at the entrance to the alley with a few others in tow.

“With me. Let’s go, now!” Dahm said weakly.

Seeing how weak Dahm looked, a hint of cold hesitation flashed through Caesar’s eyes.

He was wondering if he should finish off Dahm right now, Dahm was so weak, and he had so many people on his side, so he might actually manage it if he tried. After he got the mask, he could easily say that Dahm was killed by the Blood Breeds.

His only concern was whether or not Dahm was truly that weak, or whether it was all just a facade.

Caesar could not resist the temptation of the mask.

This was a chance to increase his longevity and martial arts! See how Hochman and Dahm reached the upper level in just a few years under Lord Fist Saint’s training. At such a speed, if it was Caesar and the others, they should be able to reach upper level as well!!

Since Lord Fist Saint only needed a few years to train up an upper level fighter, he probably would not worry too much about one of them dying…

Before he could help it, Caesar’s gaze on Dahm had changed.

“I’ve informed the intelligence group before coming here, they’ll send reinforcements right away! Let’s go now, before the Blood Breeds get here!” Dahm’s gaze flashed, and he spoke quickly.

Only then did Caesar pull back his gaze slightly.

“Everyone, guard the Marshall, we retreat now!” He waved his hand, and the people from his family hurriedly helped Dahm up, the whole group rapidly retreating from the alley.

*********************

Holy Fist Palace

Garen opened his eyes and looked at the time on the alarm clock, there were several minutes left.

He reached out his hand and held the bottle of blood above Tu Lan.

He squeezed the bottle until it shattered, and the blood inside began to drip down slowly. It looked like the most viscous oil-based liquid, or something like a sugar syrup, slowly dripping onto Tu Lan’s forehead.

Strangely, not one second after the blood dripped onto her, it was rapidly absorbed into Tu Lan’s skin, without leaving a trace behind, as though her skin had absorbed it all.

Psst!

In the pool of blood, Tu Lan opened her eyes abruptly, and her unfocused pupils began to dilate rapidly.

Hsss…

She took a deep breath, and then released it, her chest expanding massively and then deflating like a balloon.

“How is it?” Garen asked quietly.

“Not bad, I’ve handed it over.” Tu Lan nodded, and was not perturbed at all to show her naked body as she stood up in the pool, yanking some robes off the hangar.

“I have two masks here, but they’re hidden somewhere in the cargo ship, so we need to check it. Send someone careful over,” she said quickly.

“No problem,” Garen understood. “Two masks… That’s truly some good news…”

“I also have some bad news,” Tu Lan said with a frown. “I heard from an old acquaintance that all the Blood Breed Death Apostles have vanished, they all went to–”

“To look for the remaining masks?” Garen completed her sentence.

“You know about it?” Tu Lan was slightly surprised.

Garen looked calm.

“It was not hard to guess.” He was already this close to his second Soul Seed, he could gather it at any time, but he kept feeling as though something was missing. Even if this second Soul Seed had not been completely created and hatched, his spirit had already reached an unprecedented peak because of it. His heart was completely clear and light, like a pure mirror of water, without any ripples whatsoever.

In the critical moment when he is gathering his Soul Seed, there must be as few impurities as possible, only the purest will could gather all the power of the soul, and highly compress it. This was also a little trick that Black Sethe taught him to speed up the process.

“Aren’t you afraid that they’ll destroy the masks as soon as they obtain them?” Tu Lan asked in confusion.

“If they obtain the masks, they won’t destroy them so easily…” Garen said calmly. “Nobody would be willing to give up that chance. This is a chance to be the first to break the Death Apostles’ myth of immortality…”

Once they obtain the Final Mask and achieve the Original Bloodline, they would be able to truly threaten and suppress the other Blood Apostles. Blood Apostles would no longer be symbols of immortality, and when that happens, the one possessing the Original Bloodline would truly be the only dictator, the strongest in the world!

Even at the level of power that Garen was at now, he still did not dare to wage full-on war with the Blood Breed Death Apostles, simply because he could not kill the Death Apostles. If he could not kill them, that just meant both sides would end up injured, and both would have lost.

That was not what Garen hoped for, and neither was it what the Blood Breeds wanted.